<items><item><title>Data Science Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WKFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WDKJ WEKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WAH- WDH- WJJ- WKJ- WAF- WCH- WGJ- WBAB WBH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are you looking for a supportive, collaborative workplace with great teams and inspiring leaders? You&#8217;ve come to the right place. We&#8217;re looking for ambitious people who share our values and want to make every day better for people around the world. If this sounds like you, and the career below sounds exciting, we&#8217;d like to hear from you.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Working Arrangement&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Hybrid&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;This position has accountability as a data domain and data visualization subject matter expert for the Group Benefits Advanced Analytics Team.&amp;nbsp; The successful candidate will be responsible for delivering model output and analytics to the Group Benefits business and will work with Data Scientists to build new models by completing exploratory data analysis, data sourcing, and maintaining existing models.&amp;nbsp; They will be responsible for creating and managing scores/dashboards that deliver model outcomes and ensures a robust feedback loop for modelling purposes.&amp;nbsp; They will join the team as we embark on cloud native architecture in Azure Platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Support Advanced Analytics projects through data sourcing, exploration, cleanup, manipulation &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Support data delivery from both internal and external sources; works with data subject matter experts, data scientists, Group Benefits Sponsor Reporting, and the Canadian Data Office (CDO) across Canadian Division&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Tactical support of data validation, consolidation, and cleansing processes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work with Data Scientists to transform business requests into value-add deliverables including data mapping, data aggregation, data cleansing &amp;amp; other data-related processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Automate processes to improve turnaround time on data availability and increase efficiencies in the model building process&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Deliver ad hoc analysis by analyzing structured and unstructured data using statistical techniques &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Group Benefits Advanced Analytics subject matter expert responsible for deploying model output to business end users&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Works closely with data scientists and business teams to deploy model output through data visualization tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Communicate analytical concepts through visualizations and presentations to non-technical business users&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monitor data inputs and outputs for data drift and recommends rebuilds of models based on monitoring standards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Supports Manulife&#8217;s Advanced Analytics&#8217; Model Development Lifecycle with Intake &amp;amp; Prioritization, Forward Design, Data Prep, and Insight Action.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;University degree in quantitative based field (Math, Sci, Engineering, Comp Sci)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3-5 years business experience with 2+ year of data analytics experience preferred.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills &lt;span class="WFN2"&gt;(written/visual/verbal)&lt;/span&gt; with specific experience communicating technical concepts to non-technical audiences&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent attention to detail with proven ability to organize and prioritize&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Thorough understanding of and experience with data gathering, extraction, transformation and staging of data for consumption&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advanced working SQL knowledge and experience working with relational databases and SQL&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Visualization expert with tools such as Power BI, R Shiny and/or Tableau&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in building ETL pipelines to perform feature engineering on large-scale datasets using Python and Spark&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of statistical concepts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proven relationship management skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Intimate understanding of the model lifecycle, experience managing data science projects with business end users&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of VBA code nice to have&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Every career at Manulife/John Hancock provides the opportunity to learn new skills and move your career forward. Ready to make an impact somewhere? What are you waiting for? Apply today.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About John Hancock and Manulife &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;John Hancock is a unit of Manulife Financial Corporation, a leading international financial services group that helps people make their decisions easier and lives better. We operate primarily as John Hancock in the United States, and Manulife globally, including Canada, Asia and Europe. We provide financial advice, insurance and wealth and asset management solutions for individuals, groups and institutions. Assets under management and administration by Manulife and its subsidiaries were CAD$1.3 trillion (US$1.1 trillion) as of June 30, 2021. Manulife Financial Corporation trades as MFC on the TSX, NYSE, and PSE, and under 945 on the SEHK. Manulife can be found at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="manulife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.manulife.com/"&gt;manulife.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;One of the largest life insurers in the United States, John Hancock supports more than 10 million Americans with a broad range of financial products, including &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="life insurance opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/life-insurance.html"&gt;life insurance&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="annuities opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhannuities.com/Marketing/default.aspx"&gt;annuities&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="investments opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhinvestments.com/"&gt;investments&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="401(k) plans opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/retirement.html"&gt;401(k) plans&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="education savings plans opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhinvestments.com/529"&gt;education savings plans&lt;/a&gt;. Additional information about John Hancock may be found at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="johnhancock.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/index.html"&gt;johnhancock.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;At Manulife&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;/John&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Hancock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;develop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;and&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;retain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WFN2"&gt;retention,&amp;nbsp;advancement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;colour&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is our priority to remove barriers to&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;provide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="recruitment@manulife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:recruitment@manulife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WFN2"&gt;recruitment@manulife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Data-Science-Engineer_JR22021357-1</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298819/manulife_rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Manulife</company></item></items>