<items><item><title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WKFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WDKJ WEKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WBH- WEH- WKJ- WLJ- WBF- WDH- WHJ- WBAB WCH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are you looking for a supportive, collaborative workplace with great teams and inspiring leaders? You&#8217;ve come to the right place. We&#8217;re looking for ambitious people who share our values and want to make every day better for people around the world. If this sounds like you, and the career below sounds exciting, we&#8217;d like to hear from you.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Working Arrangement&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Hybrid&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The candidate will be a part of the Group Advanced Analytics team and will be tasked with packaging models, automating workflow, and operationalizing analytics solutions to generate business value to various parts of the JH/Manulife. The ideal candidate must be an advanced programmer with a good understanding of Data Science, Data Engineering, Application development, Software Engineering, and DevOps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Typical Qualification: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s degree in Computer Science, Data Science, Applied Math, Engineering, Operation Research, Statistics, or other related quantitative fields&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;MS or Ph.D. preferred&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Accountabilities: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Brings a unique skillset that overlaps with Data Science, Data Engineering, Application Development, Software Engineering and DevOps&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Has a clear understanding of how to convert a model into a user-friendly application&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage data science infrastructure to streamline model development and deployment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Architecting, developing, optimizing, and owning the deployment of ML functionalities into production systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and evaluate new approaches for handling high-volume real-time data streams in an inferencing environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Defining best practices for code, APIs, and frameworks that will lay the foundation for MLOps capabilities. Apply state of the art from research and practice of ML to Manulife\'s products&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proposing appropriate tools &lt;span class="WGN2"&gt;(languages/libraries/frameworks)&lt;/span&gt; for implementing projects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working closely with Infrastructure architects to design scalable and cost-effective solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Following Software Deployment and QA processes and MLOps best practices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop measurements and feedback systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Model testing, production and deployment and Continuous &lt;span class="WGN2"&gt;integration/continuous&lt;/span&gt; delivery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work as part of a team with frequent interactions with data scientists. Daily activities may also require close touchpoints with architecture, cloud, data engineering, and risk management teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mentor associates and peers on DevOps/MLOps best practices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Experiences: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of hands-on experience with large-scale systems in software engineering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 year of experience in productionizing code through DevOps pipeline (git, Jenkins pipeline, code scan)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with big data processing and building data APIs. Experience with automated data quality frameworks is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working experience in building and deploying machine learning models as REST-based API using Flask, Elasticsearch, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong software development skills (+3 years working experience) with proficiency in Python&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advanced working SQL knowledge and experience working with relational databases and SQL&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in infrastructure, including Cloud Computing, Linux OS, Networks, Docker, Kubernetes, RDBMS and NoSQL Databases&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working with cloud native architecture (PaaS) using Azure stack preferably and experience with Azure ML, DataBricks (Spark), Azure Data Factory will be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in building ETL pipelines to perform feature engineering on large-scale dataset using Spark&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An ability to balance a sense of urgency with shipping high quality and pragmatic solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with user interface design (UX, PowerBI, node.js) and iterative customer-driven design processes would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Infrastructure as code (Terraform/ARM) is an asset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expertise delivering analytics &amp;amp; machine learning products, with a deep understanding of agile product delivery in an enterprise environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Every career at Manulife/John Hancock provides the opportunity to learn new skills and move your career forward. Ready to make an impact somewhere? What are you waiting for? Apply today.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About John Hancock and Manulife &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;John Hancock is a unit of Manulife Financial Corporation, a leading international financial services group that helps people make their decisions easier and lives better. We operate primarily as John Hancock in the United States, and Manulife globally, including Canada, Asia and Europe. We provide financial advice, insurance and wealth and asset management solutions for individuals, groups and institutions. Assets under management and administration by Manulife and its subsidiaries were CAD$1.3 trillion (US$1.1 trillion) as of June 30, 2021. Manulife Financial Corporation trades as MFC on the TSX, NYSE, and PSE, and under 945 on the SEHK. Manulife can be found at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="manulife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.manulife.com/"&gt;manulife.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;One of the largest life insurers in the United States, John Hancock supports more than 10 million Americans with a broad range of financial products, including &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="life insurance opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/life-insurance.html"&gt;life insurance&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="annuities opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhannuities.com/Marketing/default.aspx"&gt;annuities&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="investments opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhinvestments.com/"&gt;investments&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="401(k) plans opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/retirement.html"&gt;401(k) plans&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="education savings plans opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhinvestments.com/529"&gt;education savings plans&lt;/a&gt;. Additional information about John Hancock may be found at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="johnhancock.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/index.html"&gt;johnhancock.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;At Manulife&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;/John&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Hancock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;develop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;and&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;retain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGN2"&gt;retention,&amp;nbsp;advancement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;colour&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is our priority to remove barriers to&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;provide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="recruitment@manulife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:recruitment@manulife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGN2"&gt;recruitment@manulife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Senior-Machine-Learning-Engineer_JobReq0448033</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298819/manulife_rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Manulife</company></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WKFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WDKJ WEKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WBH- WEH- WKJ- WLJ- WBF- WDH- WHJ- WBAB WCH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid12-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid12-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-13" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are you looking for a supportive, collaborative workplace with great teams and inspiring leaders? You&#8217;ve come to the right place. We&#8217;re looking for ambitious people who share our values and want to make every day better for people around the world. If this sounds like you, and the career below sounds exciting, we&#8217;d like to hear from you.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Working Arrangement&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Hybrid&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The Senior Data Scientist develops and implements analytics enabled solutions to improve business process, to generate insights, and reduce risks across North America Retirement Operations. This position reports to the Director, Risk &amp;amp; Control Governance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Develops and implements analytics enabled solutions to improve business process and controls&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Leverage extensive theoretical and practical knowledge of advanced analytic methods and algorithms, understanding their utility in different problem domains (sparse data, rare event detection, etc), evaluation methodologies and pitfalls, and stays on top of industry &amp;amp; academic developments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Works on problems of diverse scope / complexity where analysis of situations or data requires an in-depth evaluation of a variety of factors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong ability to generate relevant, actionable insights based on iterative data analysis, translate data-driven output into business language, and to make appropriate recommendations to respective business stakeholders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Independently provides analysis on datasets of significant complexity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Quickly able to develop enough business insight to connect data sources across multiple diverse and complicated systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Recommends implementable solutions to (or in collaboration with) business partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Considers change management in all aspects of their work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Engages in ongoing discussions and moves others towards a position, appealing to their needs and interests to gain acceptance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Maintains a strong internal network, begins to network with more senior stakeholders within the organization. Begins to develop an external network and develop their own brand, particular in their own practice area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Shares ideas with others, leads brainstorming sessions. Ensures all voices are heard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Actively seeks out coaching and incorporates feedback into their work. Promotes best practices within the team. Shares technical expertise with others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Owns their career development. Takes advantage of available resources to advance their technical and business skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Understands how their project supports broader business strategy, including the core drivers of business value. Able to prepare a business case on the benefits of their assigned work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Incorporates lessons learned throughout the business into their work. Engages with global counterparts to share learnings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong ability to construct systematic process to implement analytics insights and solutions, this includes (but not limited to):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;1) designing a process with multiple relevant parties with clear specifications of roles and responsibilities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;2) identifying required tasks, system / data flow and contingency&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3) specifying check-and-balance throughout the process&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;4) establishing rigorous tracking and closed-loop learning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;5) implement such process in a scalable way&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Other responsibilities as required based on business priorities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;Education, Experience and Skills:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Advanced degree in Statistics, Math, Computer Science, or Engineering; or Bachelor&#8217;s degree with equivalent technical experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Generally, a minimum of 5 years of applicable experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Advanced knowledge of programming languages and concepts, e.g., Python&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Insurance or Financial Services industry experience and strong knowledge of the Retirement business preferred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Demonstrated experience exhibiting innovation and leadership in proposing new strategies and/or tactics based on analysis findings&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with Big Data platforms desired&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working with link analysis and graph databases is a plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with analysis of unstructured data desired&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with working Agile desired&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Expert in basic and advanced statistical tests, distributions, maximum likelihood estimators, statistical modelling techniques (XGBoost, regression, cluster / factor / principle components, decision tree, survival analysis, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Advanced knowledge of different techniques and knowledge of machine learning algorithms. Basic knowledge of AI toolkits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Expert in data visualization tools such as Tableau, Power BI, QlikView, open source data visualization libraries - ggplot and d3.js&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Advanced knowledge of common database querying languages such as SQL. Capability of applying a systematic, structured approach to explore / navigate / mine massive amount of data, structured or un-structured, to uncover hidden patterns / insights. Strong working knowledge of relational database models (e.g. data vaulting techniques, rules tables).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Solid understanding of risk identification within a process and how to mitigate key risks through use of data analytics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Turn statistical and computational analysis into user-friendly graphs, charts, and animation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to communicate results and educate others through reports and presentations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Able to prioritize, meet deadlines, and be results orientated&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Able to display empathy with the business and anticipate their push back and areas of concern&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Adaptable and open to change&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Every career at Manulife/John Hancock provides the opportunity to learn new skills and move your career forward. Ready to make an impact somewhere? What are you waiting for? Apply today.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About John Hancock and Manulife &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;John Hancock is a unit of Manulife Financial Corporation, a leading international financial services group that helps people make their decisions easier and lives better. We operate primarily as John Hancock in the United States, and Manulife globally, including Canada, Asia and Europe. We provide financial advice, insurance and wealth and asset management solutions for individuals, groups and institutions. Assets under management and administration by Manulife and its subsidiaries were CAD$1.3 trillion (US$1.1 trillion) as of June 30, 2021. Manulife Financial Corporation trades as MFC on the TSX, NYSE, and PSE, and under 945 on the SEHK. Manulife can be found at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="manulife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.manulife.com/"&gt;manulife.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;One of the largest life insurers in the United States, John Hancock supports more than 10 million Americans with a broad range of financial products, including &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="life insurance opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/life-insurance.html"&gt;life insurance&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="annuities opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhannuities.com/Marketing/default.aspx"&gt;annuities&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="investments opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhinvestments.com/"&gt;investments&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="401(k) plans opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/retirement.html"&gt;401(k) plans&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="education savings plans opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhinvestments.com/529"&gt;education savings plans&lt;/a&gt;. Additional information about John Hancock may be found at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="johnhancock.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/index.html"&gt;johnhancock.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;At Manulife&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;/John&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Hancock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;develop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;and&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;retain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGN2"&gt;retention,&amp;nbsp;advancement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;colour&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is our priority to remove barriers to&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;provide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="recruitment@manulife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:recruitment@manulife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGN2"&gt;recruitment@manulife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Halifax-Nova-Scotia/Senior-Data-Scientist_JR22032980-1</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298819/manulife_rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Manulife</company></item><item><title>Assistant Vice President, Group Functions Data Office</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WKFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WDKJ WEKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WBH- WEH- WKJ- WLJ- WBF- WDH- WHJ- WBAB WCH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are you looking for a supportive, collaborative workplace with great teams and inspiring leaders? You&#8217;ve come to the right place. We&#8217;re looking for ambitious people who share our values and want to make every day better for people around the world. If this sounds like you, and the career below sounds exciting, we&#8217;d like to hear from you.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Working Arrangement&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Hybrid&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;About the Job&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;The Assistant Vice President, Group Functions Data Office is responsible for leading and executing a strategic roadmap for collecting, storing, processing enterprise &amp;amp; divisional data to support and enable analytics, digital transformation and operational improvements. This involves researching, recommending and choosing optimal solutions to manage and implement modern data architecture as well as maintaining and monitoring the success of these solutions. The incumbent must have a passion for how data can be leveraged and used to drive deeper, meaningful insights that enhance the customer experience, grow our businesses, minimize risk and engage our employees globally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The role involves creating a team of highly skilled data engineering professionals while guiding and implementing industry best practices around data governance to ensure business and analytical needs are well understood and satisfied. The incumbent will participate in long range strategic planning that addresses complex data management challenges. Projects are highly complex, multi-faceted and involve many stakeholders. The overall accountabilities support analytics, executive decision making and direct customer- facing activities. In addition, the role provides thought leadership and consultative support to the many data activities across the organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As the&amp;nbsp;AVP, Group Functions Data Office, you will:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Enable software development across key Group Functions priorities through an embedded team of data analysts and data engineers, with a focus on accelerating consistent implementation of engineering patterns and approaches to deliver on key business priorities;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Aligning to and in partnership with the Global Data Office, guide, contribute and adopt the development and evolution of engineering patterns, best practices, and reference implementations to consistently increase the rate of sharing and reuse across the globe;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Promote and adopt data governance and stewardship by embedding the concepts within the software development lifecycle;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oversee and develop a distributed team of data analysts and data engineers;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability &amp;amp; preference to work in an Agile environment;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bring strong leadership and a collaboration mindset to work horizontally across the firm to realize a comprehensive data strategy;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand complex data integrations and business information models to drive the simplification of the data ecosystem;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bring strong operational and engineering excellence and ability to drive continuous improvement;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintain an enterprise view on the evolution of data technologies and software engineering, and nurture experimentation in support of understanding emerging technologies;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with business partners, analytics teams, software developers, platform engineers, and engineering leadership to uncover pain points and opportunities to accelerate the delivery of new value through software;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lead, drive and influence innovative data solutions for GWAM working closely with Technology and Operations teams.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Specifically, for Global Data Technology, the role will drive, lead and manage:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;(1) &lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Modern Data Architecture in Azure:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; Setting the strategic rollout and delivery of proven as well as emerging tooling to ensure that data pipelines are scalable, repeatable and secure serving multiple users within the organization. The incumbent is responsible for all providing leadership and direction for highly complex, multi-faceted big data initiatives associated the following functions areas:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Translate complex functional and technical requirements into detailed architecture, design and high performing capabilities;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lead the design and build of data patterns and services - both batch, real-time and complex event handing - leveraging open technologies;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ensure the timely delivery and constant communication of commitments meeting the expectations of stakeholders;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Effectively manage operational risk and change with a continuous focus on process improvements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;(2) People and Relationship Management: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Responsible for providing information, expertise and direction to a team of full time and contract staff, specifically:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Responsible for all team goal planning, achievement assessments and employee development plans;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work closely with analytic and data management teams to determine resource requirements and planning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Encourage and ensure all team members participate in cross-training and job sharing; create an annual plan for skill development and advanced technical capabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lead workshops, data engineering meetups, user group facilitation and meet with key stakeholders globally to drive and grow data engineering talent across Manulife.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Build and foster strong relationships with key stakeholders across the Advanced &lt;/span&gt;Analytics and Group Functions community&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;(3) Governance and Controls: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Responsible for ensuring all data management processes conform to standard operating procedures and aligns with how a modern data architecture aligns to enterprise technology standards and policies; contribute and provide guidance around data quality, metadata management, data stewardship and security, and access controls.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;(4) Innovation and Continuous Improvement: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Provide thought leadership and guidance around advancing new data technologies and capabilities that are value-driven; work closely with Manulife&#8217;s innovation teams (i.e., LOFT), remain current with industry advancements working closely external vendors as well connected to the Apache Foundation projects; develop actionable plans to improve operations and capabilities that have real cost, time and quality benefits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Over 10 years of demonstrated success architecting and delivering data-centric initiatives and platforms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Over 10 years of demonstrated experience with Waterfall and Agile project delivery methodologies, as well as DevOps principles, test-driven development, continuous integration, and other software development lifecycle approaches to accelerate the delivery of new features&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Over 10 years&#8217; experience in Financial Services (e.g., banking, brokerages, asset management, insurance)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Robust understanding of various data design patterns and architectural principles (e.g. Kimball vs. Inmon models, designing for the cloud, Lambda architecture)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experimenting with emerging technologies and understanding how they will impact what comes next&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A capacity for constant learning from both success and failure, and remaining open to change and continuous improvement&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent organizational and problem-solving abilities that enable you to manage through creative abrasion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong verbal and written communication with the ability to effectively articulate and communicate technical vision, possibilities, and outcomes across all levels in the organization&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developing junior data analysts and data engineers, and a passion for growing staff within the &lt;span class="WGN2"&gt;organization&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Last year Manulife spent over $1 BN on technology.&amp;nbsp; You will be working with:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Operational and Informational data integration technologies (Apache Open Projects, Kafka, IBM MQ, Informatica, Hadoop, Web Services)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cloud infrastructure and other components supporting a highly-automated global engineering platform&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Open source technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Languages such as SQL, Hive-SQL, Java, JavaScript, Python, .NET, HTML5, CSS3, Swift and other similar technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Business Intelligence &amp;amp; Analytics tools (e.g. Python, R, SAS, Power BI, Qlik, Tableau)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Variety of data platforms (e.g. Synapse, ADLS, Databricks, Hadoop, Spark, SQL Server, Oracle, H-Base, MongoDB)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cutting edge Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning software&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Digital and mobile technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Every career at Manulife/John Hancock provides the opportunity to learn new skills and move your career forward. Ready to make an impact somewhere? What are you waiting for? Apply today.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About John Hancock and Manulife &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;John Hancock is a unit of Manulife Financial Corporation, a leading international financial services group that helps people make their decisions easier and lives better. We operate primarily as John Hancock in the United States, and Manulife globally, including Canada, Asia and Europe. We provide financial advice, insurance and wealth and asset management solutions for individuals, groups and institutions. Assets under management and administration by Manulife and its subsidiaries were CAD$1.3 trillion (US$1.1 trillion) as of June 30, 2021. Manulife Financial Corporation trades as MFC on the TSX, NYSE, and PSE, and under 945 on the SEHK. Manulife can be found at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="manulife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.manulife.com/"&gt;manulife.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;One of the largest life insurers in the United States, John Hancock supports more than 10 million Americans with a broad range of financial products, including &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="life insurance opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/life-insurance.html"&gt;life insurance&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="annuities opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhannuities.com/Marketing/default.aspx"&gt;annuities&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="investments opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhinvestments.com/"&gt;investments&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="401(k) plans opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/retirement.html"&gt;401(k) plans&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="education savings plans opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.jhinvestments.com/529"&gt;education savings plans&lt;/a&gt;. Additional information about John Hancock may be found at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="johnhancock.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.johnhancock.com/index.html"&gt;johnhancock.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;At Manulife&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;/John&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Hancock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;develop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;and&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;retain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGN2"&gt;retention,&amp;nbsp;advancement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;colour&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is our priority to remove barriers to&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;provide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="recruitment@manulife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:recruitment@manulife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGN2"&gt;recruitment@manulife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Assistant-Vice-President--Group-Functions-Data-Office_JR22021268</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298819/manulife_rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Manulife</company></item></items>