<items><item><title>Senior Data Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WFFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WLJJ WMJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WDF- WLH- WMH- WDD- WFF- WIH- WAAB WEF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are you looking for a supportive, collaborative workplace with great teams and inspiring leaders? You&#8217;ve come to the right place. We&#8217;re looking for ambitious people who share our values and want to make every day better for people around the world. If this sounds like you, and the career below sounds exciting, we&#8217;d like to hear from you.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hands on experience in Azure Development, worked on Azure storage, Azure SQL Database, Azure Synapse Analytics, Azure &lt;span class="WFL2"&gt;Databricks/HDInsight,&lt;/span&gt; Virtual machines, AZURE AD, Azure Web Apps and Azure Kubernetes Service.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide hands-on expertise on Cloud technology, Azure best practices for cloud design and implementation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborates with architects and engineering teams to evaluate and document reference architectures, patterns, and technology selection for cloud application architectures.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with cloud migration process from HDP data lake to Microsoft Azure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding of Microsoft Identity and Access Management products such as Azure AD, ADFS, Azure AD Connect, Conditional Access, Azure AD Proxy, SAML&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide recommendations with respect to cloud migrations and prepare technical implementation roadmaps for Azure adoption, and experience with various Azure migration scenarios&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In-depth knowledge of security and IAM/RBAC within Azure, including the management and operation of Azure ASG, Azure Key Vault, Azure NSG, Azure AD, Azure Security Center, Azure Policy, and Azure Management Group/Subscriptions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hands on experience on Azure infrastructure compute, storage, database, DR, monitoring, backup and network management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in using Azure DevOps CI/CD pipeline&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Playing a key role in mentoring other staff members and a proven track record in knowledge transfer to other team members and departments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Azure Storage, Azure SDK, Azure PaaS Services, Azure SQL, Azure Kubernetes Service, basic Azure Networking technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience &amp;nbsp;with ETL and big data tool-chains such as those provided by Azure &lt;span class="WFL2"&gt;Databricks/HDInsight,&lt;/span&gt; Azure Data Factory and Azure Synapse Analytics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with infrastructure automation tools such as Puppet, Ansible, PowerShell, Azure ARM, or Terraform.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to proficiently write code in Python, Node.js, Bash (shell), PowerShell, or other similar languages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experienced with the Hadoop ecosystem and toolset &#8211; HDFS, MapReduce, Spark, Python, Scala, Hive and Oozie.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience using Git for source control management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of pipeline-automation tools such as Jenkins, Azure DevOps, or other comparable tools.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Every career at Manulife/John Hancock provides the opportunity to learn new skills and move your career forward. Ready to make an impact somewhere? What are you waiting for? Apply today.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About Manulife&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;About Manulife Manulife Financial Corporation is a leading international financial services provider that helps people make their decisions easier and lives better. With our global headquarters in Toronto, Canada, we operate as Manulife across our offices in Canada, Asia, and Europe, and primarily as John Hancock in the United States. We provide financial advice, insurance, and our global wealth and asset management segment, Manulife Investment Management, serves individuals, institutions and retirement plan members worldwide. At the end of 2020, we had more than 37,000 employees, over 118,000 agents, and thousands of distribution partners, serving over 30 million customers. As of March 31, 2021, we had CAD$1.3 trillion (US$1.0 trillion) in assets under management and administration, and in the previous 12 months we made $31.3 billion in payments to our customers. Our principal operations are in Asia, Canada and the United States where we have served customers for more than 155 years. We trade as \'MFC\' on the Toronto, New York, and the Philippine stock exchanges and under \'945\' in Hong Kong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Manulife is an Equal Opportunity Employer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;At Manulife&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;/John&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Hancock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, we embrace our diversity. We strive to attract,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;develop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;and&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;retain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;a workforce that is as diverse as the customers we serve and to foster an inclusive work environment that embraces the strength of cultures and individuals. We are committed to fair recruitment, &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WFL2"&gt;retention,&amp;nbsp;advancement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and compensation, and we administer all of our practices and programs without discrimination on the basis of race, ancestry, place of origin,&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;colour&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, ethnic origin, citizenship, religion or religious beliefs, creed, sex (including pregnancy and pregnancy-related conditions), sexual orientation, genetic characteristics, veteran status, gender identity, gender expression, age, marital status, family status, disability, or any other ground protected by applicable law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is our priority to remove barriers to&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;provide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;equal access to employment. A Human Resources representative will work with applicants who request a reasonable accommodation during the application process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;All information shared during the accommodation request process will be stored and used in a manner that is consistent with&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;applicable laws and Manulife/John Hancock policies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;To request a reasonable accommodation in the application process, contact &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:recruitment@manulife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WFL2"&gt;recruitment@manulife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://manulife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MFCJH_Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Senior-Data-Engineer_JobReq0433571-1</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298819/manulife_rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Manulife</company></item></items>