<items><item><title>Senior Account Manager, Networking - Canada</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Do you want to join a fun, creative company that is on the cutting edge of amazing technologies? NVIDIA&#8217;s fast-growing Datacenter Networking Business (a merger of NVIDIA, Mellanox, and Cumulus) is looking for a strong &lt;b&gt;Senior Account Manager&lt;/b&gt; who will bring technical and business insight to help grow the Ethernet &amp;amp; Infiniband switch business in Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you&#8217;ll be doing:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You will be an integral part of a small, nimble team that is responsible for a significant and rapidly growing recurring revenue contribution to the Enterprise products group, the fastest growing and most dynamic segment at NVIDIA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Working with the channel team to build alliances and expand our quality channels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Partnering with the technical team on designs, competition etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being the link between the overlay team and the field (roadmap updates, tech communications&#8230;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Define and drive the discussions, strategy and be the specialist in the team, enabling our key partners to drive Networking solutions sales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Delivering a concise state of the business in the region at any given time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What we need to see:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s degree or higher in related field (or equivalent experience).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;6+ years of technical sales or Product Management background in the Ethernet market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience from Ethernet switch companies &#8211; advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Excellent communication skills in English. Additionally French will be an advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;An understanding of the business issues of large enterprises (FSI, Healthcare, Manufacturing, etc) &lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;Networking/Switching/Data&lt;/span&gt; Center technology background.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Self-starter, with a &#8216;can-do&#8217; attitude and ability to multitask and prioritize in a demanding environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Travel is required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Excellent communication and presentation abilities. Excellent interpersonal skills, peer networking and team play, colleagues and customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ways to stand out from the crowd:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong Background in modern Data Center networking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with deep learning, data science, and NVIDIA GPUs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Successful management of technical products throughout their lifecycle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Love technology and passionate about what you do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;NVIDIA is widely considered to be one of the technology world&#8217;s most desirable employers. We have some of the most forward-thinking and hardworking people in the world working for us. Are you creative and autonomous? Do you love a challenge? If so, we want to hear from you. Come, join our Datacenter communication Infrastructure team and help us build the scalable communication platforms driving our success in this dynamic and quickly growing field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;NVIDIA is committed to fostering a diverse work environment and proud to be an equal opportunity employer. As we highly value diversity in our current and future employees, we do not discriminate (including in our hiring and promotion practices) on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, gender expression, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, disability status or any other&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://nvidia.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/NVIDIAExternalCareerSite/job/Canada-Remote/Senior-Account-Manager--Networking---Canada_JR1946052</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298516/nvidia-logo.jpg</logo><company>NVIDIA</company></item><item><title>Compute Performance Developer Technology Engineer - CUDA</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Compute Performance Developer Technology Engineer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;NVIDIA is hiring passionate, world-class computer scientists to work in its Compute Developer Technology (Devtech) team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;In this role, you will research and develop techniques to GPU-accelerate leading applications in high performance computing fields within scientific computing, computational engineering, and data science. You will be performing in-depth analysis and optimization to ensure the best possible performance on current and next-generation GPU architectures. This involves:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working directly with key application developers to understand the current and future problems they are solving, crafting and optimizing core parallel algorithms and data structures to provide the best solutions using GPUs, through both reference code development and direct contribution to the applications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating closely with diverse groups at NVIDIA such as the architecture, research, libraries, tools, and system software teams to influence the design of next-generation architectures, software platforms, and programming models, by investigating the impact on application performance and developer productivity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will need to travel from time to time for conferences and for on-site visits with developers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What we need to see:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A BS, MS, or PhD degree from a leading university in an engineering or computer science related discipline with 3+ years of relevant experience. While not a requirement, domain expertise in telecommunications, medical imaging, machine learning, deep learning, or natural sciences is helpful.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Programming fluency in C/C++ and/or Fortran with a deep understanding of software design, programming techniques, and algorithms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong mathematical fundamentals, including linear algebra and numerical methods.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with parallel programming, ideally CUDA C/C++ and OpenACC.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and organization skills, with a logical approach to problem solving, good time management, and task prioritization skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;With highly competitive salaries and a comprehensive benefits package, NVIDIA is widely considered to be one of the technology industry\'s most desirable employers. We have some of the most brilliant and talented people in the world working with us and our engineering teams are growing fast in some of the hottest and state of the art fields: Deep Learning, Artificial Intelligence, Autonomous Vehicles, Supercomputing and more. Are you a creative and autonomous computer scientist with a real passion for parallel computing? If so, we want to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;#deeplearning&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://nvidia.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/NVIDIAExternalCareerSite/job/Canada-Toronto/Compute-Performance-Developer-Technology-Engineer---CUDA_JR1926525</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298516/nvidia-logo.jpg</logo><company>NVIDIA</company></item><item><title>Software Engineer, Omniverse - New College Grad</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;For two decades, we have pioneered visual computing, the art and science of computer graphics. With our invention of the GPU - the engine of modern visual computing - the field has grown to encompass video games, movie production, product design, medical diagnosis and scientific research. Today, we stand at the beginning of the next era, the AI computing era, ignited by a new computing model, GPU deep learning. This new model - where deep neural networks are trained to recognize patterns from massive amounts of data - has shown to be deeply effective at solving the most complex problems in everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are looking for a Software Engineer to further the development of our high-performance compute graph &#8211; OmniGraph - on top of our Omniverse platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you\'ll be doing:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Key member involved in the design, development, optimization, and documentation of our OmniGraph project for our Omniverse platform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ensuring a high level of architectural quality, performance in the developed code and features&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Debugging and fixing deficiencies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Support members of other teams / clients as they adopt the technology developed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Support the technology on multiple hardware platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Partnering and collaborating with peers and managers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What we need to see:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong Python and C++ skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Graduating or will recently graduate from BS/MS in Computer Science or equivalent experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Minimum 1+year of relevant experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working in large scale code bases/ projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A solid sense of software architecture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proven ability to optimize code / data for performance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Phenomenal team player and collaborator&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ways to stand out from the crowd:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with CUDA or GPU&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Knowledge with computer graphics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Knowledge / experience with HPC architectures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience withcompilers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Understanding of USD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;NVIDIA is widely considered to be one of the technology world&#8217;s most desirable employers. We have some of the most forward-thinking and hardworking people in the world working for us. Are you creative and autonomous? Do you love the challenge of crafting the highest performance &amp;amp; lowest power silicon possible? If so, we want to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://nvidia.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/NVIDIAExternalCareerSite/job/Canada-Toronto/Software-Engineer--Omniverse---New-College-Grad_JR1946942-1</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298516/nvidia-logo.jpg</logo><company>NVIDIA</company></item><item><title>Senior Graphics Tools and Pipeline Engineer - DRIVE Sim</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Autonomous vehicles are redefining the way we live, work, and play&#8212;creating safer and more efficient roads. These revolutionary benefits require massive computational horsepower and large-scale production software expertise. Tapping into decades-long experience in high-performance computing, imaging, and AI, NVIDIA has built a software-defined, end-to-end platform for the transportation industry that enables continuous improvement and continuous deployment through over the air updates. It delivers everything needed to develop autonomous vehicles at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Simulation gives us the capability to test an autonomous vehicle in a near-infinite variety of conditions and scenarios before it even reaches the road, accelerating development time and improving the reliability of the self-driving stack at the same time. We&#8217;re looking for a talented Graphics Tools and Pipeline Engineer to join the DRIVE Sim team and help make it all a reality. This meaningful role will see you working with technical visionaries within the company to define and deliver a simulation environment that advances the state of the art in autonomous vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Priorities often change in a fast-paced environment like ours. Some of the things you will work on:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Design and development of asset creation and management tools ranging from exporters, to content creation tools, to asset management tools, and even implement real-time runtime functionality for specific types of content&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Work with content creators, designers, and other specialists to capture requirements and ensure tool design specifications are met&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Work with the design team to architect, engineer, and implement new systems and tools to facilitate the creation of exciting new content&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Directly impact the future of self-driving car technology!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What we need to see:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Bachelor of Science or equivalent experience in Computer Science, Artificial Intelligence, Applied Math, or related field or equivalent work experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;4+ years of experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Solid C++ skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience developing plugins for DCC tools like Maya or Max&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience programming runtime logic for games such as handling animation / camera / state machines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Excellent Python scripting skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Programming with an eye for performance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working with of 3D content toolchains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong mathematical fundamentals, including linear algebra and numerical methods&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ways to stand out from the crowd:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with data-parallel and/or accelerated computing (CUDA, OpenCL)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Background with game engine development&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working with cloud-based services&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Familiarity with an existing game engine with an understanding of game engine and editor concepts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience writing UIs with a toolkit such as wxWidgets, WPF, QT, Slate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;NVIDIA is widely considered to be one of the technology world&#8217;s most desirable employers. We have some of the most forward-thinking and hardworking people in the world working for us. If you\'re creative and autonomous, we want to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://nvidia.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/NVIDIAExternalCareerSite/job/Canada-Toronto/Senior-Graphics-Tools-and-Pipeline-Engineer_JR1933619</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298516/nvidia-logo.jpg</logo><company>NVIDIA</company></item><item><title>Senior Verification Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are looking for a Senior Verification Engineer for Memory Controllers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;For two decades, we have pioneered visual computing, the art and science of computer graphics. With our invention of the GPU - the engine of modern visual computing - the field has grown to encompass video games, movie production, product design, medical diagnosis and scientific research. Today, we stand at the beginning of the next era, the AI computing era, ignited by a new computing model, GPU deep learning. This new model - where deep neural networks are trained to recognize patterns from massive amounts of data - has shown to be deeply effective at solving the most complex problems in everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a Verification Engineer at NVIDIA, you will verify the design and implementation of our state of the art memory subsystem for our mobile SoCs and GPUs. This position offers the opportunity to have real impact in a dynamic, technology-focused company impacting product lines ranging from consumer graphics to self-driving cars and the growing field of artificial intelligence. We have crafted a team of outstanding people stretching around the globe, whose mission is to push the frontiers of what is possible today and define the platform for the future of computing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;In this position, you will be responsible for verification of memory subsystem design, architecture, golden models and micro-architecture using advanced verification methodologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As an intermediate to senior member of our verification team, you\'ll understand the design &amp;amp; implementation, define the verification scope, develop the verification infrastructure (Testbenches, BFMs, Checkers, Monitors), execute test/coverage plans, and verify the correctness of the design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Collaborate with architects, designers, emulation and silicon verification teams to accomplish your tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What we need to see:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Bachelors, Master\'s or PhD Degree in a related field (or equivalent experience).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Minimum of 4 years of professional experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience developing TB\'s from scratch using SV and UVM methodology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Background in developing test bench environments for unit level verification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience in verification using random stimulus along with functional coverage and assertion-based verification methodologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Prior Design or Verification experience of dynamic memory controllers (ddr{2, 3, 4}, lpddr{2, &lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;3,4,5},Gddr{5,6},HBM{1,&lt;/span&gt; 2}) and/or high-speed interconnects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong C++ programming experience, scripting ability and experience with System Verilog is highly preferred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Exposure to design and verification tools (VCS or equivalent simulation tools, debug tools like Debussy, GDB).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong debugging, problem solving and analytical skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong communication and interpersonal skills are required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to work in a geographically diverse team environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Self motivated, ability to work independently and drive tasks to completion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;NVIDIA is widely considered to be one of the technology world&#8217;s most desirable employers. We have some of the most forward-thinking and hardworking people in the world working for us. Are you creative and autonomous? Do you love the challenge of crafting the highest performance &amp;amp; lowest power silicon possible? If so, we want to hear from you. Come, join our Memory Subsystem Design Team and help build the real-time, cost-effective computing platform driving our success in this exciting and quickly growing field.&#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://nvidia.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/NVIDIAExternalCareerSite/job/Canada-Toronto/Senior-Verification-Engineer_JR1939923</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298516/nvidia-logo.jpg</logo><company>NVIDIA</company></item><item><title>FINOPS ENGINEER</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Ottawa, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect identity management and data protection solutions at the heart of digital security. Business and governments rely on us to bring trust to the billons of digital interactions they have with people. Our technologies and services help banks exchange funds, people cross borders, energy become smarter and much more. More than 30,000 organizations already rely on us to verify the identities of people and things, grant access to digital services, analyze vast quantities of information and encrypt data to make the connected world more secure.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Purpose: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a new position to manage all financial aspects related to consumption of public cloud and SaaS services by CPL Cloud Services such as Safenet Trusted Authentication (STA), Data Protection on Demand (DPoD) and Software Monetization SW services. CPL currently spends several million dollars/year on consuming cloud services. The primary goal of the FinOps analyst is&amp;nbsp;to prioritize ongoing optimization of &amp;nbsp;cloud consumption costs and to make sure the engineering teams are getting maximum value for minimal spend. Without a strong FinOps operation, CPL may be incurring expenses for services it doesn\'t need, tools no one is using, or licenses that have been abandoned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Key areas of responsibility:&lt;p&gt;Continuously monitor &amp;amp; optimize the Cloud Services consumption expenses&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forecast consumption expenses for various Cloud Services and publish detailed consumption reports on a monthly/quarterly basis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maintain/update a list of Cloud Services vendors, understand licensing terms and be able to write Statement of Work (SOW) for any contracted services&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monitor Cloud Consumption costs using Cloud Cost optimization tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identify consumption trends and recommend best practices to reduce the costs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Work with finance for forecasting and budgeting Cloud Consumption expenses&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Present reports at the monthly Cloud Operations Governance meetings and quarterly executive staff review meetings for Cloud Operations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Key Relationships:&lt;p&gt;Work with financial controller for forecasting, budgeting and cost allocation to various departments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engage with procurement team for negotiations with vendors with regards to pricing, licensing and other terms. Work collaboratively with administrators raising the purchase requisitions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With guidance from the Cloud Operations Engineering Director, collaborate with engineering managers to evangelize, implement cost saving development practices and realize cost savings&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maintain close relationships with Technical Account Managers for the various Cloud Services (e.g. AWS, Google Cloud, Data Dog) in order to learn, leverage and implement the tools offered natively by these vendors for optimizing cloud consumption costs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interact with DIS Global Business Unit Cloud Operations Team to share and collaborate on best practices for Cloud Operations as it relates to Financial Operations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s degree in Computer Science with a strong back ground in Cloud Computing and Data Analytics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Industry experience: 7+ years in a Cloud Services company offering &#8220;As a Service&#8221; products along with 2+ years of experience in a FinOps role.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of the infrastructure services in Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Google Cloud (GCP)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with tools such as AWS Trusted Advisor/cost explorer, GCP cost report,&amp;nbsp; billing export and Big Query&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Microsoft Excel for financial forecasting, expense trending and budgeting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expertise in using Microsoft Power BI for Data Analytics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Forecasting and budgeting skills and exposure to basic finance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pinpoint deficiencies and identify solutions in the deployment of a solution.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Able to work along side teams and provide feedback from a&amp;nbsp;design/cost perspective.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal, written and presentation communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/ottawa/finops-engineer/1766/15339675296</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Toronto, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect solutions that support 85 million mainline and suburban passenger journeys, worldwide, every day. Our Rail Signalling and Communication systems are used on metro lines across major cities, and 72,000 kms of route, 52,000 trains per day in 16 countries are controlled by our Traffic Management Systems. Together We deployed the first-ever nationwide ticketing system which processes over 50 million ticketing transactions in 100 cities daily.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales provides world-leading Communications-Based Train Control (CBTC) and interlocking for mass rail transit applications globally. The Centre of Competence for Urban Rail Signalling is located right before you at mid-town Toronto. As the largest office in Canada, we house a department for every step of the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC)! This includes Software, Hardware, Systems Design, Verification &amp;amp; Validation, Operations, etc. The supporting corporate shared services teams in Finance, Human Resources and IT is also located at the office. Our office space was designed to provide a sustainable, healthy workplace that expresses TRSS&#8217;s brand while increasing collaboration. Features include Greenguard furniture, EnergyStar appliances, low-emitting adhesives, sealants, and sliding glass doors on internal offices provide daylight and views to the outside. Come join the big Transport family, here in Toronto!&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a Senior Software Developer to join the team!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a Research and Technology (R&amp;amp;T) Software Developer you are expected to have a diverse skill set in terms of software implementation of advanced algorithms, mechanical and electrical design, fusion algorithms, machine learning, big data, and data analysis of prototype experimental platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will work as part of the Software team within the Research and Technology department to develop, build, test and evaluate the next generation of driverless, autonomous urban rail solutions for the mass transit market. You will be challenged to implement technology &#8220;proof-of-concepts&#8221; on revenue rail systems and support new product introduction for the global market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contribute to the overall architecture design of the next generation automated train solution&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perform all phases as related to software development: model, compile, build, debug, simulation, testing, validation and documentation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyze and write software requirements using company standard methodology&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provides support to product team and other departments as required to help with engineering productization of new solutions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use and setup tools and systems for data collection and evaluation of large datasets. Experience with &#8216;big data&#8217; algorithms is an asset&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perform prototyping in simulation environments and with &#8220;proof of concept&#8221; platforms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To implement control algorithms, optimization algorithms, nonlinear Kalman Filters, and other algorithms in C++&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyze control system dynamics, parameters and models to generate reports&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provides support to product team and other departments as required to help productize new software solutions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keeps abreast of relevant technology developments as related to the R&amp;amp;T project&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comfortable in an Agile work methodology&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assists in providing leadership and motivation to staff&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate should possess a Bachelor\'s degree in Electrical or Computer Engineering or Computer Science&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum of 5 years coding in C/C++&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proficiency with a least one scripting/productivity language (Python preferred)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experienced Linux/Unix/POSIX system developer with knowledge in Linux kernel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledgeable of object oriented techniques, design patterns, multithreading, socket programming&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working knowledge of modern software engineering practices, methods &amp;amp; tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of communication protocols, file systems, networking, and security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong communication, organizational and problem-solving skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Capability of writing professional technical reports and documentations to support engineering development&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with real-time, safety critical systems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience developing to strict coding standards such as AUTOSAR C++, MISRA C++, SEI Cert C++ guidelines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Database experience, both design and usage. SQL language and relational databases&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cloud Computing experience: Kibana, Grafana, Postgres, Docker, and Jenkins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in one or more of the following: Deep Learning, Computer Vision and Machine Learning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Theoretical knowledge in the field of optimization, controls, computer vision, or signal processing is an asset&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of railway signaling techniques would be an asset&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/toronto/senior-software-developer/1766/15022029856</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>SOLUTION ARCHITECTS MANAGER- REMOTE</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Ottawa, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect identity management and data protection solutions at the heart of digital security. Business and governments rely on us to bring trust to the billons of digital interactions they have with people. Our technologies and services help banks exchange funds, people cross borders, energy become smarter and much more. More than 30,000 organizations already rely on us to verify the identities of people and things, grant access to digital services, analyze vast quantities of information and encrypt data to make the connected world more secure.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;b&gt;Solution Architects Manager&lt;/b&gt; in &lt;b&gt;Ottawa &lt;/b&gt;will lead the solution architects team. The team works on providing strategic direction of technology solutions to continue growing Identity &amp;amp; Access Management. The ideal candidate will be play a key role in identifying &amp;amp; capturing business requirements and converting those into technological design elements while ensuring alignment between customer expectations and current product capabilities. It will require leadership and communication skills to allow guiding a team of highly qualified individuals and rallying them around a common vision. This vision will also be communicated to the rest of Engineering and product teams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leading a team of highly skilled architects with proven deliverable track record.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Build &amp;amp; share a vision for how our IAM solution is going to evolve&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interact with business stakeholder to gather business requirements, produce technical specifications, designs architectures, POCs, and ultimately handover to scrum teams to deliver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lead the architecture group in defining priorities for PI planning and PI commitments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guide teams to develop high-quality code that is maintainable, structured, highly organized and self-documenting &amp;amp; usage of Code optimization techniques.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Required Skills and Experience: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5+ years of experience working with leading Identity &amp;amp; Access Management solutions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10 years of experience in designing and developing complex software solutions using .NET AND/OR java. Ability &amp;amp; willingness to learn the other if experienced in one and not the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5+ years of experience designing Micro services, distributed systems &amp;amp; web-based software utilizing a modern web framework (angular, react, etc.), noSQL databases (MongoDb, etc), RDBMS (SQLServer, MySQL, Postgres, etc).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;10+ years of experience interacting with web protocols, architectures, infrastructure, servers (IIS), proxies, load balancing and high availability, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5+ year working on any one cloud platform (GCP is preferred) with deep dive hands-on experience involving PaaS experience like ECS, EKS, GKE, RDS, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5+ years hands-on experience on defining the architecture blueprints along with techniques to validate the design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working knowledge with&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;UML and sequence diagrams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Test Driven Development, Agile/Scrum&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Standard Web Services (SOAP), REST, Json&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Core web architecture concepts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven track record of leading a team of highly skilled individuals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Must be able to communicate clearly and concisely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clear ability to define/articulate the NFRs (non-functional requirements) and translate service requirement to technical design elements&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with OOP Concepts, Design Patterns and Design Principles (SOLID etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with Any NoSQL DB, ElasticSearch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of performance engineering and web security best practices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of implementing event driven architecture solution using Messaging platforms like RabbitMQ, SQS/SNS, Kafka, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good understanding of Front End Technologies Angular 6+, JavaScript, TypeScript.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience working with complex, high-transactional products is highly desirable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hands-on experience with transformation of a monolith to microservices architecture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with SAFe Agile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/ottawa/solution-architects-manager-remote/1766/9272709920</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>FULL STACK DEVELOPER</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Ottawa, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect identity management and data protection solutions at the heart of digital security. Business and governments rely on us to bring trust to the billons of digital interactions they have with people. Our technologies and services help banks exchange funds, people cross borders, energy become smarter and much more. More than 30,000 organizations already rely on us to verify the identities of people and things, grant access to digital services, analyze vast quantities of information and encrypt data to make the connected world more secure.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Full-stack Software Engineer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Purpose:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a seasoned full-stack Software Engineer, for the Cloud Services Platform team, you will work across a variety of disciplines to investigate, prototype, develop, test, and deliver, software across the full technology stack. This includes UI development to building backend services in a micro-service based, secure, native cloud enterprise deployment.&amp;nbsp; You will be involved in understanding requirements, translating them into working enterprise level architecture, as well as, implementing and supporting the solution.&amp;nbsp; You will work closely with a cross-matrixed team, in a scaled agile environment.&amp;nbsp; You will be involved in the entire software development lifecycle, including automation and DevOps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be part of a team required to design, implement, test, and support features with the following mind-set: end-user experience, maintainability, scalability, performance, cost, resilience CI-CD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Building cloud native software, using various platform-as-a-service (PaaS), Software-as-a-Service (SaaS), Infrastructure-as-a-Service (IaaS) technologies and related tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Applying coding/implementation best practices to produce elegant, high quality, resilient, maintainable, and reusable code&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implementing and following security best practices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proactively participating in creating unit test cases, &amp;nbsp;along with integration &amp;amp; performance testing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Enhancing, and maturing, our existing automation test suite and tooling&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participating in issue investigation, and deployment of applications, and testing/integration in various deployed environments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Managing the source code repository for projects in Git&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Documenting, managing, and maintaining internal knowledge and processes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Remaining up-to-date on industry trends, and applying the latest evolving technologies, and frameworks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collaborate with other developers, to share knowledge, and improve overall product/solution. Responsibilities include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Following agile methodology. This includes active participation in sprint planning and retrospective meetings, creation of user stories, as well as, corresponding tasks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interacting with UX team to implement and verify user experience concepts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Providing feedback to documentation team to develop, improve, and review Customer centric feature documentation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interfacing with geographically distributed teams in Austin, Ottawa, Noida, and other locations on a regular basis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s degree in Computer Science or Computer Engineering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong programming skills in any of these languages: Java, Python, Golang, Linux scripting languages, along with frameworks, such as Apache, Springboot, Node.js, J2EE&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 2 years&#8217; experience delivering software in an Agile/SAFe/Scrum development environment: designing and implementing the feature; design testing a solution; developing automated functional tests and unit tests; continuous integration/delivery; drafting the information needed in developer and customer documentation; and addressing bugs and improvements. As such, working knowledge of JIRA, GIT, build and deployment systems is required.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience developing code using IDE&#8217;s such as Intellij or Visual studio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate experience in building complex enterprise micro-service cloud based applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate strong troubleshooting skills in a cloud environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in developing web based client-server applications using a combination of Java, Golang, or Python, as well as, web application server setup/configuration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in web services, web standards; REST, HTML/CSS/JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficient understanding of web markup, protocol and client-side scripting technologies in general, including HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, AJAX, JSON, JQuery, REST API, Angular, React, Node.js&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop and design RESTful services and APIs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong backend development skills integrating with Web based front-end and SQL/non-SQL databases such as MySQL, Postgres,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience in the implementation of highly secure web-based cloud applications using the latest industry standards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity working with continuous integration tools such as: Gitlab, Teamcity, Concourse, Terraform, and CI/CD pipeline setup working experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In-depth experience working with Linux and Linux based applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with unit test development, such as junit, and test automation, using frameworks, such as Selenium, Protractor, or Playwright&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Agile/SAFe development methodology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to effectively work in a cross matrixed team environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated, enthusiastic, with an extreme desire for continual learning, and the ability to work under minimal guidance with demonstrated analytical and problem solving skills in order to deliver features on time in a fast paced team environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong collaboration and communication skills which will be fundamental to your, and the overall teams success, of the projects you work on&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A endless passion for continually learning which provide you the building blocks to develop industry leading secure cloud native applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stay current and provide insight on cutting edge software approaches, architectures, and vendors&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure that non-functional requirements such as security, performance, maintainability, scalability, usability, and reliability are being considered when architecting solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working experience/knowledge with industry leading cloud providers GCP or AWS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of code analysis tools such as IDE Tools, Security and Open source scanning tools, such as Blackduck, logging and monitoring tools (i.e. datadog)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with security and identity management (access management, authentication, authorization identity providers), as well as, monitoring framework&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of cryptographic concepts (i.e. Encryption concepts and technologies), and an understanding of encryption and cryptographic key management with experience using them to protect sensitive data in database, applications, storage systems, virtualized platforms and cloud environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with FIPS (Federal Information Processing Standards), and other NIST requirements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of CI/CD build and deployment pipelines and DevOps common industry practices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with automated deployment and associated technologies: terraforms, helm, yaml, ansible&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deployment and management of docker containers deployed in a kubernetes environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Networking and cloud infrastructure knowledge and above average application troubleshooting experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience providing L3 pager support for large complex enterprise applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/ottawa/full-stack-developer/1766/13577988912</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>IOS MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPER</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Ottawa, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect identity management and data protection solutions at the heart of digital security. Business and governments rely on us to bring trust to the billons of digital interactions they have with people. Our technologies and services help banks exchange funds, people cross borders, energy become smarter and much more. More than 30,000 organizations already rely on us to verify the identities of people and things, grant access to digital services, analyze vast quantities of information and encrypt data to make the connected world more secure.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a member of a collaborative development team, the mobile software engineer will be instrumental in the identification and implementation of a Cloud Protection Licensing (CPL) wide mobile software that covers the product portfolio. The primary objective is to design, develop, test and deliver high-quality mobile products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;iOS Mobile application Developer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, located in &lt;b&gt;Ottawa&lt;/b&gt;, will work closely with product owners, system architects, software engineers, UX/UI designers, security teams, technical writers, customer support team, and 3rd parties as necessary to ensure timely delivery of quality products and to provide support throughout the lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Responsible for developing and testing iOS projects. This includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Develop /follow mobile application coding standards to facilitate code maintenance and enhancement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Continuously improve code quality through writing unit tests, automation and performing code reviews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design, implement and execute the automation testing to improve the test execution efficiency for the SDK and App to deliver user perceived quality of the product&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Integrate with our backend services to make sure we are delivering a great mobile user experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interface closely with product managers, user experience, operations and customers to understand end user requirements and convert them into a pragmatic and effective technical solution&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participate in brainstorming sessions and contribute innovative and original ideas to our technology, algorithms and product&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Resolve issues found during engineering test and QA in a timely manner, taking risk into account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coordinate with customer support teams to diagnose product issues and successfully deliver results within a schedule&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consistent use of group tools such as Jira, Confluence, Git/GitHub for tracking of defects and management of code.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Independently manage time and prioritize tasks to achieve results within cost and schedule constraints&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2+ years&#8217; development and testing experience in mobile app/SDK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;BS in Computer Science or equivalent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Must have at least 2 years+ hands on experience&lt;/span&gt; and expertise in building iOS/iPad apps using Swift and Objective-C&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Must have prior experience in using SwiftUI for iOS/iPad app development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Must have prior experience in using iOS software development tools such XCode to develop, test, debug, and deploy quality software&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Proven ability to use tools&lt;/span&gt; such as git/GitHUB and JIRA/Confluence in the software development process&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prior experience in the use of API design such as REST&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Previous experience&lt;/span&gt; with CI/CD pipeline to build, test and deploy mobile apps/SDKs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Proven ability to create&lt;/span&gt; test strategy and UI automation testing for mobile apps/SDKs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prior experience&lt;/span&gt; with Agile development practices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent analytical, communication and presentation skills &#8211; verbal and written&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Highly motivated and self-driven&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proven ability to work independently on assigned tasks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Occasional flexibility to work outside of normal business hours to collaborate with teams in different time zones&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Referrable development experience with WatchOS and macOS apps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prior experience in&lt;/span&gt; Android using Java/Kotlin is an asset&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prior experience in&lt;/span&gt; multi-site / multi-cultural team management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding of enterprise application development, software as a service and enterprise security technologies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Able to think out of the box to offer innovative solutions to technical problems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Able to adapt communication style to match the needs of the audience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prior&lt;/span&gt; Scaled Agile Framework (SAFe) environment experience is a plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/ottawa/ios-mobile-application-developer/1766/12946217584</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>SOFTWARE ARCHITECT - WAYSIDE</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Toronto, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect solutions that support 85 million mainline and suburban passenger journeys, worldwide, every day. Our Rail Signalling and Communication systems are used on metro lines across major cities, and 72,000 kms of route, 52,000 trains per day in 16 countries are controlled by our Traffic Management Systems. Together We deployed the first-ever nationwide ticketing system which processes over 50 million ticketing transactions in 100 cities daily.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales provides world-leading Communications-Based Train Control (CBTC) and interlocking for mass rail transit applications globally. The Centre of Competence for Urban Rail Signalling is located right before you at mid-town Toronto. As the largest office in Canada, we house a department for every step of the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC)! This includes Software, Hardware, Systems Design, Verification &amp;amp; Validation, Operations, etc. The supporting corporate shared services teams in Finance, Human Resources and IT is also located at the office. Our office space was designed to provide a sustainable, healthy workplace that expresses TRSS&#8217;s brand while increasing collaboration. Features include Greenguard furniture, EnergyStar appliances, low-emitting adhesives, sealants, and sliding glass doors on internal offices provide daylight and views to the outside. Come join the big Transport family, here in Toronto!&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thales Canada Transport Solutions is looking for a Software Architect for our train control systems and more precisely for Wayside Software. The successful candidate will be responsible for the software architecture and its consistency with the solution/system architecture, the Architect coordinates with the Solution Architect and PDA in order to make sure that the top down refinement of the solution is consistent with the software strategy and constraints including COTS &amp;amp; OSS selection and components reuse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensures that software architecture stability is maintained across lifecycle phases from Bid to Delivery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Directs and coordinates software architecture studies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approves the technical, technological, and methodological choices taken in respect of the selected software architecture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guarantees adherence to in-scope standards, reuse policy and product development plans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identifies modelling, simulation and prototyping opportunities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Co-ordinates product definition and assessment of trade-offs between aspects of cost, customer requirements and technological possibilities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prepares the Design &amp;amp; Justification Files&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provides knowledge on state-of-the-art software architecture, taking into account the impact of future developments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monitors technological developments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Respects the established deadlines, costs and performances for the different projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mandatory Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;University degree in Computer or Software Engineering&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum of 7 years of experience with embedded critical software development&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fluent oral and written communication skills in English&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expert knowledge of modern software engineering practices, methods and tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good programming expertise (C, Ada, Assembly, Python, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of railway signaling techniques an asset&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In-depth knowledge of SELTRAC product&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Development experience in C&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expert knowledge of SELTRAC signaling system and software architecture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/toronto/software-architect-wayside/1766/9272756592</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>SENIOR MANAGER, CHIEF SOFTWARE ARCHITECT</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Toronto, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect solutions that support 85 million mainline and suburban passenger journeys, worldwide, every day. Our Rail Signalling and Communication systems are used on metro lines across major cities, and 72,000 kms of route, 52,000 trains per day in 16 countries are controlled by our Traffic Management Systems. Together We deployed the first-ever nationwide ticketing system which processes over 50 million ticketing transactions in 100 cities daily.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales provides world-leading Communications-Based Train Control (CBTC) and interlocking for mass rail transit applications globally. The Centre of Competence for Urban Rail Signalling is located right before you at mid-town Toronto. As the largest office in Canada, we house a department for every step of the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC)! This includes Software, Hardware, Systems Design, Verification &amp;amp; Validation, Operations, etc. The supporting corporate shared services teams in Finance, Human Resources and IT is also located at the office. Our office space was designed to provide a sustainable, healthy workplace that expresses TRSS&#8217;s brand while increasing collaboration. Features include Greenguard furniture, EnergyStar appliances, low-emitting adhesives, sealants, and sliding glass doors on internal offices provide daylight and views to the outside. Come join the big Transport family, here in Toronto!&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Chief Software Architect Manager&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to lead the team of Chief Software Architects and foster the community of the Software Architects. The successful candidate will be responsible for the Design and Architecture of the software developed at Thales Canada Transportation Solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will have the Chief Software Architects of each subsystem (wayside, onboard, supervision) as direct reports&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are responsible for this team in terms of hiring, training, mentoring, objective setting and performance evaluation, support in problem solving, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the &lt;span&gt;Chief Software Architect Manager&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;you will lead and foster the community of the Software Architects: detecting the talent, developing the skills, developing knowledge sharing, detecting and developing the new ideas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are ultimately responsible for the Design and Architecture of the software which is developed at TCTS (Thales Canada Transportation Solutions): Definition of the design drivers, architecture patterns; conduct and supervise the architecture trade-off; Definition of the software roadmap and product policy; Providing guidance and review of the developments, foster co-engineering with the other disciplines; Promoting cost effective design while contributing to cost estimates and bid estimates; Ensuring compliance to the standards; Instrumental in the definition and implementation of the process, practices and tools; Lastly staying in tune with Thales Group technical strategy and finding opportunities for collaboration with other Thales business units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Staying abreast of current software architecture trends and working with the software architect community to determine their applicability to TCTS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;University degree in Computer Science, Engineering, or closely related field&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over 15 years of relevant working experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expertise with Software Architecture; Software development process and Development of mission-critical and/or safety critical software and embedded software for complex systems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in the railway domain is a plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leading and developing a community&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leading transformation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/toronto/senior-manager-chief-software-architect/1766/11655390624</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>Finance Manager</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Canvass AI, A Leader in Industrial AI, Seeks Finance Manager&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI is disrupting the industrial sector with its leading AI platform by enabling operators to scale the use of machine learning in their day-to-day production to gain immediate business benefits. Funded by Alphabet&#8217;s Gradient Ventures and Yamaha Motor Ventures, Canvass is democratizing access to AI by requiring little or no data science knowledge to use it. Global companies are employing Canvass AI today to achieve higher quality, lower cost, less disruption while reducing waste and emissions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a Finance Manager you will be responsible for the financial operations of Canvass. Producing financial reports and developing strategies based on financial research. Guiding senior executives in making sound business decisions in the long and short term. This position reports to the CEO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location: Toronto, Ontario or remote&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul role="list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monitor the day-to-day financial operations within the company (payroll, invoicing, and other transactions)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prepare monthly and quarterly management reporting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide insightful information and expectations to senior leadership to aid in long-term and short-term decision-making&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support project analysis, validation of plans and product pricing, and ad-hoc requests&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage the company\'s financial accounting, HR platform, monitoring, and reporting systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contract and oversee outside services for tax preparation, accounting, payroll, auditing, banking, investments, recruiting, SR&amp;amp;ED claims, and other financial and HR needs as necessary&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Track the company&#8217;s financial status and operating performance to identify areas for potential improvement&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Present financial reports to board members, stakeholders, executives, and clients in formal meetings&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure compliance with accounting policies and regulatory requirements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul role="list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor\'s degree in Finance or Accounting; CPA a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-3 years of combined experience in accounting, financial analysis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with software scale-ups is preferred&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to synthesize data into actionable information&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to work and effectively communicate with senior-level business partners&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent business judgment, analytical, and decision-making skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of financial reporting and data mining tools &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong demonstrated use of Excel, Word, and PowerPoint&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Solid communication skills, both written and verbal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Deep understanding of business principles and practices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Integrity, honesty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Generous time off, including vacation and personal days personal days to help rejuvenate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Extended learning via Coursera account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Flexible work policy, with options to work remotely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Stock options as part of your compensation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Attend conferences and training courses to extend your knowledge and skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Latest technology and tools to excel at your role&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why join Canvass?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI is changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and it&#8217;s getting noticed everywhere. &amp;nbsp;We&#8217;ve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Start-ups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange as a Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&#8217;s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in. &amp;nbsp;From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. &amp;nbsp;We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions. &amp;nbsp;We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/finance-manager</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298882/canvass-logo-rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Canvass Analytics Inc.</company></item><item><title>Senior Software Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI is disrupting the industrial sector with its cutting-edge AI platform, by transforming industrial engineers into data and digital engineers. Backed by some of the world&#8217;s largest companies like Google&#8217;s Gradient Ventures, Canvass is democratizing the use of AI in day to day operations so industrial companies can build AI/ML models at scale and deploy them in production to gain business benefits in real time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Things you should know about our tech: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; We use a microservices architecture built predominantly with Python &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Our single-page web application is built with React and we use Django for our RESTful API layer &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; We use Kubernetes to manage our cloud deployments in Azure &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; We&#8217;ve built a data pipeline with Kafka and use Kubeflow to orchestrate our machine learning pipeline &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; We use CircleCI to continuously integrate and deploy code changes &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we&#8217;re looking for: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re looking for candidates with: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; experience building web applications with Python, bonus points for experience with a RESTful API framework &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; experience using React (or other JavaScript frameworks) to build complex web applications &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; An understanding of microservice architecture and distributed system design &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Proven track record of delivering well-designed and tested software &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Solid understanding of relational and non-relational databases and best practices &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, we&#8217;re looking for a senior developer that exemplify these qualities: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;Activation &amp;amp; Engagement&lt;/strong&gt; Our developers are critical to the progress of our application and our business. We expect our developers to maintain focus on the business impact of their changes and advocate for work that will drive outcomes instead of just output. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;Teamwork &amp;amp; Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt; Our teams are small and extremely collaborative. Developers work very closely with a small number of other developers, a designer, and a product manager to meaningfully impact the business every week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;Excellence &amp;amp; Craft &lt;/strong&gt;Software development is more than checking features off a list of requirements. We need our developers to build systems that are accessible to new teammates and extensible so that they can evolve with our business. We want our developers to take pride in what they build. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;Communication &amp;amp; Leadership &lt;/strong&gt;A developer can have a large impact by helping to grow the abilities and understanding of their teammates. We&#8217;re looking for people who can deliver learning sessions to introduce their technical teammates to new concepts and who can explain and contextualize their work to teammates outside of engineering. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;You want to join a company that&#8217;s at the forefront of leading edge technology and you want to be the person that takes us there and captures massive market share. You want to be part of an ambitious, successful team that is rapidly scaling up, that gives you room to grow and build your career as the company grows. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Your Benefits &lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; An incredible team with Inclusive culture, open to ideas &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; You build the future of the planet. An opportunity to work in a leading edge AI company that is making the planet safer and greener for the future. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Generous time off, including vacation and personal days to help rejuvenate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Flexible office policy, with option to work remotely &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Equity Plan &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass &lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in. From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. &amp;nbsp;We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions. We have an inclusive culture and we are driven by the passion to make an impact to the future of the industrial sector which in turn impacts the climate sustainability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/senior-software-engineer</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298882/canvass-logo-rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Canvass Analytics Inc.</company></item><item><title>Team Lead, DevOps/Cloud</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500 industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. Canvass Analytics&#8217; customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things you should know about our product &amp;amp; teams:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Our platform is fully hosted in Azure and is primarily built using Kubernetes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;We use CircleCI to continuously integrate and deploy changes using infrastructure-as-Code (IaC)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Our microservices architecture and tooling are developed in Python&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;We&#8217;ve built data pipelines with Kafka and use Kubeflow to orchestrate our machine learning jobs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What we&#8217;re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;We&#8217;re looking for candidates with:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Track record of building and managing secure, scalable, IaC-based infrastructure in Azure, AWS, or GCP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;A passion for observability and automation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Demonstrated leadership and mentoring skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Experience creating and managing Kubernetes clusters, using tools such as Helm and Terraform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Strong networking and Linux knowledge, including knowing what to look for when things go wrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;An understanding of microservice architecture and distributed system design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Proficiency with Python&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;This is a senior role, requiring at least 8 years professional experience in related technical roles (e.g. DevOps, system administration, software development, testing)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re looking for a hands-on leader to manage and scale our growing cloud infrastructure and the team that supports it. A typical week will include a healthy mix of design, technical implementation, proactive production support and team management &#8211; perfect for someone who wants to stay close to the technology but still wants to flex their leadership skills. Reporting to the head of Engineering, you\'ll have full ownership of the resources that power our industrial AI platform as well as the DevOps tooling that makes it easy for development teams to bring their code into production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your team&#8217;s responsibilities will include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;High Availability - maximizing our uptime through design, automation and process&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Scalability &#8211; designing flexible infrastructure to meet the demands of high-burst, resource-intensive machine learning workloads&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Security &#8211; continuously improving our security and putting the technology in place to support SOC2 certification&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Growth &#8211; starting as a team of two, help us grow by providing mentorship, expanding the team&#8217;s capabilities and bringing new team members on board as our customer base expands&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8205;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who you are:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, we&#8217;re looking for engineers that exemplify these qualities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Activation &amp;amp; Engagement Our engineers are critical to the progress of our application and our business. We expect our engineers to maintain focus on the business impact of their changes and advocate for work that will drive outcomes instead of just output.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Teamwork &amp;amp; Collaboration Our teams are small and extremely collaborative. You will work very closely with Product Development and Customer Success to meaningfully impact the business every week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Excellence &amp;amp; Craft Operations is more than just keeping the lights on 24/7. We need to build secure, scalable systems that are also easy to understand and easy to extend so that they can evolve with our business. We want our engineers to take pride in what they build.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Communication &amp;amp; Leadership We&#8217;re looking for people who can teach and introduce their teammates to new concepts, and who can explain and contextualize their work to colleagues outside of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s in it for you:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You want to join a company that&#8217;s at the forefront of leading-edge technology and you want to be the person that takes us there and captures massive market share. You want to be part of an ambitious, successful team that is rapidly scaling up, that gives you room to grow and recognition. You will reap the rewards of your efforts with great incentive targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Inclusive culture, open to ideas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Generous time off, including vacation and personal days to help rejuvenate &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Top technology and tools to excel at your role &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and it&#8217;s getting noticed everywhere.&amp;nbsp; We&#8217;ve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by Google&#8217;sGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&amp;nbsp;From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&amp;nbsp;We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you don&#8217;t have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/team-lead-devops-cloud</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298882/canvass-logo-rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Canvass Analytics Inc.</company></item><item><title>Cloud Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. CanvassAnalytics&#8217; customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things you should know about our product &amp;amp;teams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Our infrastructure is based on Kubernetes and various Azure cloud technologies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We use CircleCI to continuously integrate and deploy code changes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Deployment to production is git-based and happens on a regular basis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We use a micro services architecture built predominantly withPython&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We&#8217;ve built data pipelines with Kafka and use Kube flow to orchestrate our machine learning pipeline&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What we&#8217;re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re looking for candidates with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; A passion for building secure and scalable cloud infrastructure inAzure, AWS or GCP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience creating and managing Kubernetes clusters, using tools such as Helm and Terraform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Strong networking and Linux knowledge, including knowing what to look for when things go wrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Proven track record of proactive system management and monitoring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; An understanding of micro service architecture and distributed system design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Comfortable working with Python and Javascript&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Bonus points for managing Kafka and/or Spark clusters&#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&#8203;Who you are:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, we&#8217;re looking for engineers&amp;nbsp;that exemplify these qualities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Activation &amp;amp; Engagement&amp;nbsp;Our engineers are critical to the progress of our application and our business. We expect our engineers to maintain focus on the business impact of their changes and advocate for work that will drive outcomes instead of just output.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Teamwork &amp;amp; Collaboration&amp;nbsp;Our teams are small and extremely collaborative. You will work very closely with DevOps, ProductDevelopment and Customer Success to meaningfully impact the business every week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Excellence &amp;amp; Craft&amp;nbsp;Cloud infrastructure is more than just keeping the lights on 24/7. We need to build secure, scalable systems that are also easy to understand and easy to extend so that they can evolve with our business. We want our engineers to take pride in what they build.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Communication &amp;amp; Leadership&amp;nbsp;An engineer can have a large impact by helping to grow the abilities and understanding of their teammates.We&#8217;re looking for people who can deliver learning sessions to introduce their technical teammates to new concepts and who can explain and contextualize their work to teammates outside of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Awesome team and culture (every day)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Generous time off, including vacation and personal days&amp;nbsp; to help rejuvenate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Top technology and tools to excel at your role&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and it&#8217;s getting noticed everywhere.&amp;nbsp; We&#8217;ve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by Google&#8217;sGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&amp;nbsp; From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes.&amp;nbsp; We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&amp;nbsp; We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you don&#8217;t have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/cloud-engineer</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298882/canvass-logo-rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Canvass Analytics Inc.</company></item><item><title>Machine Learning Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500 industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. CanvassAnalytics&#8217; customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Things you should know about our product &amp;amp; teams&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We don&#8217;t build machine learning pipelines to solve specific problems: we create pipelines that are able to solve classes of industrial data problems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We use Keras, SciKit-Learn,XGBoost, SHAP and regularly research and add new libraries to our stack&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Our pipelines and micro services are developed predominantly with Python&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We use Kubeflow to build flexible ML pipelines and Kafka for data pipelines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; We use CircleCI to continuously test, integrate and deploy code changes, including ML&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What we&#8217;re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re looking for candidates with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Experience applying machine learning and deep learning algorithms to time-series problems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Strong knowledge of probability and statistics, plus a passion for working with data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The ability to implement feature engineering and data transformations at scale&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Solid Python development skills, including experience with NumPy, Pandas and one or more ML libraries&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; An understanding of micro service architecture and containerization&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; A proven track record of delivering well-designed and tested software&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&#8203;Who you are:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, we&#8217;re looking for engineers&amp;nbsp;that exemplify these qualities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Activation &amp;amp; Engagement&amp;nbsp;Our engineers are critical to the progress of our application and our business. We expect our engineers to maintain focus on the business impact of their changes and advocate for work that will drive outcomes instead of just output.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Teamwork &amp;amp; Collaboration&amp;nbsp;Our teams are small and extremely collaborative. You will work very closely with DevOps, ProductDevelopment and Customer Success to meaningfully impact the business every week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Excellence &amp;amp; Craft&amp;nbsp;Cloud infrastructure is more than just keeping the lights on 24/7. We need to build secure, scalable systems that are also easy to understand and easy to extend so that they can evolve with our business. We want our engineers to take pride in what they build.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Communication &amp;amp; Leadership&amp;nbsp;An engineer can have a large impact by helping to grow the abilities and understanding of their teammates.We&#8217;re looking for people who can deliver learning sessions to introduce their technical teammates to new concepts and who can explain and contextualize their work to teammates outside of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Awesome team and culture (every day)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Generous time off, including vacation and personal days&amp;nbsp; to help rejuvenate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Top technology and tools to excel at your role&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and it&#8217;s getting noticed everywhere.&amp;nbsp; We&#8217;ve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by Google&#8217;sGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&amp;nbsp;From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&amp;nbsp;We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you don&#8217;t have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/machine-learning-engineer</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298882/canvass-logo-rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Canvass Analytics Inc.</company></item><item><title>Account Executive</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500 industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. Canvass Analytics&#8217; customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who We Need&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is seeking an Account Executive to join our sales team, a true hunter who wants to join us in North America at this pivotal point in our growth. You will develop your territory, build out the sales strategy and satisfy your drive to close the deal. You are a pioneer in an industry calling out for disruption, transforming the way operational decisions in the Industrial sector are made using AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who You Are&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are ready to take the next step in your career, understand the Industrial market and come with a roster of contacts who you are prepared to call. You have a proven track record of building relationships, from C-suite to Operations Managers. Empowering prospects and clients with data-driven insights to help them save money, accelerate competitive advantage and stay ahead is what motivates you. You are happiest on the road pursuing your targets and gaining new ground in this race to become an industry leader in industrial AI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What You Bring&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;You have an Engineering degree and the logical, technical approach that comes with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Industry experience. You have 5 years selling into industrial companies, perhaps working for larger companies and moving into progressively more nimble ones. You get an adrenaline rush every time you close the deal. Your achievements go beyond quotas, extending into highly satisfied clients who trust your expertise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Motivation and drive. You get a thrill from pursuing the close which also means you are calm under pressure and can make sound decisions quickly. The confidence in our product and our company just makes it easier for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Sales methodology and innovation. You believe in following a process because it works and changing it up when it doesn&#8217;t. You want to contribute to building tactics and refining our processes for repeatable success.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Communication. You have outstanding presentation skills. Your consulting approach in meetings gains the trust of those listening to you. Your written and verbal one-on-one communication skills - including the ability to listen and provide a real solution to a client&#8217;s unique issues - are why you consistently exceed quota.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Passion. You want to be in sales - this is where your career path starts and ends. You are genuinely interested in new ideas and new technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Awesome team and culture (every day)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Generous time off, including vacation and personal days &amp;nbsp;to help rejuvenate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Top technology and tools to excel at your role&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and it&#8217;s getting noticed everywhere.&amp;nbsp; We&#8217;ve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by Google&#8217;sGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&amp;nbsp; From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes.&amp;nbsp; We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&amp;nbsp; We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you don&#8217;t have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/account-executive</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298882/canvass-logo-rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Canvass Analytics Inc.</company></item><item><title>Test Automation Developer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass Analytics, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered analytics platform transforms plant operations, giving them predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering Fortune 1,500 industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. Canvass Analytics&#8217; customers include leading energy, manufacturing, food and ag, oil and gas, and metals and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Things you should know about our product &amp;amp; teams&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &#8226;We use a microservices architecture built predominantly with Python&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Our single-page web application is built with React&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;We use Kubernetes to manage our cloud deployments in Azure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;We&#8217;ve built data pipelines with Kafka and use Kubeflow to orchestrate our machine learning pipeline&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;We use CircleCI to continuously integrate, test and deploy code changes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What we&#8217;re looking for:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;We&#8217;re looking for candidates with:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Passionate about creating automated tests to ensure that an application works both before, during and post-deployment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Interested in applying their test automation knowledge to a platform offering multiple test challenges: IoT data ingestion, data pipelines, machine learning pipelines and of course an SPA front end&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Familiar with the testing tools we already use (pytest, jest, cypress) and ready to add new ones into the mix&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Solid Python and Javascript programming skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;An understanding of RESTful APIs and microservice architecture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who you are:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, we&#8217;re looking for developers that exemplify these qualities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Activation &amp;amp; Engagement Our developers are critical to the progress of our application and our business. We expect our developers to maintain focus on the business impact of their changes and advocate for work that will drive outcomes instead of just output.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Teamwork &amp;amp; Collaboration Our teams are small and extremely collaborative. Developers work very closely with a small number of other developers, a designer, and a product manager to meaningfully impact the business every week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Excellence &amp;amp; Craft Software development is more than checking features off a list of requirements. We need our developers to build systems that are accessible to new teammates and extensible so that they can evolve with our business. We want our developers to take pride in what they build.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Communication &amp;amp; Leadership A developer can have a large impact by helping to grow the abilities and understanding of their teammates. We&#8217;re looking for people who can deliver learning sessions to introduce their technical teammates to new concepts and who can explain and contextualize their work to teammates outside of engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Inclusive culture, open to ideas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Generous time off, including vacation and personal days to help rejuvenate &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Top technology and tools to excel at your role &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8226;Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for theIndustrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and it&#8217;s getting noticed everywhere.&amp;nbsp; We&#8217;ve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange asa Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by Google&#8217;sGradient Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in.&amp;nbsp;From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions.&amp;nbsp;We have an inclusive culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Apply Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think this job is meant for you but worried you don&#8217;t have it all?If you feel you meet 70% of the qualifications listed and you are an innovative team player, express your interest here and we promise to consider your full profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also follow us on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CanvassAI" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/canvassai" target="_blank"&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to learn more about us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics welcomes and encourages applications from people with disabilities. Accommodations are available on request for candidates taking part in all aspects of the selection process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/test-automation-developer</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298882/canvass-logo-rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Canvass Analytics Inc.</company></item><item><title>Product Marketing - Industry Lead</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A Leader in Automating Intelligent Industrial Operations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI is disrupting the industrial sector with its cutting-edge AI platform, by transforming industrial engineers into data and digital engineers. Backed by some of the world&#8217;s largest companies like Google&#8217;s Gradient Ventures, Canvass is democratizing the use of AI in day to day operations so industrial companies can build AI/ML models at scale and deploy them in production to gain business benefits in real time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the VP of Marketing, you live and breathe product marketing and know the immense value this strategic function brings to an organization. Through your proven experience in B2B -SaaS product marketing, you have learned how to keep your eye on the big picture and execute on what needs to get done to move the needle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for an experienced, collaborative, and driven Product Marketing Industry Lead, who will take Canvass AI to new heights and drive rapid growth across existing and new markets. You will be responsible for core go-to-market activism and ongoing product success - defining product positioning through a deep understanding of the market, buyers, and key competitors. You will synthesize information and serve as an internal and external evangelist and influencer to ensure the sales, marketing, and customer success are equipped with the right tools, knowledge, and information to properly position Canvass AI to win in the market. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Conceptualize, build and analyze various marketing plans, strategies and campaigns to power the growth of Canvass AI&#8217;s brand and product.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Develop and launch campaigns to support our GTM (go to market) initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Develop targeted and meaningful content, product positioning and messaging that differentiates Canvass AI capabilities across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Communicate the value proposition of Canvass AI&#8217;s platform and capabilities to sales enablement and develop assets and sales tools that support the sales cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Participate in the launch of new product releases and manage the cross-functional implementation of industry-agnostic plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Work closely with our Product Management and Go-To-Market teams to develop enablement content, product demos, sales tools and strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Help drive market intelligence through in-depth industry and competitive analysis, while consistently devising programs to outpace the competition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Develop the strategy and manage the marketing programs that drive demand within the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Work with our broader marketing team to develop thought leadership and increase awareness of Canvass AI for expert data scientist user personas, influencers, and decision makers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Create and maintain a crystal clear and highly compelling product messaging matrix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Create and shape customer personas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Track competitive marketing landscape against category.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Empower sales with competitive intelligence, and create and maintain competitor talking tracks, battle cards, cheat sheets, FAQs, and training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; SaaS product marketing experience is a must.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 8-10 years of work experience in B2B Product Marketing and/or Product Management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Deep understanding of machine learning and analytic applications, especially in production / operational environments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Demonstrated success in product launches and end-to-end execution of supporting marketing strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Excellent communication skills a must; written and oral, including presentation and product demonstration experience to large and diverse audiences. You have a knack for developing compelling, differentiated, and memorable product narratives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Analyst relations experience with firms such as Forrester and Gartner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; You enjoy collaborating with passionate cross-functional teams (e.g., sales, product management, marketing, customer success).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Roll up your sleeve get stuff done attitude with high growth start-up experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Bachelor&#8217;s degree in a related field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Awesome team and culture (every day)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Generous time off, including vacation and personal days personal days to help rejuvenate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Top technology and tools to excel at your role&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Free team lunches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for the Industrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and it&#8217;s getting noticed everywhere. &amp;nbsp;We&#8217;ve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange as a Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by Google&#8217;s Gradient Ventures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in. &amp;nbsp;From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. &amp;nbsp;We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions. &amp;nbsp;We have an inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/product-marketing-industry-lead</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298882/canvass-logo-rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Canvass Analytics Inc.</company></item><item><title>Sales Account Executive</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="project-rich-text w-richtext"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Canvass AI - Industrial AI Built for Industrial Engineers &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Canvass, we are disrupting the way industrial operational data is being used to make critical business decisions. Our disruptive, leading edge AI-powered platform, transforms plant operations, giving &amp;nbsp;predictive insights that enable autonomous operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI software platform is empowering industrial companies to transform industrial engineers into digital engineers who are driving data driven decisions in day to day operations. Canvass customers include leading energy, manufacturing, and mining companies around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re an agile scale-up with the operational intelligence of a global business. As we accelerate rapidly, we are constantly looking for driven and ambitious innovators to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You&#8217;ll Do &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass AI is seeking an Account Executive, a true hunter who wants to join our team and expand the business globally. This is an individual contributor position, newly added for business expansion. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul role="list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will be identifying, negotiating and closing big deals in industrial market. &amp;nbsp;You will be comfortable presenting Canvass&#8217;s value proposition and business case to the C-Executive Suite as well as the technical users. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will be called upon to utilize superior salesmanship to develop sales opportunities and identify the necessary decision makers and champions of the prospective deal. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will listen, identify and understand customer &amp;nbsp;needs and deliver to their expectations. You will be able to build relationships with multiple stakeholders and influence them in a positive way. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will actively seek out new sales leads and business opportunities through active networking and utilizing business referrals. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are hugely curious will constantly look for ways to enhance your knowledge of our industry, market, and competitors to provide that sales edge needed to close business and generate revenue. &amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt; Keep learning AND be curious: we are constantly looking for ways to enhance knowledge of our industry, market and competitors to provide the sales edge to close business and generate revenue. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will seek feedback at every opportunity so you can be the best you can be. &amp;nbsp;You will seek this from leaders, peers and clients. &lt;strong&gt;We do the right thing always and take extreme pride in who we are, what we build and what we do. &amp;nbsp;AND, we are led by character.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who You Are &amp;amp; What Makes You Qualified&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul role="list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are one to the top 10% of the sales people in your current company/division. &amp;nbsp;You are able to teach, tailor and take control of the sales cycle in a professional way. You are someone who pursues your passions with energy and commitment. &lt;strong&gt; We never, ever give up.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fast learner;&lt;/strong&gt; You are incredibly fast learner (we are in a market ready to change very fast and you have to be nimble of mind to keep up). &amp;nbsp;You have the intelligence to evolve to customer pain and map to customer personas and use cases. You will quickly learn our product, competition, processes, methodologies and how to build business cases mapped to successful business outcomes. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Persistence, Heart and Desire&lt;/strong&gt;. You will actively seek out new sales leads and business opportunities through active networking, partners and utilizing business referrals. You will be called upon to utilize superior salesmanship to develop sales opportunities and identify the necessary decision makers and influencers of the prospective deal. &amp;nbsp;get a thrill from pursuing the close which also means you are calm under pressure and can make sound decisions quickly. The confidence in our product and our company just makes it easier for you.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coachability and Adaptability:&lt;/strong&gt; You believe in following a process because it works and changing it up when it doesn&#8217;t. You want to contribute to building tactics and refining our processes for repeatable success. Being familiar with MEDDICC and Challenger Sales is a plus. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul role="list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integrity:&lt;/strong&gt; You will seek feedback at every opportunity so you can be the best you can be. &amp;nbsp;You will seek this from leaders, peers and clients. &lt;strong&gt;We do the right thing always and take extreme pride in who we are, what we build and what we do. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curiosity:&lt;/strong&gt; You are hugely curious will constantly look for ways to enhance your knowledge of our industry, market, and competitors to provide that sales edge needed to close business and generate revenue. &amp;nbsp;You will keep asking the customer questions and gain validation of what you heard throughout the customer journey. &lt;strong&gt;Keep learning. AND be curious: we are constantly looking for ways to enhance knowledge of our industry, market and competitors to provide the sales edge to close business and generate revenue&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul role="list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;You love the Digital Transformation Revolution You understand challenging the status quo will provide positive business impact to all functions of an organization is critical. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#183; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 5+ years success in industrial or enterprise software sales or business technology products and services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul role="list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with and understanding of AI and Machine Learning is highly favorable. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exemplary written and oral communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal, planning, and organizational skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Data" experience &#8211; big data, analytics, data science, machine learning, data integration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with selling within Industrial Manufacturing is a plus. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Background in selling innovation and new concepts to large Enterprises&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to travel 10 to 40%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Software scale up experience is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s degree required&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You want to join a company that&#8217;s at the forefront of leading edge technology and you want to be the person that takes us there and captures massive market share. You want to be part of an ambitious, successful team that is rapidly scaling up, that gives you room to grow and recognition as you close new accounts. With a shorter-than-usual sales cycle for enterprise, you will reap the rewards of your efforts with uncapped commission and great incentive targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Some of the benefits you can expect as part of our team include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul role="list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inclusive culture, open to ideas&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Generous time off, including vacation and personal days to help rejuvenate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extended health benefits, including drug coverage, dental coverage, and Health Spending Account&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flexible office policy, with options to work remotely&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Attend Conferences to extend your knowledge and skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Company-provided MacBooks and standing desks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Top technology and tools to excel at your role&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Equity Plan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8205;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8205;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Join Canvass?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canvass Analytics is using AI to automate operations for the Industrial sector. We are changing the way industry thinks and uses AI, and it&#8217;s getting noticed everywhere. &amp;nbsp;We&#8217;ve been recognized by Network World as a Top 10 Hot AI-Powered IoT Startups and by Canadian Innovation Exchange as a Top 20 Most Innovative Canadian Company. Canvass is backed by Google&#8217;s Gradient Ventures and Yamaha Ventures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What\'s it like working at Canvass&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a place where everyone is all in. From the CEO to the newest hire, we all pitch in where needed and do what it takes. &amp;nbsp;We are a relatively flat organization where everyone is invited to the table, to listen in and be part of the conversation and decisions. &amp;nbsp;We have an inclusive culture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&#8205;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.canvass.io/careers/sales-account-executive</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298882/canvass-logo-rgb_1_.jpg</logo><company>Canvass Analytics Inc.</company></item><item><title>Engineering Program Manager - Data - Remote</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="grid__item grid__item--tablet-up-two-thirds job-posting__grid-content"&gt;      &lt;div class="block"&gt;        &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;About the role&lt;/h2&gt;        &lt;p class="block__content"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re looking for an Engineering Program Manager to join the Shopify Data Platform Engineering team to help us shape the future of Data Platform Engineering, as well as help guide our next program manager hires.&lt;br&gt;Our team builds and maintains Shopify&#8217;s data infrastructure through tools, software, and data engineering. We make sure that Shopify, its merchants, partners, and internal teams have the data they need when and where they need it most. &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;You&#8217;ll help us develop, build and deliver better ways to distribute, use, and make decisions with data across our growing organization. You&#8217;ll be working in a collaborative environment with highly technical individuals and teams, with stakeholders that are versed in data and engineering practices and principles. This means getting deep into understanding data, engineering, and working with product management.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Day in the Life of a Shopify Engineering Program Manager :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developing a deep understanding of our team\'s technical capacity and goals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Managing relationships with our stakeholders/internal customers; customer and stakeholder management will be a key component of this role&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Navigating projects between Data Platform Engineering and other teams across Shopify, which requires building high-trust relationships on both sides&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensuring projects are not developed or delivered in isolation from each other, but rather as complementary &amp;nbsp;projects with clear scopes that contribute to the larger goals of Data Platform Engineering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Applying and training our team on project management good practices and tools&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Delivering cross-team and cross-organization initiatives through project management and process design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working with and managing a pipeline of customers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Owning and managing relationships with external vendors&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partnering with highly technical teams and individuals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working with multidisciplinary teams&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Passion for building roadmaps and leading teams towards impactful results&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding of how to build scalable and reliable systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A background in software development or Computer Science/Software Engineering education&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It&#8217;d be great if you have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with a variety of big data technologies/concepts &amp;nbsp;including Flink, DBT, Kafka, Data Flow, Presto&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with a variety of technologies, including Google Cloud Platform, Kubernetes, or other PaaS technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with data reporting tools, including Tableau, Mode, Superset, Streamlit, or others&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Note: if some of this tech is new to you, that\'s okay! We realise that not everyone has worked with this stack before and provide opportunities for learning as you go.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;p&gt;The posting will close on the 6th October.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Shopify, we are committed to building and fostering an environment where our employees feel included, valued, and heard. Our belief is that a strong commitment to diversity and inclusion enables us to truly make commerce better for everyone. We strongly encourage applications from Indigenous peoples, racialized people, people with disabilities, people from gender and sexually diverse communities, and/or people with intersectional identities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We know that applying to a new role takes a lot of work and we truly value your time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;How we hire&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              At Shopify, we put a lot of care and time into who we hire. We believe that in order to build the best products, we need to build high impact teams. Our recruitment process centres around what we call the Life Story interview, a conversational-style interview where we get to learn more about you.&lt;/div&gt;            &lt;a class="link link--secondary link--point-right" href="/careers/how-we-hire"&gt;Learn more about our hiring process&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="link__arrow"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon link__arrow-inner" aria-hidden="true" focusable="false"&gt; &lt;use xlink:href="#modules-arrow-right"&gt;&lt;/use&gt; &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.shopify.ca/careers/engineering-program-manager-data-remote_864c742e-a80a-4d6a-89fd-1ac93e6b80aa</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298787/shopify_logo_square.png</logo><company>Shopify Inc.</company></item><item><title>Data Science Manager (Remote, Canada)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="grid__item grid__item--tablet-up-two-thirds job-posting__grid-content"&gt;      &lt;div class="block"&gt;        &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;About the role&lt;/h2&gt;        &lt;p class="block__content"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data is a crucial part of Shopify&#8217;s mission to make commerce better for everyone. We organize and interpret petabytes of data to provide solutions for our merchants and stakeholders across the organization. From pipelines and schema design to machine learning products and decision support, data science at Shopify is a diverse role with many opportunities to positively impact our success.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for Data Science Managers to join our Data Science teams&amp;nbsp;and help shape the insights and algorithms that will inform our&amp;nbsp;strategies as we grow globally.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What your role will look like:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partner closely with product, engineering and other RnD stakeholders to guide their decisions using data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proactively identify and champion projects that solve complex problems across multiple domains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply specialized skills and fundamental data science methods (e.g. experimental design, recommender systems and machine learning when needed) to inform improvements to our business&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design and implement end-to-end data pipelines: work closely with stakeholders to build&amp;nbsp; models, tables or schemas that support business processes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Empower teams to build and maintain actionable KPIs, production-quality dashboards, informative deep dives, and scalable data products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will need to have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;7-10 years of commercial experience as in a data science role&amp;nbsp;solving high impact business problems, including 3+ years leading and maintaining&amp;nbsp;high performance data science teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience building and managing high performance data science teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience delivering business impact through analysis and data products&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience building data pipelines and driving ETL design decisions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technical leadership and management experience (you enjoy doing both).&amp;nbsp; You can jump into the code to the level that your direct reports admire and respect, but are also interested in developing people and capacity for your team&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience creating data product strategies, shipping data products, iterating after launch, and trying again&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience using Python including a strong grasp of object oriented programming (OOP) fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong ability to prioritize and communicate to technical and non-technical audiences alike&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It would be great if you have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Previous experience using Spark (either via Scala or Pyspark)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with statistical methods like regression, GLMs or experiment design and analysis, shipping productionized&amp;nbsp;machine learning systems or other advanced techniques are also welcome&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with data storytelling using&amp;nbsp;Tableau, QlikView, Mode, Matplotlib, D3, or similar data visualization tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;p&gt;All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&#8217;re interested in helping us shape the future of commerce at Shopify, click the &#8220;Apply Now&#8221; button to submit your application. Please submit a resume and cover letter with your application. Make sure to tell us how you think you can make an impact at Shopify, and what drew you to the role.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply before October 15th, 5:00 pm EST.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;At Shopify, we are committed to building and fostering an environment where our employees feel included, valued, and heard.&amp;nbsp;Our belief is that a strong commitment to diversity &amp;amp; inclusion enables us to truly make commerce better for everyone. We encourage applications from Indigenous peoples, racialized people, people with disabilities, people from gender and sexually diverse communities, and/or people with intersectional identities. Please take a look at &lt;a href="https://www.shopify.com/about/environment#SustainabilityReports"&gt;our Sustainability Reports&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about Shopify&#8217;s commitments to our communities, and our planet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;How we hire&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              At Shopify, we put a lot of care and time into who we hire. We believe that in order to build the best products, we need to build high impact teams. Our recruitment process centres around what we call the Life Story interview, a conversational-style interview where we get to learn more about you.&lt;/div&gt;            &lt;a class="link link--secondary link--point-right" href="/careers/how-we-hire"&gt;Learn more about our hiring process&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="link__arrow"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon link__arrow-inner" aria-hidden="true" focusable="false"&gt; &lt;use xlink:href="#modules-arrow-right"&gt;&lt;/use&gt; &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.shopify.ca/careers/data-science-manager-remote-canada_60487190-f32f-4238-9ce6-927f91892e76</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298787/shopify_logo_square.png</logo><company>Shopify Inc.</company></item><item><title>Staff Data Scientist (Remote, Canada)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="grid__item grid__item--tablet-up-two-thirds job-posting__grid-content"&gt;      &lt;div class="block"&gt;        &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;About the role&lt;/h2&gt;        &lt;p class="block__content"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data is a crucial part of Shopify&#8217;s mission to make commerce better for everyone. We organize and interpret petabytes of data to provide solutions for our merchants and stakeholders across the organization. From pipelines and schema design to machine learning products and decision support, data science at Shopify is a diverse role with many opportunities to positively impact our success.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Staff Data Scientists focus on pushing products and the business forward, with a focus on solving important problems rather than specific tools. We are looking for talented data scientists to help us better understand our merchants and buyers so we can help them on their journey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;7-10 years of commercial experience in a data science role solving high impact business problems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have well built technical experience that inspires individual contributors&amp;nbsp; creativity and innovation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience with product leadership and technical decision making.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have been working closely with various levels of business stakeholders, from c-suite and down.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can jump into the code on a deep level, but are also able to contribute to long term initiatives by mentoring your team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Multiple work streams excites you, you are able to use ambiguity as an opportunity for high level thinking.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience creating data product strategies,&amp;nbsp;data products, iterating after launch, and trying again.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience using Python including a strong grasp of object oriented programming (OOP) fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What would be great if you have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Previous experience using Spark.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with statistical methods like regression, GLMs or experiment design and analysis.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exposure to Tableau, QlikView, Mode, Matplotlib, or similar data visualization tools.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;p&gt;All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&#8217;re interested in helping us shape the future of commerce at Shopify, click the &#8220;Apply Now&#8221; button to submit your application. Please submit a resume and cover letter with your application. Make sure to tell us how you think you can make an impact at Shopify, and what drew you to the role.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply before October 15th, 5:00 pm EST.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;At Shopify, we are committed to building and fostering an environment where our employees feel included, valued, and heard.&amp;nbsp;Our belief is that a strong commitment to diversity &amp;amp; inclusion enables us to truly make commerce better for everyone. We encourage applications from Indigenous peoples, racialized people, people with disabilities, people from gender and sexually diverse communities, and/or people with intersectional identities. Please take a look at &lt;a href="https://www.shopify.com/about/environment#SustainabilityReports"&gt;our Sustainability Reports&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about Shopify&#8217;s commitments to our communities, and our planet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;How we hire&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              At Shopify, we put a lot of care and time into who we hire. We believe that in order to build the best products, we need to build high impact teams. Our recruitment process centres around what we call the Life Story interview, a conversational-style interview where we get to learn more about you.&lt;/div&gt;            &lt;a class="link link--secondary link--point-right" href="/careers/how-we-hire"&gt;Learn more about our hiring process&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="link__arrow"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon link__arrow-inner" aria-hidden="true" focusable="false"&gt; &lt;use xlink:href="#modules-arrow-right"&gt;&lt;/use&gt; &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.shopify.ca/careers/staff-data-scientist-remote-canada_c820bb56-a6e6-42be-9125-94c4b0a9a479</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298787/shopify_logo_square.png</logo><company>Shopify Inc.</company></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist (Remote, Canada)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="grid__item grid__item--tablet-up-two-thirds job-posting__grid-content"&gt;      &lt;div class="block"&gt;        &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;About the role&lt;/h2&gt;        &lt;p class="block__content"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data is a crucial part of Shopify&#8217;s mission to make commerce better for everyone. We organize and interpret petabytes of data to provide solutions for our merchants and stakeholders across the organization. From pipelines and schema design to machine learning products and decision support, data science at Shopify is a diverse role with many opportunities to positively impact our success.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Data Scientists focus on pushing products and the business forward, with a focus on solving important problems rather than specific tools. We are looking for talented data scientists to help us better understand our merchants and buyers so we can help them on their journey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proactively identify and champion projects that solve complex problems across multiple domains&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partner closely with product, engineering and other business leaders to influence product and program decisions with data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apply specialized skills and fundamental data science methods (e.g. regression, survival analysis, segmentation, experimentation, and machine learning when needed) to inform improvements to our business&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and implement end-to-end data pipelines: work closely with stakeholders to build instrumentation and define dimensional models, tables or schemas &amp;nbsp;that support business processes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build actionable KPIs, production-quality dashboards, informative deep dives, and scalable data products&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Influence leadership to drive more data-informed decisions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Define and advance best practices within data science and product teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;4-6 years of commercial experience as a Data Scientist &#8203;&#8203;&#8203;&#8203;&#8203;&#8203;solving high impact business problems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extensive experience with Python and software engineering fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with applied statistics and quantitative modelling (e.g. regression, survival analysis, segmentation, experimentation, and machine learning when needed)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to translate analytical insights into clear recommendations and effectively communicate them to technical and non-technical stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Curiosity about the problem domain and an analytical approach&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong sense of ownership and growth mindset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience with one or more:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of advanced SQL techniques&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expertise with statistical techniques and their applications in business&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Masterful data storytelling and strategic thinking&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of dimensional modelling and scaling ETL pipelines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience launching productionized machine learning models at scale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extensive domain experience in e-commerce, marketing or SaaS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;p&gt;All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you&#8217;re interested in helping us shape the future of commerce at Shopify, click the &#8220;Apply Now&#8221; button to submit your application. Please submit a resume and cover letter with your application. Make sure to tell us how you think you can make an impact at Shopify, and what drew you to the role.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply before October 15th, 5:00 pm EST.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;At Shopify, we are committed to building and fostering an environment where our employees feel included, valued, and heard.&amp;nbsp;Our belief is that a strong commitment to diversity &amp;amp; inclusion enables us to truly make commerce better for everyone. We encourage applications from Indigenous peoples, racialized people, people with disabilities, people from gender and sexually diverse communities, and/or people with intersectional identities. Please take a look at &lt;a href="https://www.shopify.com/about/environment#SustainabilityReports"&gt;our Sustainability Reports&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about Shopify&#8217;s commitments to our communities, and our planet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;How we hire&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              At Shopify, we put a lot of care and time into who we hire. We believe that in order to build the best products, we need to build high impact teams. Our recruitment process centres around what we call the Life Story interview, a conversational-style interview where we get to learn more about you.&lt;/div&gt;            &lt;a class="link link--secondary link--point-right" href="/careers/how-we-hire"&gt;Learn more about our hiring process&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="link__arrow"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon link__arrow-inner" aria-hidden="true" focusable="false"&gt; &lt;use xlink:href="#modules-arrow-right"&gt;&lt;/use&gt; &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.shopify.ca/careers/senior-data-scientist-remote-canada_36f0f3fb-7421-4620-909e-cb88da269b16</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298787/shopify_logo_square.png</logo><company>Shopify Inc.</company></item><item><title>Data Development Manager (Remote, Canada)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="grid__item grid__item--tablet-up-two-thirds job-posting__grid-content"&gt;      &lt;div class="block"&gt;        &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;About the role&lt;/h2&gt;        &lt;p class="block__content"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Data Platform Engineering group builds and maintains the platform that delivers accessible data to power decision-making at Shopify for over a million merchants. We&#8217;re hiring high-impact developers across teams:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Engine group organizes all merchant and Shopify data into our data lake in highly-optimized formats for fast query processing, and maintaining the security and quality of our datasets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Analytics group leverages the Engine primitives to build and deliver simple and useful products that power scalable transformation of data at Shopify in batch, streaming, or for machine learning. This group is focused on making it really simple for our users to answer three questions: What happened in the past? What is happening now? And, what will happen in the future?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Data Experiences group builds end-user experiences for experimentation, data discovery, and business intelligence reporting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Reliability group operates the data platform in a consistent and reliable manner. They build tools for other teams on Data Platform to leverage and encourage consistency as they champion reliability across the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your role:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Providing people and technical leadership within your team to support the mission of the Data Platform Engineering group.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working closely with a cross-functional team of product leaders, engineering leaders, and distributed system engineers to influence the organizational vision and help solve hard problems in scaling the data platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strategic and tactical deliverables for your team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deploying the team towards data platform priorities, achieving measurable impact and outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Defining and executing on your team&#8217;s deliverables.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sourcing and hiring for positions in your team or organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;All aspects of performance management, including compensation, performance improvement plans, promotions, and separations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              &lt;p&gt;About You:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;An experienced manager of teams of high-performing engineers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technical engineering background in one or more areas listed in the next section.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A proven track record of delivering impactful results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exceptional communication skills and ability to translate technical concepts into easy to understand language for our stakeholders.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excitement for working with a remote team; you value collaborating on problems, asking questions, delivering feedback, and supporting others in their goals whether they are in your vicinity or entire cities apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Data Development Manager at Shopify would typically have at least 2 years of experience leading high-functioning teams, and expertise in &lt;strong&gt;one or more&lt;/strong&gt; of the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with the internals of a distributed compute engine (Spark, Presto, DBT, or Flink/Beam)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in query optimization, resource allocation and management, and data lake performance (Presto, SQL)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with cloud infrastructure (Google Cloud, Kubernetes, Terraform)&lt;br&gt;Experience with security products and methods (Apache Ranger, Apache Knox, OAuth, IAM, Kerberos)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience deploying and scaling ML solutions using open-source frameworks (MLFlow, TFX, H2O, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience building full-stack applications (Ruby/Rails, React, TypeScript)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background and practical experience in statistics and/or computational mathematics (Bayesian and Frequentist approaches, NumPy, PyMC3, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Modern Big-Data storage technologies (Iceberg, Hudi, Delta)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;p&gt;Please apply before October 15th, 5:00 pm EST.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;At Shopify, we are committed to building and fostering an environment where our employees feel included, valued, and heard. Our belief is that a strong commitment to diversity and inclusion enables us to truly make commerce better for everyone. We strongly encourage applications from Indigenous people, racialized people, people with disabilities, people from gender and sexually diverse communities and/or people with intersectional identities.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shopify is now permanently remote and working towards a future that is digital by design.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.shopify.com/careers/work-anywhere"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;How we hire&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              At Shopify, we put a lot of care and time into who we hire. We believe that in order to build the best products, we need to build high impact teams. Our recruitment process centres around what we call the Life Story interview, a conversational-style interview where we get to learn more about you.&lt;/div&gt;            &lt;a class="link link--secondary link--point-right" href="/careers/how-we-hire"&gt;Learn more about our hiring process&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="link__arrow"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon link__arrow-inner" aria-hidden="true" focusable="false"&gt; &lt;use xlink:href="#modules-arrow-right"&gt;&lt;/use&gt; &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.shopify.ca/careers/data-development-manager-remote-canada_71646971-1d64-4512-85d6-6d76ac747d17</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298787/shopify_logo_square.png</logo><company>Shopify Inc.</company></item><item><title>Staff Data Engineer (Remote, Canada)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="grid__item grid__item--tablet-up-two-thirds job-posting__grid-content"&gt;      &lt;div class="block"&gt;        &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;About the role&lt;/h2&gt;        &lt;p class="block__content"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Data Platform Engineering group builds and maintains the platform that delivers accessible data to power decision-making at Shopify for over a million merchants. We&#8217;re hiring high-impact developers across teams:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Engine group organizes all merchant and Shopify data into our data lake in highly-optimized formats for fast query processing, and maintaining the security and quality of our datasets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Analytics group leverages the Engine primitives to build and deliver simple and useful products that power scalable transformation of data at Shopify in batch, streaming, or for machine learning. This group is focused on making it really simple for our users to answer three questions: What happened in the past? What is happening now? And, what will happen in the future?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Data Experiences group builds end-user experiences for experimentation, data discovery, and business intelligence reporting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Reliability group operates the data platform in a consistent and reliable manner. They build tools for other teams on Data Platform to leverage and encourage consistency as they champion reliability across the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;An experienced technical leader with a proven track record of delivering impactful results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technical engineering background in one or more areas in the next section.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with technical mentoring, coaching, and improving the technical output of the people around you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exceptional communication skills and ability to translate technical concepts into easy to understand language for our stakeholders.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excitement for working with a remote team; you value collaborating on problems, asking questions, delivering feedback, and supporting others in their goals whether they are in your vicinity or entire cities apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Staff Data Developer would typically have 6-10 years of experience in &lt;strong&gt;one or more&lt;/strong&gt; of the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with the internals of a distributed compute engine (Spark, Presto, DBT, or Flink/Beam)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in query optimization, resource allocation and management, and data lake performance (Presto, SQL)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with cloud infrastructure (Google Cloud, Kubernetes, Terraform)&lt;br&gt;Experience with security products and methods (Apache Ranger, Apache Knox, OAuth, IAM, Kerberos)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience deploying and scaling ML solutions using open-source frameworks (MLFlow, TFX, H2O, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience building full-stack applications (Ruby/Rails, React, TypeScript)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Background and practical experience in statistics and/or computational mathematics (Bayesian and Frequentist approaches, NumPy, PyMC3, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Modern Big-Data storage technologies (Iceberg, Hudi, Delta)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;p&gt;Please apply before October 15th, 5:00 pm EST.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;At Shopify, we are committed to building and fostering an environment where our employees feel included, valued, and heard. Our belief is that a strong commitment to diversity and inclusion enables us to truly make commerce better for everyone. We strongly encourage applications from Indigenous people, racialized people, people with disabilities, people from gender and sexually diverse communities and/or people with intersectional identities.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shopify is now permanently remote and working towards a future that is digital by design.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.shopify.com/careers/work-anywhere"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;#LI-REMOTE&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;How we hire&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              At Shopify, we put a lot of care and time into who we hire. We believe that in order to build the best products, we need to build high impact teams. Our recruitment process centres around what we call the Life Story interview, a conversational-style interview where we get to learn more about you.&lt;/div&gt;            &lt;a class="link link--secondary link--point-right" href="/careers/how-we-hire"&gt;Learn more about our hiring process&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="link__arrow"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon link__arrow-inner" aria-hidden="true" focusable="false"&gt; &lt;use xlink:href="#modules-arrow-right"&gt;&lt;/use&gt; &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.shopify.ca/careers/staff-data-engineer-remote-canada_9356598e-1a12-4c7f-8133-f611f0c83cb5</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298787/shopify_logo_square.png</logo><company>Shopify Inc.</company></item><item><title>Senior Data Engineer (Remote, Canada)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="grid__item grid__item--tablet-up-two-thirds job-posting__grid-content"&gt;      &lt;div class="block"&gt;        &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;About the role&lt;/h2&gt;        &lt;p class="block__content"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our&amp;nbsp;Data Platform Engineering group&amp;nbsp;builds&amp;nbsp;and maintains&amp;nbsp;the platform that delivers accessible data to power decision-making at Shopify for over&amp;nbsp;a million merchants. We&#8217;re hiring high-impact developers across teams:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Engine group organizes all merchant and Shopify data into our data lake in highly-optimized formats for fast query processing, and maintaining the security +&amp;nbsp;quality of our datasets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Analytics group builds products that leverage the Engine primitives to deliver simple and useful products that power scalable transformation of data at Shopify in batch, or streaming, or for machine learning. This group is focused on making it really simple for our users to answer three questions: What happened in the past? What is happening now? And, what will happen in the future?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Data Experiences group builds end-user experiences for experimentation, data discovery, and business intelligence reporting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Reliability group operates the data platform efficiently in a consistent and reliable manner. They build tools for other teams at Data Platform to leverage to encourage consistency and they champion reliability across the platform.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              &lt;p&gt;While our&amp;nbsp;teams value&amp;nbsp;specialized skills, they\'ve also got a lot in common. We\'re looking for a(n):&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High-energy self-starter with experience and passion for data and big data scale processing. You enjoy working in fast-paced environments and love making an impact.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exceptional communicator with&amp;nbsp;the&amp;nbsp;ability to translate technical concepts into easy to understand language for our stakeholders.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excitement for working with a remote team; you value collaborating on problems, asking questions, delivering feedback, and supporting others in their goals whether they are in your vicinity or entire cities apart.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid software engineer: experienced in building and maintaining systems at scale.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Senior Data Developer at Shopify typically has&amp;nbsp;4-6 years of experience in &lt;strong&gt;one or more&lt;/strong&gt; of the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working with the internals of a distributed compute engine (Spark, Presto, DBT, or Flink/Beam)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Query optimization, resource allocation and management, and data lake performance (Presto, SQL)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cloud infrastructure (Google Cloud, Kubernetes, Terraform)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Security products and methods (Apache Ranger, Apache Knox, OAuth, IAM, Kerberos)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deploying and scaling ML solutions using open-source frameworks (MLFlow, TFX, H2O, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Building full-stack applications (Ruby/Rails, React, TypeScript)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Background and practical experience in statistics and/or computational mathematics (Bayesian and Frequentist approaches, NumPy, PyMC3, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Modern Big-Data storage technologies (Iceberg, Hudi, Delta)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;#Senior Software Developer- Distributed Systems #Senior Software Developer- Data Engineering #Senior Data App Developer #Senior Data Reliability Engineer #Senior Software Developer- Reliability&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;p&gt;Please apply before October 15th, 5:00 pm EST.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;At Shopify, we are committed to building and fostering an environment where our employees feel included, valued, and heard. Our belief is that a strong commitment to diversity and inclusion enables us to truly make commerce better for everyone. We strongly encourage applications from Indigenous people, racialized people, people with disabilities, people from gender and sexually diverse communities and/or people with intersectional identities.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shopify is now permanently remote and working towards a future that is digital by design. &lt;a href="https://www.shopify.com/careers/work-anywhere"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;#LI-REMOTE&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;How we hire&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              At Shopify, we put a lot of care and time into who we hire. We believe that in order to build the best products, we need to build high impact teams. Our recruitment process centres around what we call the Life Story interview, a conversational-style interview where we get to learn more about you.&lt;/div&gt;            &lt;a class="link link--secondary link--point-right" href="/careers/how-we-hire"&gt;Learn more about our hiring process&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="link__arrow"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon link__arrow-inner" aria-hidden="true" focusable="false"&gt; &lt;use xlink:href="#modules-arrow-right"&gt;&lt;/use&gt; &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.shopify.ca/careers/senior-data-engineer-remote-canada_767261d1-3030-4bb3-894a-242c550f4f1a</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298787/shopify_logo_square.png</logo><company>Shopify Inc.</company></item><item><title>Senior Data Science Manager, Commercial (Remote, Canada)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="grid__item grid__item--tablet-up-two-thirds job-posting__grid-content"&gt;      &lt;div class="block"&gt;        &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;About the role&lt;/h2&gt;        &lt;p class="block__content"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data Science &amp;amp; Engineering is a crucial part of Shopify&#8217;s mission to make commerce better for everyone. We organize and interpret petabytes of data to provide solutions for our merchants and stakeholders across the organization. From pipelines and schema design to machine learning products and decision support, data science at Shopify is a diverse role with many opportunities to positively impact our success. The Data Science &amp;amp; Engineering team acts as the impact multiplier for Shopify&#8217;s product teams, putting over 11 petabytes of data to work to make our merchants more successful.&amp;nbsp; From delivering merchandising insights to optimizing shipping and processing rates, to reducing credit card fraud, to ad campaign recommendations - our Data Scientists deliver solutions from pipeline to the platform via an array of open source tools.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a Senior Data Science Manager to lead the team that partners with our Commercial Data Science team. The Commercial&amp;nbsp;team is a rapidly growing area within Shopify that plays a vital role in delivering on this vision by reaching entrepreneurs around the world and helping them succeed on Shopify. The Commercial&amp;nbsp;team&#8217;s mission is to empower the most entrepreneurs to succeed. Commercial Data Science and Engineering builds data-informed growth strategies and data products that enable merchants to come, stay and grow on Shopify.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What your role will look like:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working closely with an interdisciplinary team, you and your team will tackle challenging marketing, commercial&amp;nbsp;and growth-related problems. We build strong data foundations, anomaly detection tools, and reporting frameworks to empower the growth organization to make great decisions quickly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the Data Science &amp;amp; Engineering team members you&#8217;ll work with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/allaahilal/"&gt;Ella Hilal, Director of Data Science, Growth and Revenue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kirjain/"&gt;Kiran Jain, Director of Data Science, Growth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shopify team members you&#8217;ll work closely with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/morganb/"&gt;Morgan Brown, VP Growth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will need to have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Experience at scale:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;You&#8217;ve been a leader in multiple tech companies where analytics on top of massive data sets drives product/business decisions and results in powerful data products. You have a strong background in machine learning including experience implementing models and productionizing innovative end-to-end machine learning systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analytics expertise:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;You&#8217;ll need to be amazing at coming up with new, meaningful metrics to measure success of our products; you\'ll be equally strong at making sure the data needed to support those metrics are available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Well-balanced skills:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;People have trouble pinning you down. Business, product and technical teams claim you as their own.&amp;nbsp; You are equal parts technical and functional (and both are exceptionally strong), and you are equally comfortable and effective at presenting to technical or business leaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Passionate about business strategy:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;You&#8217;ve experienced and thrived in similar channel-related environments and have a knack for working with business users that are responsible for top-line growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team development:&lt;/strong&gt; You&#8217;ll need a demonstrated track record of attracting top data/analytics talent, developing those people (both ICs and managers) to make them even better, and managing the growth of teams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key technology stack and tools we work with:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Python&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SQL&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spark&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Google Cloud Platform&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;p&gt;We know that applying to a new role takes a lot of work and we truly value your time. We are looking forward to reading your application. Shopify is now permanently remote and working towards a future that is digital by default. &lt;a href="https://www.shopify.com/careers/work-anywhere"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt; about what this can mean for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply before October 15th, 5:00 pm EST.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Shopify, we are committed to building and fostering an environment where our employees feel included, valued, and heard. Our belief is that a strong commitment to diversity and inclusion enables us to truly make commerce better for everyone. We strongly encourage applications from Indigenous people, racialized people, people with disabilities, people from gender and sexually diverse communities and/or people with intersectional identities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;#LI-REMOTE&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;How we hire&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              At Shopify, we put a lot of care and time into who we hire. We believe that in order to build the best products, we need to build high impact teams. Our recruitment process centres around what we call the Life Story interview, a conversational-style interview where we get to learn more about you.&lt;/div&gt;            &lt;a class="link link--secondary link--point-right" href="/careers/how-we-hire"&gt;Learn more about our hiring process&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="link__arrow"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon link__arrow-inner" aria-hidden="true" focusable="false"&gt; &lt;use xlink:href="#modules-arrow-right"&gt;&lt;/use&gt; &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.shopify.ca/careers/senior-data-science-manager-commercial-remote-canada_33147676-6171-445b-87ce-0aeba50fac07</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298787/shopify_logo_square.png</logo><company>Shopify Inc.</company></item><item><title>Senior Data Science Manager, Operate (Remote, Canada)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="grid__item grid__item--tablet-up-two-thirds job-posting__grid-content"&gt;      &lt;div class="block"&gt;        &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;About the role&lt;/h2&gt;        &lt;p class="block__content"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data Science &amp;amp; Engineering is a crucial part of Shopify&#8217;s mission to make commerce better for everyone. We organize and interpret petabytes of data to provide solutions for our merchants and stakeholders across the organization. From pipelines and schema design to machine learning products and decision support, data science at Shopify is a diverse role with many opportunities to positively impact our success. The Data Science &amp;amp; Engineering team acts as the impact multiplier for Shopify&#8217;s product teams, putting over 11 petabytes of data to work to make our merchants more successful.&amp;nbsp; From delivering merchandising insights to optimizing shipping and processing rates, to reducing credit card fraud, to ad campaign recommendations - our Data Scientists deliver solutions from pipeline to the platform via an array of open source tools.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a&lt;strong&gt; Senior Data Science Manager&lt;/strong&gt; to lead the team that partners with our Operate data team (part of Core). The Shopify Core is what&#8217;s &#8220;in the box&#8221; when merchants sign up for Shopify: the world&#8217;s best Online Store, Checkout, and the Admin to set up and run their business. The Operate&#8217;s Mission is to help merchants start and run their business on Shopify&#8217;s platform by building the most powerful Admin. Operate Data Science and Engineering team contributes to this mission by building best-in-class insights and data products to enable every merchant&#8217;s success.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What your role will look like:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working closely with an interdisciplinary team, you and your team will be responsible for the evolution of all admin tools (such as admin home, navigation, search, etc.) across mobile and web and tackle the evolution of how our most sophisticated merchants are utilizing our platform (large organizations with multiple businesses and staff). Your team will focus on developing strong data foundations, data-informed products, and reporting and experimentation frameworks to empower the Operate organization to make great decisions quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will need to have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team development:&lt;/strong&gt; You&#8217;ll need a demonstrated track record of attracting top data/analytics talent, developing those people (both ICs and managers) to make them even better, and managing the growth of teams. You have several years of experience managing and scaling multiple teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Experience at scale:&lt;/strong&gt; You&#8217;ve been a leader in multiple companies where analytics on top of massive data sets drives product/business decisions and results in powerful data products. You have extensive experience with technologies like SQL, Spark, and Python.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analytics expertise:&lt;/strong&gt; You&#8217;ll need to be amazing at coming up with new, meaningful metrics to measure the success of our products; you\'ll be equally strong at making sure the data needed to support those metrics are available. You have multiple years of experience managing decisions at scale, including causal inference and experimentation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Well-balanced skills:&lt;/strong&gt; People have trouble pinning you down. Business, product, and technical teams claim you as their own.&amp;nbsp; You are equal parts technical and functional (and both are exceptionally strong), and you are equally comfortable and effective at presenting to technical or business leaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Passionate about business strategy: &lt;/strong&gt;You&#8217;ve experienced and thrived in similar channel-related environments and have a knack for working with business users that are responsible for top-line growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key technology stack and tools we work with:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Python&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;SQL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spark&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google Cloud Platform&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mode/Tableau&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;      &lt;p&gt;We know that applying to a new role takes a lot of work and we truly value your time. We are looking forward to reading your application. Shopify is now permanently remote and working towards a future that is digital by default. &lt;a href="https://www.shopify.com/careers/work-anywhere"&gt;Learn more&lt;/a&gt; about what this can mean for you.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please apply before October 15th, 5:00 pm EST.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Shopify, we are committed to building and fostering an environment where our employees feel included, valued, and heard. Our belief is that a strong commitment to diversity and inclusion enables us to truly make commerce better for everyone. We strongly encourage applications from Indigenous people, racialized people, people with disabilities, people from gender and sexually diverse communities and/or people with intersectional identities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;div class="grid grid--equal-height"&gt;        &lt;div class="grid__item"&gt;          &lt;div class="block"&gt;            &lt;h2 class="block__heading heading--4"&gt;How we hire&lt;/h2&gt;            &lt;div class="block__content"&gt;              At Shopify, we put a lot of care and time into who we hire. We believe that in order to build the best products, we need to build high impact teams. Our recruitment process centres around what we call the Life Story interview, a conversational-style interview where we get to learn more about you.&lt;/div&gt;            &lt;a class="link link--secondary link--point-right" href="/careers/how-we-hire"&gt;Learn more about our hiring process&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class="link__arrow"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon link__arrow-inner" aria-hidden="true" focusable="false"&gt; &lt;use xlink:href="#modules-arrow-right"&gt;&lt;/use&gt; &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.shopify.ca/careers/senior-data-science-manager-operate-remote-canada_8d8ab872-83a2-4bc1-9c01-b743abe7323d</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298787/shopify_logo_square.png</logo><company>Shopify Inc.</company></item><item><title>Data Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why join us?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Are you looking to join a dynamic pension plan that embodies the strong values of its 500,000 members and is an industry leading global investor? &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;If so, we would love to tell you our story.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;At OMERS we put our people first and are proud to embrace the diversity of thought and leadership that comes from having locations in Toronto, London, New York, Singapore, Sydney and other major cities across North America and Europe. &amp;nbsp;Our culture is truly one of a kind. We get stuff done, and have fun doing it! &amp;nbsp;We take great pride in contributing to the communities where we live with an ever-constant eye to the global investment markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a key member of the Enterprise Data &amp;amp; Advanced Analytics team, the Data Engineer is passionate, down to earth, takes great pride in delivering next generation full stack solutions that meet and exceed our strategic business goals. Driving innovation in the development of advanced capabilities, you are leading with a product management &amp;amp; system-thinking approach. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;The candidate will develop end-to-end data pipelines, with a focus on system integration and cloud to support OMERS decision makers and collaborate with a community of designers, product managers, data engineers and architects in ideation, design, development, testing, technical support, research and knowledge-sharing through the implementation lifecycle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a member of this team, you will be responsible for:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Designing,&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;d&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;eploying and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;ustaining scaled data pipelines to achieve a high level of reliability, scalability and security in supporting business objectives.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sourcing, transforming and delivering structured and unstructured assets for use in Azure Databricks, Synapse Analytics, Power BI, and more.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Operating in an Agile development environment.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Communicating effectively with other engineers in the same team, with other teams and with various other&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;partners&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;such as product managers, data analysts, IT infrastructure specialists, security specialists, enterprise architects and members of senior management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Participating in solution build, delivery, support and troubleshooting.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leading&amp;nbsp;change and communicating impacts to business partners&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;and fellow team members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Exhibiting the ability to work on multiple projects simultaneously and ensuring delivery on time, within scope and within budget.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Participating in establishing sound data management practices for the team and the organization.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Identifying, defining and implementing opportunities for&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;improving&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;existing processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Defining and executing technical test plans, perform unit, performance and integration testing and automate regression testing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&#8203;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;To succeed in this role, you have:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;i&gt;Professional&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Experience&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;. 3+ years solving complex technical data projects using the Microsoft Azure data stack or equivalent work experience is&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Financial industry application is preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Industry Knowledge&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;bility&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;to quickly propose Azure Data Platform solutions by recalling the latest best practices learned from MVP &amp;amp; Product Team articles, MSFT documentation, whitepapers, and community publications is&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Relationship Building&lt;/b&gt;. Proven track record of building deep technical relationships. &amp;nbsp;Experience in aligning expectations across various&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;partners&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#8203;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Problem&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Solving.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The ability&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;to trace data lineage / workflows and resolve technical issues with minimal&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;direction&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Demonstrated proficiency in understanding and implementing business workflows is a plus.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Teamwork&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Motivated and keen to work in a collaborative environment with a focus on team success over and above individual success.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;i&gt;Technical&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Enterprise-scale technical experience with cloud and hybrid infrastructures, architecture designs, and technology management is&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Breadth of technical experience and knowledge across the Azure Data Platform, with depth / Subject Matter Expertise in&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;two&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;or more of the following Data Platform resources is&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8203;&lt;b&gt;&#8203;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Azure Data Factory,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; Dedicated Synapse SQL (SQL DW),&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; Azure Databricks,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; Azure Functions using C#, PowerShell or Python,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; Kubernetes and containerization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;automating CI/CD pipelines using Azure DevOps or equivalent work&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;experience is&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience with the Microsoft Power Platform is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience developing star schema reporting pipelines using Kimball or Data Vault v2.0 methodologies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience with GCP and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;BigQuery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;is preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;i&gt;Education&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s Degree in&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;an&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;appropriate field of study or equivalent work experienc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Candidates with&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;Microsoft&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Azure&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;certifications&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;are desired&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Our story:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Founded in 1962, OMERS is one of Canada&#8217;s largest defined benefit pension plans, with $105 billion in net assets as at December 31, 2020. &lt;/span&gt;OMERS is a jointly-sponsored pension plan, with 1,000 participating employers ranging from large cities to local agencies, and over half a million active, deferred and retired members. OMERS members include union and non-union employees of municipalities, school boards, local boards, transit systems, electrical utilities, emergency services and children&#8217;s aid societies across Ontario. Contributions to the Plan are funded equally by members and employers. OMERS teams work in Toronto, London, New York, Amsterdam, Luxembourg, Singapore, Sydney and other major cities across North America and Europe &#8211; serving members and employers and originating and managing a diversified portfolio of high-quality investments in public markets, private equity, infrastructure and real estate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;OMERS is committed to having a workforce that reflects the communities in which we live and work. We are an equal opportunity employer committed to a barrier-free recruitment and selection process. At OMERS inclusion and diversity means belonging. How we create a sense of belonging is through our employees and our vast network of Employee Resource Groups. Whether you are passionate about gender, pride, or visible minorities, we have groups that are focused on making a difference in all of our lives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://omers.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/OMERS_External/job/Head-Office-Toronto/Data-Engineer_JR-1163</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/881085/omers-logo-featured-image.jpg</logo><company>OMERS</company></item><item><title>Student Analyst, Retail Asset Management (Winter 2022 - 4 Months)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why join us?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Are you looking to join an innovative, global real estate company who builds communities and connects people to exceptional places? If so, we would love to tell you our story.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;At Oxford, our culture is truly one of a kind. Across business lines and around the world, we embrace the complex and tackle opportunities with speed and agility. We are ambitious and humble, forward looking and service-focused. We get stuff done, and have fun doing it! &amp;nbsp;We take great pride in contributing to the communities where we live. We believe that what is good for the environment is good for business. Together we deliver exceptional experiences to our over 2 million daily customers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Are you looking to join an innovative, global real estate company who builds communities and connects people to exceptional places? If so, we would love to tell you our story.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Oxford, our culture is truly one of a kind. Across business lines and around the world, we embrace the complex and tackle opportunities with speed and agility. We are ambitious and humble, forward looking and service-focused. We get stuff done, and have fun doing it! We take great pride in contributing to the communities where we live. We believe that what is good for the environment is good for business. Together we deliver exceptional experiences to our over 2 million daily customers.&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Oxford is looking for an Intern Analyst to join our Retail Asset Management team in Toronto, Canada. This position supports the retail leasing and operating teams in a collaborative effort to focus on driving asset values and investment returns. The Retail Asset Management group is principally responsible for maximizing returns and asset values, managing co-ownership relationships, developing asset management plans for each retail asset, and collaborating with key internal stakeholders including Development and Investments to drive asset values. The Intern Analyst will be an integral member of a lean team and be primarily responsible for a wide range of ad-hoc tasks and special projects. He/ she will gain exposure to all facets of the retail asset management business including leasing, operations, research, marketing and development.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;As a member of this team, you will be responsible for:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Participate in process improvement initiatives related to monthly/quarterly reporting and creation of data analytics dashboards&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Provide support on various ad-hoc tasks including but not limited to major leasing and capital investment decisions, tenant financial performance summaries, drawing insights from historical and budgeted property-level financials, etc.&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Assist the Asset Management team in the monitoring of operating and leasing targets as part of the annual budget process&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Work closely with the Analyst(s) in analyzing and identifying budget variances on a monthly and quarterly basis&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Participate in meetings with Leasing and Property teams to expand knowledge of real estate asset management and the retail sector&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Keep current with market trends and update/create market reports and research for internal use&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Assume leadership on any assigned special projects aimed at improving the overall asset management capabilities of our team in supporting leasing, operations and research&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;To succeed in this role, you have:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Working towards completion of an undergraduate or post-graduate degree with a concentration in Commerce, Finance, Data Analytics, Real Estate, Urban Planning or Engineering&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Thrive in organizations that constantly evolve and adapt&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Driven to achieving results and continuously striving to deliver the highest performance through creative thinking&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Prior internship experience in real estate (asset management, leasing, appraisal, investments or development) considered an asset&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Proficient in Microsoft Excel and PowerPoint, knowledge of ARGUS Enterprise considered an asset&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Self-motivated individual with a strong work ethic and a high level of attention to detail&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Demonstrate an eagerness to learn and respond well to constructive feedback&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Strong leadership, interpersonal, verbal and written communication, problem solving and project management skills&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Ability to work well under pressure with multiple competing deadlines&lt;br&gt;&#8226; Have a flexible attitude towards a variety of work tasks as is required in a small working group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Our story:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Oxford Properties Group (&#8220;Oxford&#8221;) is a leading global real estate investor, asset manager and business builder. It builds, buys and grows defined real estate operating business with world-class management teams. Established in 1960, Oxford and its portfolio companies manage approximately C$70 billion of assets across four continents on behalf of their investment partners. Oxford&#8217;s owned portfolio encompasses office, logistics, retail, multifamily residential, life sciences and hotels; it spans more than 150 million square feet in global gateway cities and high-growth hubs. A thematic investor with a committed source of capital, Oxford invests in properties, portfolios, development sites, debt, securities and real estate businesses across the risk-reward spectrum. Together with its portfolio companies, Oxford is one of the world&#8217;s most active developers with over 100 projects currently underway globally across all major asset classes. Oxford is owned by OMERS, the Canadian defined benefit pension plan for Ontario\'s municipal employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;For more information on Oxford, visit &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="http://www.oxfordproperties.com"&gt;&lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;www.oxfordproperties.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;OMERS is committed to having a workforce that reflects the communities in which we live and work. We are an equal opportunity employer committed to a barrier-free recruitment and selection process. At OMERS inclusion and diversity means belonging. How we create a sense of belonging is through our employees and our vast network of Employee Resource Groups. Whether you are passionate about gender, pride, or visible minorities, we have groups that are focused on making a difference in all of our lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://omers.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/OMERS_External/job/Head-Office-Toronto/Student-Analyst--Retail-Asset-Management--Winter-2022---4-Months-_JR-0188</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/881085/omers-logo-featured-image.jpg</logo><company>OMERS</company></item><item><title>Senior Specialist, Marketing (18 Month Contract)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why join us?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Are you looking to join an innovative, global real estate company who builds communities and connects people to exceptional places? If so, we would love to tell you our story.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;At Oxford, our culture is truly one of a kind. Across business lines and around the world, we embrace the complex and tackle opportunities with speed and agility. We are ambitious and humble, forward looking and service-focused. We get stuff done, and have fun doing it! &amp;nbsp;We take great pride in contributing to the communities where we live. We believe that what is good for the environment is good for business. Together we deliver exceptional experiences to our over 2 million daily customers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As the Senior Marketing Specialist, you are a clever, digitally savvy marketing professional who is passionate about executing with excellence. Known for an ability to partner with multiple stakeholders to support business strategy, you have a strong understanding of marketing, brand and communications best practices along with being an exceptional project manager. You are curious and proactive, comfortable working for an evolving global organization, navigating different cultures and contexts, and have a proven track record of supporting high performing and strategic marketing teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reporting to the Senior Manager, the Senior Marketing Specialist will ensure our global strategy is supported and regional needs are met, as we grow and scale globally. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;As a member of this team, you will be responsible for:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Project Management&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Working as a strategic partner to our internal cross-functional teammates, while comfortably and professionally managing the end-to-end process of mid-size marketing projects (i.e. the development of microsites, new collateral requests, and the creation of corporate videos)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Supporting the global marketing management team with the planning, implementation, and execution of larger strategic projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Adeptly digesting and translating briefs and job requests to define and develop marketing deliverables, pulling in key stakeholders as and when required&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Design and Creative&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Partnering with Global Creative Services to support our creative design studio through project management, creative development including writing, editing, sourcing images and/or video assets, customer relations and providing quality control of our brand&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Supporting relationships with third party agencies doing creative work on behalf of Oxford and its assets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Digital Marketing and Analytics&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Reading and understanding data and analytics to support our teams and our partners goals and objectives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;To succeed in this role, you must have:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A post secondary degree focused in business, marketing or a related field&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;4-5 years of experience in a similar role; experience in the real estate industry is considered an asset but not mandatory&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;High-quality and efficient writing and editing skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working with a creative studio and design team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Specific experience with Agility CMS Adobe Creative Suite, DAMs, CRMs. Experience with digital project management tools would be an asset&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with email marketing strategy, Google Analytics, Google AdWords, SEO principles and social media marketing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A passion for learning new and evolving marketing technology solutions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A desire to innovate and bring fresh solutions to problems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A customer service-oriented approach with the capability to excel in an agile and highly matrixed environment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working in a collaborative environment with a comfort for ambiguity and flexibility that comes with working cross-functionally&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A high level of comfort building trusting relationships, independently partnering with colleagues and interacting with senior leaders across the organization&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Openness to receiving constructive feedback and guidance as well as constructively sharing it with others to collectively elevate efforts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Our story:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Oxford Properties Group (&#8220;Oxford&#8221;) is a leading global real estate investor, asset manager and business builder. It builds, buys and grows defined real estate operating business with world-class management teams. Established in 1960, Oxford and its portfolio companies manage approximately C$70 billion of assets across four continents on behalf of their investment partners. Oxford&#8217;s owned portfolio encompasses office, logistics, retail, multifamily residential, life sciences and hotels; it spans more than 150 million square feet in global gateway cities and high-growth hubs. A thematic investor with a committed source of capital, Oxford invests in properties, portfolios, development sites, debt, securities and real estate businesses across the risk-reward spectrum. Together with its portfolio companies, Oxford is one of the world&#8217;s most active developers with over 100 projects currently underway globally across all major asset classes. Oxford is owned by OMERS, the Canadian defined benefit pension plan for Ontario\'s municipal employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;For more information on Oxford, visit &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="http://www.oxfordproperties.com"&gt;&lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;www.oxfordproperties.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;OMERS is committed to having a workforce that reflects the communities in which we live and work. We are an equal opportunity employer committed to a barrier-free recruitment and selection process. At OMERS inclusion and diversity means belonging. How we create a sense of belonging is through our employees and our vast network of Employee Resource Groups. Whether you are passionate about gender, pride, or visible minorities, we have groups that are focused on making a difference in all of our lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://omers.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/OMERS_External/job/Head-Office-Toronto/Senior-Specialist--Marketing--18-Month-Contract-_JR-1414</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/881085/omers-logo-featured-image.jpg</logo><company>OMERS</company></item><item><title>Business Analyst, Global Investments Technology</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why join us?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Are you looking to join a dynamic pension plan that embodies the strong values of its 500,000 members and is an industry leading global investor? &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;If so, we would love to tell you our story.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;At OMERS we put our people first and are proud to embrace the diversity of thought and leadership that comes from having locations in Toronto, London, New York, Singapore, Sydney and other major cities across North America and Europe. &amp;nbsp;Our culture is truly one of a kind. We get stuff done, and have fun doing it! &amp;nbsp;We take great pride in contributing to the communities where we live with an ever-constant eye to the global investment markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;The Business Analyst, Global Investments Technology (GIT) will join a team that leads the delivery of the products and platforms that enable OMERS Global Investments (GI) to analyze opportunities, action investment decisions and optimize the OMERS investment portfolio. GIT works across investment teams including Capital Markets, Infrastructure, Private Equity, Growth Equity and Ventures, and in close collaboration with Finance, Risk &amp;amp; Compliance teams.&lt;br&gt;As a key member of the GIT team, the Business Analyst is instrumental in improving data &amp;amp; analytics capabilities by championing industry best practices and delivering high quality business requirements to support investment decision making. &lt;br&gt;The Business Analyst will analyze existing systems, as well as document requirements for new systems and new features and cultivate a business relationship that assists in meeting business demands. The individual must also support and collaborate with Power BI developers, data scientists and investment professionals and engage in technical support, research and integration as part of 1 or more product team(s).&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;As a member of this team, you will be responsible for&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;u&gt;:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Technical&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Documenting existing business processes, looking for opportunities to create efficiencies, and ensuring that technical teams understand what to build to automate them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analyzing an existing system&#8217;s functionality, data, and infrastructure, and how the system communicates with other systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding and deriving business value from data: analysing, preparing, formatting, and maintaining information&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identifying and defining detailed product requirements and use cases using various techniques, depending on the types of requirements being documented (e.g. user stories, requirements documents, use case diagrams, data flow diagrams, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Investigating, evaluating and/or proposing solutions (internal, market) to identified problems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chairing design review sessions, ensuring the requirements were accurately captured and are understood by the people that will be working in meeting them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Defining and executing business QA and UAT test plans, performing performance and integration tests and helping automate regression tests&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participating in solution delivery and support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creating and hosting functional training sessions for different applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Organizational&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Operating in a hybrid Agile/Waterfall development environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Communicating effectively with other analysts and various other partners such as product managers, data engineers, IT infrastructure specialists, security specialists, enterprise architects and members of senior management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leading change and communicating impacts to partners and fellow team members&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identifying, defining, and implementing opportunities for improving existing processes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exhibiting the ability to work on multiple projects simultaneously and ensuring timely delivery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Serving as a liaison to the business community&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leading small projects in the role of project manager&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Professional&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Experience&lt;/b&gt;. 5+ years understanding the capabilities in complicated interconnected systems, Financial industry application is preferred. Private Markets application is highly desirable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Functional experience&lt;/b&gt; &amp;nbsp;2+ years in SharePoint, &amp;nbsp;MS Dynamics (or other CRM), eFront (or Investran) and Power BI highly desirable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor&#8217;s Degree in a relevant field of study or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CBAP certification is considered as an asset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Industry Knowledge of&lt;/b&gt; best practices. asking probing questions to understand the reasons for certain requirements, and communicating to technical teams accordingly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Relationship Building&lt;/b&gt;. Consistent track record of building deep business relationships. Experience in aligning expectations across various partners&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Teamwork&lt;/b&gt;. Motivated and keen to work in a collaborative environment with a focus on team success&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Our story:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Founded in 1962, OMERS is one of Canada&#8217;s largest defined benefit pension plans, with $105 billion in net assets as at December 31, 2020. &lt;/span&gt;OMERS is a jointly-sponsored pension plan, with 1,000 participating employers ranging from large cities to local agencies, and over half a million active, deferred and retired members. OMERS members include union and non-union employees of municipalities, school boards, local boards, transit systems, electrical utilities, emergency services and children&#8217;s aid societies across Ontario. Contributions to the Plan are funded equally by members and employers. OMERS teams work in Toronto, London, New York, Amsterdam, Luxembourg, Singapore, Sydney and other major cities across North America and Europe &#8211; serving members and employers and originating and managing a diversified portfolio of high-quality investments in public markets, private equity, infrastructure and real estate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;OMERS is committed to having a workforce that reflects the communities in which we live and work. We are an equal opportunity employer committed to a barrier-free recruitment and selection process. At OMERS inclusion and diversity means belonging. How we create a sense of belonging is through our employees and our vast network of Employee Resource Groups. Whether you are passionate about gender, pride, or visible minorities, we have groups that are focused on making a difference in all of our lives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://omers.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/OMERS_External/job/Head-Office-Toronto/Business-Analyst--Dynamics-365--SharePoint---Global-Investments-Technology_JR-1381</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/881085/omers-logo-featured-image.jpg</logo><company>OMERS</company></item><item><title>Senior Integration Architect</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why join us?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Are you looking to join a dynamic pension plan that embodies the strong values of its 500,000 members and is an industry leading global investor? &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;If so, we would love to tell you our story.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;At OMERS we put our people first and are proud to embrace the diversity of thought and leadership that comes from having locations in Toronto, London, New York, Singapore, Sydney and other major cities across North America and Europe. &amp;nbsp;Our culture is truly one of a kind. We get stuff done, and have fun doing it! &amp;nbsp;We take great pride in contributing to the communities where we live with an ever-constant eye to the global investment markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;We are looking for a highly motivated Integration Architect to join our Technology team in Toronto. In this role, you will create and maintain technical designs and architectural artifacts for the organization&#8217;s Integration Solutions between systems ranging from internal core systems all the way to SaaS products, third party companies and OMERS Partners that would adhere to corporate and industry technical and security best practices. Included in your architectural related activities, you will have exposure to API design, API Management, IPaaS integrations, event layer, data flow, current state and target state architecture.&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You will be leading the Integration capability team from the Data and Analytics team where you will be tasked with supporting key Enterprise Integration systems while guiding OMERS to mature its Integration capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We take great pride in leading the industry by earning respect through every interaction, every day. We go above and beyond to protect and grow relationships by anticipating needs, being honest and considerate, and valuing customers as genuine partners.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a member of this team, you will be responsible for:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding the technology landscape in OMERS to be able to plan, architect, develop and deliver Integration solutions using agile methodology and play your role in moving towards OMERS&#8217; transformation priorities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with the Technical Business Analysts and Product Owners to fully understand solution requirements, identify risks and determine architectural patterns&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creating technical designs that would appropriately address business needs. Including but not limited to, designing/developing system integrations, developing/ implementing business intelligence solutions and implementing customer facing mobile applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creating and maintaining appropriate reference documentation for development teams as per OMERS standards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assisting development teams in developing solutions when required. Including but not limited to coaching, code reviews, troubleshooting integrations, setting up software or hardware during the course of POCs or projects.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leading and developing technical design sessions for facilitation with other members of the team and external vendors&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support and maintain the operations of OMERS Enterprise Integration platforms in coordination with Integration platform vendors and enterprise function teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participating in RFPs for vendor selection and reviewing their products from technical perspective towards selection of the best candidates for OMERS.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensuring technical designs are vetted by Architecture Review Board, aligned with technical-long term strategies and properly integrated all other systems in the organization&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensuring business solutions are developed and maintained in a manner that is conducive to information access security policies and architectural standards and guidelines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Providing guidance and thought leadership on Integrations related decisions to other members of the IT team during the solution development and implementation phases&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keeping current with industry best practices and recommend new patterns, frameworks and technologies when appropriate. Identify opportunities, risks and constraints to enhance the business solution.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;To succeed in this role, you have:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Computer Science background education BSc or higher&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;One or more Azure/GCP/AWS Cloud Architect Certification preferred&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum 7 years of application software development&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum 3 years of solid Integration Architecture background creating Services Layers (both on premise and in Cloud)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum 2 years designing APIs and using API Management software (Google ApigeeX preferred)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum 2 years of experience with any IPaaS platform (Dell &lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;Boomi/Informatica/SnapLogic&lt;/span&gt; preferred)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum 2 years of experience with integration tools (Azure Data Factory, Google Cloud Data Fusion, DataBricks)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience with major Cloud providers&#8217; services (GCP, Azure, AWS)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical, mathematical, and creative problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent listening, interpersonal, written, and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ability to exercise independent judgment and take action on it&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A logical mindset and are efficient, with keen attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ability to effectively prioritize and execute tasks while under pressure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a team-oriented, collaborative environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A desire to keep current with latest trends in technology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High self-motivation and can take initiative&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Agile development methodology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of architectural design patterns&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience building large distributed systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of solution development lifecycle concepts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of IaaS, PaaS and SaaS concepts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;OMERS is committed to having a workforce that reflects the communities in which we live and work. Diversity and Inclusion at OMERS means we respect and value the broadest range of experiences, geographies, gender, ethnicities, and perspectives as key elements of our culture. We are an equal opportunity employer committed to a barrier-free recruitment and selection process. If contacted for an employment opportunity, please advise if you require accommodation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Our story:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Founded in 1962, OMERS is one of Canada&#8217;s largest defined benefit pension plans, with $105 billion in net assets as at December 31, 2020. &lt;/span&gt;OMERS is a jointly-sponsored pension plan, with 1,000 participating employers ranging from large cities to local agencies, and over half a million active, deferred and retired members. OMERS members include union and non-union employees of municipalities, school boards, local boards, transit systems, electrical utilities, emergency services and children&#8217;s aid societies across Ontario. Contributions to the Plan are funded equally by members and employers. OMERS teams work in Toronto, London, New York, Amsterdam, Luxembourg, Singapore, Sydney and other major cities across North America and Europe &#8211; serving members and employers and originating and managing a diversified portfolio of high-quality investments in public markets, private equity, infrastructure and real estate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;OMERS is committed to having a workforce that reflects the communities in which we live and work. We are an equal opportunity employer committed to a barrier-free recruitment and selection process. At OMERS inclusion and diversity means belonging. How we create a sense of belonging is through our employees and our vast network of Employee Resource Groups. Whether you are passionate about gender, pride, or visible minorities, we have groups that are focused on making a difference in all of our lives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://omers.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/OMERS_External/job/Head-Office-Toronto/Integration-Architect_JR-1326</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/881085/omers-logo-featured-image.jpg</logo><company>OMERS</company></item><item><title>General Application</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;section class="section section--no-divider"&gt;      &lt;div class="col-2 "&gt;        &lt;div class="col-2__item wysiwyg-content"&gt;         &lt;div class="authors hide-mobile location-titles"&gt;                                                          &lt;/div&gt;          &lt;p&gt;Don\'t see a role for you? Please complete the form below to share your interest in Borealis AI!&lt;/p&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;                &lt;div class="col-2__item"&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/section&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.borealisai.com/en/careers/employment/5432950002/</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/340845/Borealis_AI_Promo_Vertical_Blue.png</logo><company>Boreails AI</company></item><item><title>Machine Learning Engineering Lead</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;section class="section section--no-divider"&gt;      &lt;div class="col-2 "&gt;        &lt;div class="col-2__item wysiwyg-content"&gt;         &lt;div class="authors hide-mobile location-titles"&gt;                          &lt;div class="careers-location-title"&gt;Available Locations&lt;/div&gt;              &lt;a href="https://www.borealisai.com/en/about/locations/#city_toronto" class="careers-location-name"&gt;                &lt;div&gt;Toronto&lt;/div&gt;              &lt;/a&gt;                                                          &lt;/div&gt;          &lt;h2&gt;What\'s the opportunity?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re looking for an&amp;nbsp;Engineering Manager to lead our Equities Returns Prediction team,&amp;nbsp;being at the forefront of machine learning technology&#8239;and working on extremely challenging problems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Machine Learning Engineering Lead&lt;/strong&gt;, you&#8217;ll be responsible for owning and delivering a project end to end &#8211; everything from data pre-processing to implementing machine learning&amp;nbsp;training pipelines and deploying inference in a production environment. You&#8217;ll be directly managing a team of machine learning engineers, responsible for strategic planning, execution and delivery. You will provide your team with technical leadership and mentorship. You will work along other engineering&#8239;leads&amp;nbsp;across Borealis AI. As a people manager you will be responsible for growing your team and&#8239;fostering career growth of the engineers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Borealis AI, you&#8217;ll be joining a team that works directly with leading researchers in machine learning, has access to rich and massive datasets, and offers the computational resources to support ongoing development in areas such as reinforcement learning, unsupervised learning and computer vision.&amp;nbsp;Each project we take on is like a small start-up, imagine working in a start-up that can immediately impact millions of customers!&amp;nbsp;You can find out more about our&amp;nbsp;work&amp;nbsp;at&#8239;&lt;a href="&amp;quot;http://www.borealisai.com/&amp;quot;" target="&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot;" data-sk="&amp;quot;tooltip_parent&amp;quot;" data-stringify-link="&amp;quot;http://www.borealisai.com&amp;quot;"&gt;www.borealisai.com&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;section class="&amp;quot;section" section--no-divider&amp;quot;=""&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2" col-2--sidebar-left&amp;quot;=""&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2__item&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;ul data-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;" data-stringify-type="&amp;quot;unordered-list&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Lead&amp;nbsp;and directly manage a team of&amp;nbsp;4&amp;nbsp;engineers, being responsible for planning execution and delivery of ML systems;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Establish high standards and share knowledge in performance, scalability, enterprise system architecture, and engineering best practices;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Establish and maintain collaboration with research and business teams to converge on the best solutions;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Extending prototypes into fully functional, polished solutions ready for internal and/or external use;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Grow and develop the team, helping each team member advance in their career.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section class="&amp;quot;section" section--no-divider&amp;quot;=""&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;h2&gt;You\'re our ideal candidate if you:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Have 7+ years&amp;nbsp;of&amp;nbsp;experience&amp;nbsp;delivering software projects to production;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Have experience managing a team of engineers;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Have experience&amp;nbsp;developing&amp;nbsp;modular, robust, scalable software in&amp;nbsp;a&amp;nbsp;modern&amp;nbsp;programming&amp;nbsp;language;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Experience working with business, product and other technical teams;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Experience with scaling and performance of large systems;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Have led the full lifecycle of software product development including the successful deployment of products to production;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Experience taking a leading role in building complex software products, fostering career growth of software engineers, and establishing software engineering best practices within your team;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Have background&amp;nbsp;in&amp;nbsp;machine learning or a related field;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Experience with Capital Markets or any financial domain is a big plus.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s in it for you?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Become part of a team that thinks progressively and works collaboratively. We care about seeing each other reach full potential;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;A comprehensive Total Rewards Program including bonuses and flexible benefits, competitive compensation, commissions, and stock options where applicable;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Leaders who support your development through coaching and managing opportunities;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-stringify-indent="&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;"&gt;Ability to make a difference and lasting impact from a local-to-global scale.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;About Borealis AI&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Borealis AI, a RBC Institute for Research, is a curiosity-driven research centre dedicated to achieving state-of-the-art in machine learning. Established in 2016, and with labs in Toronto, Montreal, Waterloo and Vancouver, we support academic collaborations and partner with world-class research centres in artificial intelligence. With a focus on ethical AI that will help communities thrive, our machine learning scientists perform fundamental and applied research in areas such as reinforcement learning, natural language processing, deep learning, and unsupervised learning to solve ground-breaking problems in diverse fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Inclusion and Equal Opportunity Employment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;RBC is an equal opportunity employer committed to diversity and inclusion. We are pleased to consider all qualified applicants for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, age, disability, protected veterans status, Aboriginal/Native American status or any other legally-protected factors. Disability-related accommodations during the application process are available upon request.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;                &lt;div class="col-2__item"&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/section&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.borealisai.com/en/careers/employment/5022745002/</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/340845/Borealis_AI_Promo_Vertical_Blue.png</logo><company>Boreails AI</company></item><item><title>Machine Learning Researcher</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;section class="section section--no-divider"&gt;      &lt;div class="col-2 "&gt;        &lt;div class="col-2__item wysiwyg-content"&gt;         &lt;div class="authors hide-mobile location-titles"&gt;                                                          &lt;/div&gt;          &lt;section class="&amp;quot;section" section--no-divider&amp;quot;="" data-gtm-vis-first-on-screen-9184414_39="&amp;quot;983&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-total-visible-time-9184414_39="&amp;quot;1100&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-first-on-screen-9184414_40="&amp;quot;1048&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-total-visible-time-9184414_40="&amp;quot;700&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2" col-2--sidebar-left&amp;quot;=""&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2__item&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s the opportunity?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Machine Learning Researcher&lt;/strong&gt;, you&#8217;re looking to channel your love of playing with real-world data into industry-disrupting solutions. We\'re a lab that supports research on a wide variety of theoretical and applied machine learning projects.&amp;nbsp;Working in our lab will grant you unique access to massive structured and unstructured datasets with the tools and resources necessary to build game-changing statistical models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being part of our team means you&#8217;ll also have the opportunity to publish original research in peer-reviewed academic journals and participate in conferences around the world, such as NeurIPS, ICLR, ICML, CVPR and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section class="&amp;quot;section" section--no-divider&amp;quot;="" data-gtm-vis-first-on-screen-9184414_39="&amp;quot;3460&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-total-visible-time-9184414_39="&amp;quot;500&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-first-on-screen-9184414_40="&amp;quot;3543&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-total-visible-time-9184414_40="&amp;quot;300&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2" col-2--sidebar-left&amp;quot;=""&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2__item&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2__item&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developing novel AI solutions that facilitate impactful products;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Conducting original, publishable research by advancing the state-of-the-art in machine learning techniques;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working with the development team to transfer research work into production;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interpreting larger organizational needs and designing algorithmic solutions that can drive the next generation of banking experiences;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identifying relevant new AI technologies as they become available, and disseminating them into the bank&#8217;s technology capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section class="&amp;quot;section" section--no-divider&amp;quot;="" data-gtm-vis-first-on-screen-9184414_39="&amp;quot;3875&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-total-visible-time-9184414_39="&amp;quot;900&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-first-on-screen-9184414_40="&amp;quot;3943&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-total-visible-time-9184414_40="&amp;quot;700&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2" col-2--sidebar-left&amp;quot;=""&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2__item&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;You&#8217;re our ideal candidate if you have:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2__item&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A passion for solving open problems using data and algorithms;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A PhD in a sub-area of AI or demonstrated research track record by means of publications and/or sophisticated AI product experience;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to formulate and drive a research project independently without close supervision;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Python and Deep Learning packages such as Tensorflow or PyTorch.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section class="&amp;quot;section" section--no-divider&amp;quot;="" data-gtm-vis-first-on-screen-9184414_39="&amp;quot;4496&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-total-visible-time-9184414_39="&amp;quot;500&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-first-on-screen-9184414_40="&amp;quot;4529&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-total-visible-time-9184414_40="&amp;quot;400&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2" col-2--sidebar-left&amp;quot;=""&gt;&lt;h2 class="&amp;quot;col-2__item&amp;quot;"&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2__item&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Become part of a team that thinks progressively and works collaboratively. We care about seeing each other reach full potential;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A comprehensive Total Rewards Program including bonuses and flexible benefits, competitive compensation, commissions, and stock options where applicable;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leaders who support your development through coaching and managing opportunities;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to make a difference and lasting impact from a local-to-global scale.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;About Borealis AI&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section class="&amp;quot;section" section--no-divider&amp;quot;="" data-gtm-vis-first-on-screen-9184414_39="&amp;quot;4777&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-total-visible-time-9184414_39="&amp;quot;2300&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-first-on-screen-9184414_40="&amp;quot;4842&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-total-visible-time-9184414_40="&amp;quot;2200&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-polling-id-9184414_39="&amp;quot;126&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-polling-id-9184414_40="&amp;quot;128&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-recent-on-screen-9184414_39="&amp;quot;7612&amp;quot;" data-gtm-vis-recent-on-screen-9184414_40="&amp;quot;7629&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2" col-2--sidebar-left&amp;quot;=""&gt;&lt;div class="&amp;quot;col-2__item&amp;quot;"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Borealis AI, a RBC Institute for Research, is a curiosity-driven research centre dedicated to achieving state-of-the-art in machine learning. Established in 2016, and with labs in Toronto, Montreal, Waterloo and Vancouver, we support academic collaborations and partner with world-class research centres in artificial intelligence. With a focus on ethical AI that will help communities thrive, our machine learning scientists perform fundamental and applied research in areas such as reinforcement learning, natural language processing, deep learning, and unsupervised learning to solve ground-breaking problems in diverse fields.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inclusion and Equal Opportunity Employment&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RBC is an equal opportunity employer committed to diversity and inclusion. We are pleased to consider all qualified applicants for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, age, disability, protected veterans status, Aboriginal/Native American status or any other legally-protected factors. Disability-related accommodations during the application process are available upon request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;                &lt;div class="col-2__item"&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/section&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.borealisai.com/en/careers/employment/5409806002/</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/340845/Borealis_AI_Promo_Vertical_Blue.png</logo><company>Boreails AI</company></item><item><title>Machine Learning Software Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;section class="section section--no-divider"&gt;      &lt;div class="col-2 "&gt;        &lt;div class="col-2__item wysiwyg-content"&gt;         &lt;div class="authors hide-mobile location-titles"&gt;                                                          &lt;/div&gt;          &lt;h2&gt;What\'s the opportunity?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re looking for an enthusiastic software developer who&#8217;s excited by the opportunity of being at the forefront of machine learning technology, and working on extremely challenging problems. As a Machine Learning Software Engineer, you&#8217;ll be responsible for owning and delivering a project end to end &#8211; everything from literature review and data pre-processing to implementing machine learning algorithms and front-end development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Borealis AI, you&#8217;ll be joining a team that works directly with leading researchers in machine learning, has access to rich and massive datasets, and offers the computational resources to support ongoing development in areas such as reinforcement learning, unsupervised learning and computer vision. You can find out more about our research areas at borealisai.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Building machine learning-based software solutions for solving important problems;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prototyping solutions to evaluate the impact of selected algorithms on the target problem;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with research and business teams to converge on the best solutions;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Optimizing algorithms and prototypical solutions for efficient implementation;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extending prototypes into fully functional, polished solutions ready for internal and/or external use;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Supporting projects with thorough documentation of usage, design decisions and capabilities;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extracting, transforming and loading massive datasets using distributed computing framework technologies (Hadoop, Spark, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;You\'re our ideal candidate if you:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A bachelor&#8217;s degree in Computer Science, Software Engineering, or equivalent. &amp;nbsp;A master&#8217;s or PhD in an AI sub-field is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years of software development experience (including co-op and internships) in a high-responsibility, minimal-supervision environment;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with writing modular, robust, scalable software in one of the major languages such as C++, C#, Java, Python 3.x;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the Unix command line and bash scripting;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Deep Learning packages such as Tensorflow, Theano, Keras and PyTorch is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exposure to distributed computing frameworks (e.g. Hadoop, Spark) as well as SQL, NoSQL and graph databases;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in two or more of the following areas: Traditional Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Natural Language Processing, Time-Series Analysis, Computer Vision, Reinforcement Learning;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of professional software engineering best practices for the full software development life cycle, including testing methods, coding standards, code reviews and source control management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s in it for you?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Become part of a team that thinks progressively and works collaboratively. We care about seeing each other reach full potential;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A comprehensive Total Rewards Program including bonuses and flexible benefits, competitive compensation, commissions, and stock options where applicable;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leaders who support your development through coaching and managing opportunities;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to make a difference and lasting impact from a local-to-global scale.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;About Borealis AI&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Borealis AI, a RBC Institute for Research, is a curiosity-driven research centre dedicated to achieving state-of-the-art in machine learning. Established in 2016, and with labs in Toronto, Montreal, Waterloo and Vancouver, we support academic collaborations and partner with world-class research centres in artificial intelligence. With a focus on ethical AI that will help communities thrive, our machine learning scientists perform fundamental and applied research in areas such as reinforcement learning, natural language processing, deep learning, and unsupervised learning to solve ground-breaking problems in diverse fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Inclusion and Equal Opportunity Employment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;RBC is an equal opportunity employer committed to diversity and inclusion. We are pleased to consider all qualified applicants for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, age, disability, protected veterans status, Aboriginal/Native American status or any other legally-protected factors. Disability-related accommodations during the application process are available upon request.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;                &lt;div class="col-2__item"&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/section&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.borealisai.com/en/careers/employment/5022762002/</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/340845/Borealis_AI_Promo_Vertical_Blue.png</logo><company>Boreails AI</company></item><item><title>Research Engineer &#8211; Data Systems</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;section class="section section--no-divider"&gt;      &lt;div class="col-2 "&gt;        &lt;div class="col-2__item wysiwyg-content"&gt;         &lt;div class="authors hide-mobile location-titles"&gt;                                                          &lt;/div&gt;          &lt;h2&gt;Research Engineer &#8211; Data Systems&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Borealis AI is a team of researchers and developers dedicated to solving today&#8217;s leading problems in machine learning and artificial intelligence. Our researchers are dedicated to pushing the boundaries of theoretical and applied science, while our development team transforms state-of-the-art technologies and algorithms into impactful products with the potential to reach millions of people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re looking for an enthusiastic Research Engineer who&#8217;s excited by the opportunity of being at the forefront of machine learning technology, and working on extremely challenging problems. As a Research Engineer, you&#8217;ll be part of a collaborative team delivering AI projects end to end &#8211; everything from data pre-processing and exploration, to prototyping novel algorithmic solutions, to software implementations of machine learning-based products. You will function as a bridge between research and development teams to help extend research prototypes into implemented products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Borealis AI, you&#8217;ll be joining a team that works directly with leading researchers in machine learning, has access to rich and massive datasets, and offers the computational resources to support ongoing development in areas such as reinforcement learning, unsupervised learning and computer vision. You can find out more about our research areas at borealisai.com&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your responsibilities include:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Building data systems to support machine learning-based software solutions;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Conducting comparisons to existing data algorithms and baselines;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reviewing, extending, and optimizing prototype data solutions;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Supporting projects with thorough documentation, design decisions, and capabilities;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with research and business teams to model and deliver on their data needs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;You\'re our ideal candidate if you:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A master&#8217;s or PhD degree in computer science, software engineering, or equivalent, with research experience in data systems;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years of software engineering experience in a high-responsibility, minimal-supervision environment;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with writing modular, robust, scalable software in one of the major languages such as Python 3.x, C++, or Java;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid understanding of distributed computing using CPUs and GPUs;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity to Deep Learning packages such as Tensorflow, Theano, Keras and PyTorch is an asset;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills and a collaborative attitude&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What\'s in it for you?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Become part of a team that thinks progressively and works collaboratively. We care about seeing each other reach full potential;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A comprehensive Total Rewards Program including bonuses and flexible benefits, competitive compensation, commissions, and stock options where applicable;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leaders who support your development through coaching and managing opportunities;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to make a difference and lasting impact from a local-to-global scale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;About Borealis AI&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Borealis AI, a RBC Institute for Research, is a curiosity-driven research centre dedicated to achieving state-of-the-art in machine learning. Established in 2016, and with labs in Toronto, Montreal, Waterloo and Vancouver, we support academic collaborations and partner with world-class research centres in artificial intelligence. With a focus on ethical AI that will help communities thrive, our machine learning scientists perform fundamental and applied research in areas such as reinforcement learning, natural language processing, deep learning, and unsupervised learning to solve ground-breaking problems in diverse fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Inclusion and Equal Opportunity Employment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;RBC is an equal opportunity employer committed to diversity and inclusion. We are pleased to consider all qualified applicants for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, age, disability, protected veterans status, Aboriginal/Native American status or any other legally-protected factors. Disability-related accommodations during the application process are available upon request.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;                &lt;div class="col-2__item"&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/section&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://www.borealisai.com/en/careers/employment/5105845002/</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/340845/Borealis_AI_Promo_Vertical_Blue.png</logo><company>Boreails AI</company></item></items>