<items><item><title>Deep Learning Engineering Intern, Content &amp; Technology - Fall 2021</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WEFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WIJJ WJJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WKE- WCH- WDH- WKC- WME- WPG- WAAB WLE-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are looking for Deep Learning Interns for our Simulation Technology team! Do you have a passion for computer gaming, virtual reality, computer vision, and artificial intelligence?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ever dream about inventing your own holodeck? Do you want to work on leading-edge problems alongside some of the best and brightest people in the world? NVIDIA has continuously reinvented itself over two decades. Our invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More recently, GPU deep learning ignited modern AI &#8212; the next era of computing. NVIDIA is a &#8220;learning machine&#8221; company that constantly evolves by adapting to new opportunities that are hard to solve, that only we can pursue, and that matter to the world. This is our life&#8217;s work, to amplify human creativity and intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You will apply deep learning techniques to the simulation of virtual environments, developing methods to generate synthetic data for training neural networks to achieve results comparable to networks trained on real data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Work on improving realism for agents in synthetic environments &#8211; using reinforcement learning techniques to control behavior and animation of simulated characters, crowds, and vehicles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Conduct research into novel Deep Learning network architectures and techniques for achieving the above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Perform additional development around related technologies as applied to games, VR and visual effects applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What we need to see:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Currently pursuing a PhD, MS, or BS in Computer Science or related field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;1+ year experience with C++/C, CUDA, DirectX, or OpenGL in addition to Python, PyTorch and TensorFlow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Expertise in neural networks, computer graphics, simulation or game development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Dedication to producing high quality and creative results&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ways to stand out from the crowd&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are a great communicator and self-motivated towards team goals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You welcome mentoring others around you&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sharp mathematics skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;NVIDIA is widely considered to be one of the technology world&#8217;s most desirable employers. We have some of the brightest people in the world working for us and, due to unprecedented growth, our elite engineering teams are rapidly growing. If you\'re a creative and autonomous engineer with a real passion for technology, we want to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;#deeplearning&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://nvidia.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/NVIDIAExternalCareerSite/job/Canada-Toronto/Deep-Learning-Engineering-Intern--Content---Technology---Fall-2021_JR1933345-1</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298516/nvidia-logo.jpg</logo><company>NVIDIA</company></item><item><title>Compute Performance Developer Technology Engineer - CUDA</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WEFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WIJJ WJJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WKE- WCH- WDH- WKC- WME- WPG- WAAB WLE-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Compute Performance Developer Technology Engineer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;NVIDIA is hiring passionate, world-class computer scientists to work in its Compute Developer Technology (Devtech) team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;In this role, you will research and develop techniques to GPU-accelerate leading applications in high performance computing fields within scientific computing, computational engineering, and data science. You will be performing in-depth analysis and optimization to ensure the best possible performance on current and next-generation GPU architectures. This involves:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working directly with key application developers to understand the current and future problems they are solving, crafting and optimizing core parallel algorithms and data structures to provide the best solutions using GPUs, through both reference code development and direct contribution to the applications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating closely with diverse groups at NVIDIA such as the architecture, research, libraries, tools, and system software teams to influence the design of next-generation architectures, software platforms, and programming models, by investigating the impact on application performance and developer productivity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will need to travel from time to time for conferences and for on-site visits with developers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What we need to see:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A BS, MS, or PhD degree from a leading university in an engineering or computer science related discipline with 3+ years of relevant experience. While not a requirement, domain expertise in telecommunications, medical imaging, machine learning, deep learning, or natural sciences is helpful.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Programming fluency in C/C++ and/or Fortran with a deep understanding of software design, programming techniques, and algorithms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong mathematical fundamentals, including linear algebra and numerical methods.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with parallel programming, ideally CUDA C/C++ and OpenACC.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and organization skills, with a logical approach to problem solving, good time management, and task prioritization skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;With highly competitive salaries and a comprehensive benefits package, NVIDIA is widely considered to be one of the technology industry\'s most desirable employers. We have some of the most brilliant and talented people in the world working with us and our engineering teams are growing fast in some of the hottest and state of the art fields: Deep Learning, Artificial Intelligence, Autonomous Vehicles, Supercomputing and more. Are you a creative and autonomous computer scientist with a real passion for parallel computing? If so, we want to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;#deeplearning&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://nvidia.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/NVIDIAExternalCareerSite/job/Canada-Toronto/Compute-Performance-Developer-Technology-Engineer---CUDA_JR1926525</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298516/nvidia-logo.jpg</logo><company>NVIDIA</company></item><item><title>Senior Graphics Tools and Pipeline Engineer - DRIVE Sim</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WEFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WIJJ WJJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WKE- WCH- WDH- WKC- WME- WPG- WAAB WLE-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Autonomous vehicles are redefining the way we live, work, and play&#8212;creating safer and more efficient roads. These revolutionary benefits require massive computational horsepower and large-scale production software expertise. Tapping into decades-long experience in high-performance computing, imaging, and AI, NVIDIA has built a software-defined, end-to-end platform for the transportation industry that enables continuous improvement and continuous deployment through over the air updates. It delivers everything needed to develop autonomous vehicles at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Simulation gives us the capability to test an autonomous vehicle in a near-infinite variety of conditions and scenarios before it even reaches the road, accelerating development time and improving the reliability of the self-driving stack at the same time. We&#8217;re looking for a talented Graphics Tools and Pipeline Engineer to join the DRIVE Sim team and help make it all a reality. This meaningful role will see you working with technical visionaries within the company to define and deliver a simulation environment that advances the state of the art in autonomous vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Priorities often change in a fast-paced environment like ours. Some of the things you will work on:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Design and development of asset creation and management tools ranging from exporters, to content creation tools, to asset management tools, and even implement real-time runtime functionality for specific types of content&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Work with content creators, designers, and other specialists to capture requirements and ensure tool design specifications are met&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Work with the design team to architect, engineer, and implement new systems and tools to facilitate the creation of exciting new content&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Directly impact the future of self-driving car technology!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What we need to see:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Bachelor of Science or equivalent experience in Computer Science, Artificial Intelligence, Applied Math, or related field or equivalent work experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;4+ years of experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Solid C++ skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience developing plugins for DCC tools like Maya or Max&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience programming runtime logic for games such as handling animation / camera / state machines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Excellent Python scripting skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Programming with an eye for performance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working with of 3D content toolchains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong mathematical fundamentals, including linear algebra and numerical methods&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ways to stand out from the crowd:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with data-parallel and/or accelerated computing (CUDA, OpenCL)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Background with game engine development&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working with cloud-based services&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Familiarity with an existing game engine with an understanding of game engine and editor concepts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience writing UIs with a toolkit such as wxWidgets, WPF, QT, Slate&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;NVIDIA is widely considered to be one of the technology world&#8217;s most desirable employers. We have some of the most forward-thinking and hardworking people in the world working for us. If you\'re creative and autonomous, we want to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://nvidia.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/NVIDIAExternalCareerSite/job/Canada-Toronto/Senior-Graphics-Tools-and-Pipeline-Engineer_JR1933619</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298516/nvidia-logo.jpg</logo><company>NVIDIA</company></item><item><title>Senior Verification Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WEFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WIJJ WJJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WKE- WCH- WDH- WKC- WME- WPG- WAAB WLE-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are looking for a Senior Verification Engineer for Memory Controllers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;For two decades, we have pioneered visual computing, the art and science of computer graphics. With our invention of the GPU - the engine of modern visual computing - the field has grown to encompass video games, movie production, product design, medical diagnosis and scientific research. Today, we stand at the beginning of the next era, the AI computing era, ignited by a new computing model, GPU deep learning. This new model - where deep neural networks are trained to recognize patterns from massive amounts of data - has shown to be deeply effective at solving the most complex problems in everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a Verification Engineer at NVIDIA, you will verify the design and implementation of our state of the art memory subsystem for our mobile SoCs and GPUs. This position offers the opportunity to have real impact in a dynamic, technology-focused company impacting product lines ranging from consumer graphics to self-driving cars and the growing field of artificial intelligence. We have crafted a team of outstanding people stretching around the globe, whose mission is to push the frontiers of what is possible today and define the platform for the future of computing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you will be doing:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;In this position, you will be responsible for verification of memory subsystem design, architecture, golden models and micro-architecture using advanced verification methodologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As an intermediate to senior member of our verification team, you\'ll understand the design &amp;amp; implementation, define the verification scope, develop the verification infrastructure (Testbenches, BFMs, Checkers, Monitors), execute test/coverage plans, and verify the correctness of the design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Collaborate with architects, designers, emulation and silicon verification teams to accomplish your tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What we need to see:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Bachelors, Master\'s or PhD Degree in a related field (or equivalent experience).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Minimum of 4 years of professional experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience developing TB\'s from scratch using SV and UVM methodology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Background in developing test bench environments for unit level verification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience in verification using random stimulus along with functional coverage and assertion-based verification methodologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Prior Design or Verification experience of dynamic memory controllers (ddr{2, 3, 4}, lpddr{2, &lt;span class="WLK2"&gt;3,4,5},Gddr{5,6},HBM{1,&lt;/span&gt; 2}) and/or high-speed interconnects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong C++ programming experience, scripting ability and experience with System Verilog is highly preferred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Exposure to design and verification tools (VCS or equivalent simulation tools, debug tools like Debussy, GDB).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong debugging, problem solving and analytical skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong communication and interpersonal skills are required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to work in a geographically diverse team environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Self motivated, ability to work independently and drive tasks to completion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;NVIDIA is widely considered to be one of the technology world&#8217;s most desirable employers. We have some of the most forward-thinking and hardworking people in the world working for us. Are you creative and autonomous? Do you love the challenge of crafting the highest performance &amp;amp; lowest power silicon possible? If so, we want to hear from you. Come, join our Memory Subsystem Design Team and help build the real-time, cost-effective computing platform driving our success in this exciting and quickly growing field.&#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://nvidia.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/NVIDIAExternalCareerSite/job/Canada-Toronto/Senior-Verification-Engineer_JR1939923</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298516/nvidia-logo.jpg</logo><company>NVIDIA</company></item></items>