<items><item><title>SOFTWARE ARCHITECT - WAYSIDE</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Toronto, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect solutions that support 85 million mainline and suburban passenger journeys, worldwide, every day. Our Rail Signalling and Communication systems are used on metro lines across major cities, and 72,000 kms of route, 52,000 trains per day in 16 countries are controlled by our Traffic Management Systems. Together We deployed the first-ever nationwide ticketing system which processes over 50 million ticketing transactions in 100 cities daily.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales provides world-leading Communications-Based Train Control (CBTC) and interlocking for mass rail transit applications globally. The Centre of Competence for Urban Rail Signalling is located right before you at mid-town Toronto. As the largest office in Canada, we house a department for every step of the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC)! This includes Software, Hardware, Systems Design, Verification &amp;amp; Validation, Operations, etc. The supporting corporate shared services teams in Finance, Human Resources and IT is also located at the office. Our office space was designed to provide a sustainable, healthy workplace that expresses TRSS&#8217;s brand while increasing collaboration. Features include Greenguard furniture, EnergyStar appliances, low-emitting adhesives, sealants, and sliding glass doors on internal offices provide daylight and views to the outside. Come join the big Transport family, here in Toronto!&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thales Canada Transport Solutions is looking for a Software Architect for our train control systems and more precisely for Wayside Software. The successful candidate will be responsible for the software architecture and its consistency with the solution/system architecture, the Architect coordinates with the Solution Architect and PDA in order to make sure that the top down refinement of the solution is consistent with the software strategy and constraints including COTS &amp;amp; OSS selection and components reuse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensures that software architecture stability is maintained across lifecycle phases from Bid to Delivery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Directs and coordinates software architecture studies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approves the technical, technological, and methodological choices taken in respect of the selected software architecture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guarantees adherence to in-scope standards, reuse policy and product development plans&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identifies modelling, simulation and prototyping opportunities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Co-ordinates product definition and assessment of trade-offs between aspects of cost, customer requirements and technological possibilities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prepares the Design &amp;amp; Justification Files&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provides knowledge on state-of-the-art software architecture, taking into account the impact of future developments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monitors technological developments&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Respects the established deadlines, costs and performances for the different projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mandatory Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;University degree in Computer or Software Engineering&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum of 7 years of experience with embedded critical software development&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fluent oral and written communication skills in English&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expert knowledge of modern software engineering practices, methods and tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good programming expertise (C, Ada, Assembly, Python, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of railway signaling techniques an asset&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In-depth knowledge of SELTRAC product&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Development experience in C&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expert knowledge of SELTRAC signaling system and software architecture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/toronto/software-architect-wayside/1766/9272756592</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>SENIOR MANAGER, CHIEF SOFTWARE ARCHITECT</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Toronto, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect solutions that support 85 million mainline and suburban passenger journeys, worldwide, every day. Our Rail Signalling and Communication systems are used on metro lines across major cities, and 72,000 kms of route, 52,000 trains per day in 16 countries are controlled by our Traffic Management Systems. Together We deployed the first-ever nationwide ticketing system which processes over 50 million ticketing transactions in 100 cities daily.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales provides world-leading Communications-Based Train Control (CBTC) and interlocking for mass rail transit applications globally. The Centre of Competence for Urban Rail Signalling is located right before you at mid-town Toronto. As the largest office in Canada, we house a department for every step of the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC)! This includes Software, Hardware, Systems Design, Verification &amp;amp; Validation, Operations, etc. The supporting corporate shared services teams in Finance, Human Resources and IT is also located at the office. Our office space was designed to provide a sustainable, healthy workplace that expresses TRSS&#8217;s brand while increasing collaboration. Features include Greenguard furniture, EnergyStar appliances, low-emitting adhesives, sealants, and sliding glass doors on internal offices provide daylight and views to the outside. Come join the big Transport family, here in Toronto!&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Chief Software Architect Manager&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; to lead the team of Chief Software Architects and foster the community of the Software Architects. The successful candidate will be responsible for the Design and Architecture of the software developed at Thales Canada Transportation Solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will have the Chief Software Architects of each subsystem (wayside, onboard, supervision) as direct reports&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are responsible for this team in terms of hiring, training, mentoring, objective setting and performance evaluation, support in problem solving, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the &lt;span&gt;Chief Software Architect Manager&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;you will lead and foster the community of the Software Architects: detecting the talent, developing the skills, developing knowledge sharing, detecting and developing the new ideas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are ultimately responsible for the Design and Architecture of the software which is developed at TCTS (Thales Canada Transportation Solutions): Definition of the design drivers, architecture patterns; conduct and supervise the architecture trade-off; Definition of the software roadmap and product policy; Providing guidance and review of the developments, foster co-engineering with the other disciplines; Promoting cost effective design while contributing to cost estimates and bid estimates; Ensuring compliance to the standards; Instrumental in the definition and implementation of the process, practices and tools; Lastly staying in tune with Thales Group technical strategy and finding opportunities for collaboration with other Thales business units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Staying abreast of current software architecture trends and working with the software architect community to determine their applicability to TCTS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;University degree in Computer Science, Engineering, or closely related field&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over 15 years of relevant working experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expertise with Software Architecture; Software development process and Development of mission-critical and/or safety critical software and embedded software for complex systems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in the railway domain is a plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leading and developing a community&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leading transformation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/toronto/senior-manager-chief-software-architect/1766/11655390624</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>TECHNICAL SPECIALIST - SOFTWARE</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Toronto, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect solutions that support 85 million mainline and suburban passenger journeys, worldwide, every day. Our Rail Signalling and Communication systems are used on metro lines across major cities, and 72,000 kms of route, 52,000 trains per day in 16 countries are controlled by our Traffic Management Systems. Together We deployed the first-ever nationwide ticketing system which processes over 50 million ticketing transactions in 100 cities daily.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales provides world-leading Communications-Based Train Control (CBTC) and interlocking for mass rail transit applications globally. The Centre of Competence for Urban Rail Signalling is located right before you at mid-town Toronto. As the largest office in Canada, we house a department for every step of the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC)! This includes Software, Hardware, Systems Design, Verification &amp;amp; Validation, Operations, etc. The supporting corporate shared services teams in Finance, Human Resources and IT is also located at the office. Our office space was designed to provide a sustainable, healthy workplace that expresses TRSS&#8217;s brand while increasing collaboration. Features include Greenguard furniture, EnergyStar appliances, low-emitting adhesives, sealants, and sliding glass doors on internal offices provide daylight and views to the outside. Come join the big Transport family, here in Toronto!&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a Technical Specialist. S/he will design, create, analyze, debug and deliver software for train control systems of Thales Rail Signaling Solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understand and follow the company&#8217;s processes and procedures for developing mission critical software&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Develop near real time systems in C++&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design, code, debug, write test procedures and tests software code&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Review code, test procedures and test results&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyze and implement correction for complex defect reports&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perform engineering testing in the field and investigates problems in the field&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provide input for cost estimates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provide on the job training and formal training to staff&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provide input to manage and evaluate employee&#8217;s performance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have an excellent understanding current product and contributes to extend the current product architecture and design&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technical mentoring&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep abreast of new technology developments and help to evaluate new products and processes to improve current software development&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bachelor\'s degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Science or equivalent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum of 7&amp;nbsp; years relevant working experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent command of C++ language including templates, STL, Boost, MFC usage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiar with C#, WPF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent&amp;nbsp; command of the scripting languages Ruby, Perl and Python&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiar with software building tools like gmake, MSBuild&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiar with unit testing and continuous integration frameworks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiar with Angular web development including Typescript, WebSockets, Reactive X&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiar with source control tools (Git, Clearcase, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledgeable of object oriented techniques, design patterns, multithreading, socket programming, Windows&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good analytical skills, able to diagnose issues based on field logs and correlate events to failures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familiar with agile work environments, test-driven development and continuous integration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working knowledge of modern software engineering practices, methods and tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent team collaboration skills, writing and verbal skills, people supervision skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong technical writing and communication skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with large mission-critical and multi-platform heterogeneous systems is desirable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/toronto/technical-specialist-software/1766/10804394352</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>TECHNICAL CYBERSECURITY CONSULTANT</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Ottawa, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect identity management and data protection solutions at the heart of digital security. Business and governments rely on us to bring trust to the billons of digital interactions they have with people. Our technologies and services help banks exchange funds, people cross borders, energy become smarter and much more. More than 30,000 organizations already rely on us to verify the identities of people and things, grant access to digital services, analyze vast quantities of information and encrypt data to make the connected world more secure.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Professional &lt;b&gt;Services Technical Consultant&lt;/b&gt; located in &lt;b&gt;Ottawa Canada&lt;/b&gt; will be responsible for implementing Thales data protection solutions in customer enterprise environments. This is a highly technical role with extensive customer facing responsibilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ideal candidate must be self-motivated and comfortable in the dynamic atmosphere of a technical organization with a rapidly expanding customer base and new products.&amp;nbsp; Service oriented. Business driven. Candidate must be organized and analytical, adept at working in a team environment and able to handle multiple priorities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The professional Services consultant main functions and responsibilities will include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assisting engagement specialist to scope complex Thales products&#8217; deployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Set up conference calls with customers to review deployment plans, pre-requisites and best practices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provide onsite or remote consulting services and support to Thales customer with a focus on high quality, accuracy and customer satisfaction&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Record project activities in the department project management application&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Develop and deliver technical hands-on product deep knowledge transfer to customers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Track and ensure successful completion of high impact projects by creating project scoping plans, design guides and relevant documentation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Function as technical point of contact for customer deployments and as a mentor for other team members&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Delivery of customer engagement in the area of Public Key Infrastructure (PKI)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design &#8211; Role, Policies and Procedures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Documentation and hands on deployment including hardware security modules&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provide training and knowledge transfer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design, deploy and document of Microsoft Enterprise Certificate Authorities. Certificates including installing, renewing, and revoking certificates in a variety of different locations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advice customer on best Active Directory (AD) practices on tasks related to PKI deployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design, deploy and document Hardware Secure Modules (HSM)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perform HSM integration with various databases. i.e. Oracle, MS SQL, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provide strong product and professional services solution presentation to difference audiences, internal and external.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Education:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;B.A./B.S. degree required (preferably Computer Science, Information Services or a related field).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Experience:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;5+ years of experience in software security consulting, customer facing as a consultant, trainer or sales engineer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2+ years of experience in Enterprise PKI Engineering&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2+ years of encryption, key management and hardware security modules (HSM) experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience in onsite and remote projects delivery model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ability to travel up to 60%; Ability to work under stress and managing tight deadlines, changing work environment and ability to be adaptable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;File Encryption - Full file and column/delimited a plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Network and storage encryption a plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with any of the following programing languages a plus. Java, .NET, C++&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solid background in cryptography and experience in networking and network security protocols&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Relevant security or professional certifications are beneficial; CISM, CISA, CISSP, ITIL v3, PMP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong ability to document requirements and to write technical response papers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cloud Certifications: AWS, Azure, Google Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of Thales Data Protection Products (HSMs, KeySecure, CipherTrust)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solid knowledge of information security principles and practices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/ottawa/technical-cybersecurity-consultant/1766/10685194560</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>SENIOR SOFTWARE ANALYST</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Toronto, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect solutions that support 85 million mainline and suburban passenger journeys, worldwide, every day. Our Rail Signalling and Communication systems are used on metro lines across major cities, and 72,000 kms of route, 52,000 trains per day in 16 countries are controlled by our Traffic Management Systems. Together We deployed the first-ever nationwide ticketing system which processes over 50 million ticketing transactions in 100 cities daily.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales provides world-leading Communications-Based Train Control (CBTC) and interlocking for mass rail transit applications globally. The Centre of Competence for Urban Rail Signalling is located right before you at mid-town Toronto. As the largest office in Canada, we house a department for every step of the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC)! This includes Software, Hardware, Systems Design, Verification &amp;amp; Validation, Operations, etc. The supporting corporate shared services teams in Finance, Human Resources and IT is also located at the office. Our office space was designed to provide a sustainable, healthy workplace that expresses TRSS&#8217;s brand while increasing collaboration. Features include Greenguard furniture, EnergyStar appliances, low-emitting adhesives, sealants, and sliding glass doors on internal offices provide daylight and views to the outside. Come join the big Transport family, here in Toronto!&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a Senior Software Analyst to provide design, analysis, programming, testing, review, and support for the development of software simulations and other tools for train control systems of Thales Canada Transportation Solutions. You will also plan and direct work within the software team and provide technical guidance to other analysts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understands and follows the company&#8217;s processes and procedures for developing vital software&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Implements real time systems mainly in C and C++&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Produce software requirements analysis, designs, codes, debugs, write test procedures and test software code&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reviews software requirements analysis, designs, code, test procedures and test results&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chairs design reviews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyses situations, implements corrections, and reviews defect reports&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Performs engineering testing and investigates problems in the field&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provides input for cost estimates and bid estimates&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Provides on the job training of staff&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assists with providing leadership and motivation to staff&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prepares reports and gives findings on problems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prepares and implements low level plans, schedules and budgets for software projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;B.Sc. Electrical Engineering, Computer Science or equivalent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 5 years of relevant working experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of software development environment (desktop simulator, target simulator, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of the full software development life cycle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of software architectures and design patterns&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with object-oriented programming and C++&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with communication technologies and development&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with multithreaded and real time application development&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with software debugging and application profiling and troubleshooting&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with modelling information, objects and events into software&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with source control tools, integrated development environments (IDEs), requirement management tools, problem tracking tools&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of railway signaling techniques&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Company product knowledge (SELTRAC - if new hire, to be trained)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of vehicular systems and simulations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experience with automation and platform integration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/toronto/senior-software-analyst/1766/10732194080</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>SENIOR DEVELOPMENT ENGINEER</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Ottawa, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect identity management and data protection solutions at the heart of digital security. Business and governments rely on us to bring trust to the billons of digital interactions they have with people. Our technologies and services help banks exchange funds, people cross borders, energy become smarter and much more. More than 30,000 organizations already rely on us to verify the identities of people and things, grant access to digital services, analyze vast quantities of information and encrypt data to make the connected world more secure.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At our Thales Ottawa office, we develop leading edge technologies for a cloud solution to provide digital cryptographic service. Our cloud-based Data Protection on Demand service is prevalent in today\'s digital security world. An intermediate to Senior Developer is to join our software engineering team focused on high profile software and embedded/firmware development and deliveries for a cloud service. We are looking for a talented &lt;b&gt;Senior&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;Development Engineer. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must be able to develop and deliver software and firmware according to pre-defined priorities and timelines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apply security best practices for firmware design, coding and testing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apply software engineering best practices to code, debug and review created software&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Responsible for using various 3rd party software/tool components in a cloud-based, digital security and cryptography solution&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with other team members to share knowledge and improve design/code quality and maintainability&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Follow SAFe development process, this includes attending planning sessions, design estimates, daily standups and retrospectives&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;As needed, participate in support effort for resolving customer issues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;As needed, interact with teams on other geo-sites and time zones&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep management and scrum teams timely updated with the development status and issues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep up-to-date with, and promote the use of, the latest technology, trends, tools and best practices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Required Skills and Experience:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 3 years&#8217; coding experience in C/C++ development with a focus on multi-threaded software system and embedded firmware. Good knowledge of Python and shell scripting is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of RESTful API and Linux/Windows operating systems is required&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of Cassandra database, PKCS #11, Docker as well as load balancers is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 2 years&#8217; experience delivering software in an Agile/SAFe/Scrum development environment: designing and implementing the feature; design testing a solution; developing automated functional tests and unit tests; continuous integration/delivery; drafting the information needed in customer documentation; and addressing bugs and improvements. As such, working knowledge of JIRA, GIT and Jenkins is required.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A good attitude and demonstrated ability to produce effectively in a dynamic, fast pace team environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;University or college undergraduate, or higher, degree in Computer science or Software Engineering.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This position requires direct or indirect access to hardware, software, technology or technical data controlled under the Canadian Export Control List and/or the US the Export Administration Regulations (EAR). All applicants must be eligible, or able to obtain authorization, for such access.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Preferred Skills and Experience&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Digital security, PKCS11 cryptography and noSQL database (e.g. Cassandra) background is strongly preferred.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is committed to a diverse and inclusive workplace for all.  Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/ottawa/senior-development-engineer/1766/9272830016</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item><item><title>SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Ottawa, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect identity management and data protection solutions at the heart of digital security. Business and governments rely on us to bring trust to the billons of digital interactions they have with people. Our technologies and services help banks exchange funds, people cross borders, energy become smarter and much more. More than 30,000 organizations already rely on us to verify the identities of people and things, grant access to digital services, analyze vast quantities of information and encrypt data to make the connected world more secure.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a member of a collaborative development team, the Senior Software Developer will be instrumental in the design, development, and deployment of components comprising an innovative cloud based and on premise Identity and Access Management solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Senior Software Developer will demonstrate leadership and creative problem solving abilities, and will work closely with architects, product management, platform and operations teams to ensure timely delivery of valuable, quality components and solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with team members and stakeholders to identify, refine, estimate, plan and prioritize the development and deployment of innovative features and components.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop software with performance, scalability, security, testability, maintainability, deployment and end-user experience in mind.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apply software development principles, design patterns and best practices to produce elegant, high quality code.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Review, maintain, refactor and improve upon existing software components.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep up with industry trends, technologies and security practices.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot and fix customer reported issues.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop, maintain and extend Continuous Integration / Continuous Delivery systems.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate leadership, professionalism and maturity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mentor, support and coach junior developers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regularly share knowledge within and across teams via code reviews, documentation, and presentations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participate in the validation and deployment of components in various environments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use collaboration tools like Jira, Confluence, and Teams to coordinate development efforts across geographical regions (USA, Canada, India)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apply source control good practices and workflows for branching, committing, reviewing and merging code changes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participate in and promote good Agile practices and processes within and across teams (Scrum, SAFe)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Required Skills a Experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;BSc in Computer Science, Engineering or relevant field&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience with .NET programming languages and tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience developing secure, performant web services and applications (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REST)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience developing, automating, and analyzing results of unit, integration and performance tests&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience using Git or comparable source control strategies and workflows&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience with Agile principles, frameworks and processes (Scrum / SAFe / XP)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience using and/or developing CI/CD systems (Jenkins, GitLab CI/CD)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of database design, performance optimization&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of common OOP Design Patterns and SOLID principles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience sharing knowledge via code reviews, documentation, presentations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience mentoring / supporting / coaching junior developers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to learn quickly and work autonomously and as part of a team&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with container development, deployment, and orchestration (Docker / Kubernetes / YAML / Helm / Ansible)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with development of solutions involving AuthN, AuthZ, Identity &amp;amp; Access Management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scrum / SAFe / Agile certification&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with cloud development and deployment (AWS / GCP)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding of performance testing, analysis and improvement of software components&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Logging, monitoring and alerting using tools such as FluentD and DataDog&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with using JIRA and Confluence for collaboration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Full Stack development experience using Angular / Node.js&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with static analysis / code coverage / security analysis tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Occasional flexibility to work outside of normal business hours to resolve production issues and/or collaborate with remote teams.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Object-Relational Mapping frameworks like Entity Framework&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with a variety of programming and scripting languages (Java, C#, C++, Lua, Bash, Groovy, etc)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is committed to a diverse and inclusive workplace for all.  Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/ottawa/senior-software-developer/1766/9272764720</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item></items>