<items><item><title>Senior Data Analyst, Global Investments</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WFFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WHJJ WIJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WME- WEH- WFH- WMC- WOE- WBH- WAAB WNE-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why join us?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Are you looking to join a dynamic pension plan that embodies the strong values of its 500,000 members and is an industry leading global investor? &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;If so, we would love to tell you our story.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;At OMERS we put our people first and are proud to embrace the diversity of thought and leadership that comes from having locations in Toronto, London, New York, Singapore, Sydney and other major cities across North America and Europe. &amp;nbsp;Our culture is truly one of a kind. We get stuff done, and have fun doing it! &amp;nbsp;We take great pride in contributing to the communities where we live with an ever-constant eye to the global investment markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;The Senior Data Analyst, Global Investments Technology (GIT) will join a team that leads the delivery of the products and platforms that enable OMERS Global Investments (GI) to analyze opportunities, action investment decisions and optimize the OMERS investment portfolio. GIT works across investment teams including Capital Markets, Infrastructure, Private Equity, Growth Equity and Ventures, and in close collaboration with Finance, Risk &amp;amp; Compliance teams.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a key member of the Global Investments Technology team, the Senior Data Analyst is instrumental in enhancing data &amp;amp; analytics capabilities by championing industry best practices and delivering high quality datasets, reports, and training to enhance business decision making.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senior Data Analyst will develop Power BI datasets and reports to support OMERS investment entities, maintain a healthy business relationship to assist in meeting business demands and deliver training workshops to promote a data culture. The Senior Data Analyst will also support and collaborate with data engineers, data scientists and investment professionals and engage in technical support, research and knowledge sharing through the implementation as part of 1 or more product team(s).&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;As a member of this team, you will be responsible for:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Technical&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Organizing workshops with partners to gather requirements and develop low/high fidelity wireframes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developing and monitoring Power BI Premium Dataflows to gather, transform and democratize structured and unstructured data assets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developing Power BI datasets by applying best-practice semantic modeling techniques&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Building visually stunning reports that clearly communicate an effective story&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leading solution build, delivery, support and troubleshooting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provisioning and managing resources of Premium Capacity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Managing the Power BI / Power Platform infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Usage Monitoring and Auditing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Organizational&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Operating in an Agile development environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Communicating effectively with analysts and various partners across multiple teams and with various other partners such as product managers, data engineers and members of senior management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Managing change and communicating impacts to partners and fellow team members&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Facilitating collaboration and sharing through best practices of delivering and sharing content&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identifying, defining and implementing opportunities for improving existing processes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exhibiting the ability to work on multiple projects simultaneously and ensuring timely delivery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leading the Power BI Community of Interest to review the latest features and updates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with other teams and establishing Power Platform Governance and Support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;To succeed in this role, you have:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Professional&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Experience&lt;/b&gt;. 5+ years solving complex technical projects as a full-stack (M &amp;amp; DAX) Power BI developer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor&#8217;s Degree in a scientific or engineering field of study or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft certification &#8211; Data Analyst Associate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Industry Knowledge &lt;/b&gt;of best practices learned from MVP &amp;amp; Product Team articles and Investments/Finance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Training&lt;/b&gt;. Excited to support new Power BI users by running various internal community initiatives such as presentations, hands-on workshops, or troubleshooting end-user obstacles.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated success &lt;b&gt;building deep technical relationships&lt;/b&gt; and aligning expectations across various partners.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Problem&lt;/b&gt;-&lt;b&gt;Solving.&lt;/b&gt; The ability to trace data lineage and resolve technical issues with minimal direction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Teamwork&lt;/b&gt;. Motivated and keen to work in a collaborative environment with a focus on team success.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Technical&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A depth of Power BI experience wrangling complex data using M functions and developing sophisticated semantic logic using DAX expressions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Connect/Transform. &lt;/b&gt;Knows what &#8220;M&#8221; is, how to merge, append, and perform more advanced UI transforms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Model. &lt;/b&gt;Basic knowledge of dimension / fact tables and can identify them in a dimensional model. Comfortable with simple DAX, knows the CALCULATE function well and can explain how it works.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Visualization.&lt;/b&gt; &amp;nbsp;Recommends appropriate visualizations to answer business questions and references examples of published materials that explain how to choose a visual. Proficient at all ways to manipulate look &amp;amp; feel.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Admin/Architecture&lt;/b&gt;. Has experience configuring Administrative features in the tenant. Knows how to install and manage a gateway. Basic levels of understanding of licensing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Embed/Custom Visuals&lt;/b&gt;. Understand that Power BI can be embedded internally and knows how to add and share in Teams.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Breadth of technical experience and knowledge in the MSFT data and analytics ecosystem, with Subject Matter Expertise in two or more of the following items:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Power BI Service administration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Power BI Desktop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tabular Editor and DAX Studio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Azure Synapse Analytics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Azure Data Factory&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Azure Machine Learning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Azure Databricks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Our story:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Founded in 1962, OMERS is one of Canada&#8217;s largest defined benefit pension plans, with $105 billion in net assets as at December 31, 2020. &lt;/span&gt;OMERS is a jointly-sponsored pension plan, with 1,000 participating employers ranging from large cities to local agencies, and over half a million active, deferred and retired members. OMERS members include union and non-union employees of municipalities, school boards, local boards, transit systems, electrical utilities, emergency services and children&#8217;s aid societies across Ontario. Contributions to the Plan are funded equally by members and employers. OMERS teams work in Toronto, London, New York, Amsterdam, Luxembourg, Singapore, Sydney and other major cities across North America and Europe &#8211; serving members and employers and originating and managing a diversified portfolio of high-quality investments in public markets, private equity, infrastructure and real estate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;OMERS is committed to having a workforce that reflects the communities in which we live and work. We are an equal opportunity employer committed to a barrier-free recruitment and selection process. At OMERS inclusion and diversity means belonging. How we create a sense of belonging is through our employees and our vast network of Employee Resource Groups. Whether you are passionate about gender, pride, or visible minorities, we have groups that are focused on making a difference in all of our lives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://omers.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/OMERS_External/job/Head-Office-Toronto/Senior-Data-Analyst--Global-Investments_JR-1336</url><logo>https://images.ctfassets.net/iifcbkds7nke/6GDE2X9ZAuqppSxbjWDr4F/2e2d71191ef56450d79fafa5b1946b1e/omers-logo-colour.svg</logo><company>OMERS</company></item><item><title>Business Analyst (Dynamics 365, SharePoint), Global Investments Technology</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WFFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WHJJ WIJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WME- WEH- WFH- WMC- WOE- WBH- WAAB WNE-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Why join us?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h1&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Are you looking to join a dynamic pension plan that embodies the strong values of its 500,000 members and is an industry leading global investor? &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;If so, we would love to tell you our story.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;At OMERS we put our people first and are proud to embrace the diversity of thought and leadership that comes from having locations in Toronto, London, New York, Singapore, Sydney and other major cities across North America and Europe. &amp;nbsp;Our culture is truly one of a kind. We get stuff done, and have fun doing it! &amp;nbsp;We take great pride in contributing to the communities where we live with an ever-constant eye to the global investment markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;The Business Analyst, Global Investments Technology (GIT) will join a team that leads the delivery of the products and platforms that enable OMERS Global Investments (GI) to analyze opportunities, action investment decisions and optimize the OMERS investment portfolio. GIT works across investment teams including Capital Markets, Infrastructure, Private Equity, Growth Equity and Ventures, and in close collaboration with Finance, Risk &amp;amp; Compliance teams.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a key member of the GIT team, the Business Analyst is instrumental in improving data &amp;amp; analytics capabilities by championing industry best practices and delivering high quality business requirements to support investment decision making.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Business Analyst will analyze existing systems, as well as document requirements for new systems and new features and cultivate a business relationship that assists in meeting business demands. The individual must also support and collaborate with Power BI developers, data scientists and investment professionals and engage in technical support, research and integration as part of 1 or more product team(s).&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;As a member of this team, you will be responsible for&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;u&gt;:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Technical&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Documenting existing business processes, looking for opportunities to create efficiencies, and ensuring that technical teams understand what to build to automate them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analyzing an existing system&#8217;s functionality, data, and infrastructure, and how the system communicates with other systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding and deriving business value from data: analysing, preparing, formatting, and maintaining information&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identifying and defining detailed product requirements and use cases using various techniques, depending on the types of requirements being documented (e.g. user stories, requirements documents, use case diagrams, data flow diagrams, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Investigating, evaluating and/or proposing solutions (internal, market) to identified problems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chairing design review sessions, ensuring the requirements were accurately captured and are understood by the people that will be working in meeting them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Defining and executing business &amp;nbsp;QA and UAT test plans, performing performance and integration tests and helping automate regression tests&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participating in solution delivery and support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creating and hosting functional training sessions for different applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Organizational&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Operating in a hybrid Agile/Waterfall development environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Communicating effectively with other analysts and various other partners such as product managers, data engineers, IT infrastructure specialists, security specialists, enterprise architects and members of senior management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leading change and communicating impacts to partners and fellow team members&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identifying, defining, and implementing opportunities for improving existing processes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exhibiting the ability to work on multiple projects simultaneously and ensuring timely delivery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Serving as a liaison to the business community&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leading small projects in the role of project manager&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;To succeed in this role, you have the following qualifications:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Experience&lt;/b&gt;. 5+ years understanding the capabilities in complicated interconnected systems, Financial industry application is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Functional experience:&lt;/b&gt; 2+ years in SharePoint, &amp;nbsp;MS Dynamics and Power BI&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Bachelor&#8217;s Degree in a relevant field of study or equivalent work experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CBAP certification is considered as an asset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Industry Knowledge of&lt;/b&gt; best practices. asking probing questions to understand the reasons for certain requirements, and communicating to technical teams accordingly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Relationship Building&lt;/b&gt;. Consistent track record of building deep business relationships. Experience in aligning expectations across various partners&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Teamwork&lt;/b&gt;. Motivated and keen to work in a collaborative environment with a focus on team success&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Our story:&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Founded in 1962, OMERS is one of Canada&#8217;s largest defined benefit pension plans, with $105 billion in net assets as at December 31, 2020. &lt;/span&gt;OMERS is a jointly-sponsored pension plan, with 1,000 participating employers ranging from large cities to local agencies, and over half a million active, deferred and retired members. OMERS members include union and non-union employees of municipalities, school boards, local boards, transit systems, electrical utilities, emergency services and children&#8217;s aid societies across Ontario. Contributions to the Plan are funded equally by members and employers. OMERS teams work in Toronto, London, New York, Amsterdam, Luxembourg, Singapore, Sydney and other major cities across North America and Europe &#8211; serving members and employers and originating and managing a diversified portfolio of high-quality investments in public markets, private equity, infrastructure and real estate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;OMERS is committed to having a workforce that reflects the communities in which we live and work. We are an equal opportunity employer committed to a barrier-free recruitment and selection process. At OMERS inclusion and diversity means belonging. How we create a sense of belonging is through our employees and our vast network of Employee Resource Groups. Whether you are passionate about gender, pride, or visible minorities, we have groups that are focused on making a difference in all of our lives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://omers.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/OMERS_External/job/Head-Office-Toronto/Business-Analyst--Dynamics-365--SharePoint---Global-Investments-Technology_JR-1381</url><logo>https://images.ctfassets.net/iifcbkds7nke/6GDE2X9ZAuqppSxbjWDr4F/2e2d71191ef56450d79fafa5b1946b1e/omers-logo-colour.svg</logo><company>OMERS</company></item></items>