<items><item><title>Data Scientist</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid12-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid12-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-13" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Data Analytics Engineering team is looking to bring a new Data Scientist on board. You will help build end-to-end applications and processes for the business community leveraging AI, ML, Big Data and Cloud Infrastructure, and provide support to the Sun Life Data Science community. Our projects feature innovative yet practical approaches to deliver the best service in Advanced Analytics support across Sun Life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you do? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop data science analytic approaches such as machine learning, deep learning, and natural language programming&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assist with the development of compelling and effective data visualizations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop interactive dashboards, reports and data visualizations allowing the end-user to explore data and discover insights independently&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lead the design, development and implementation of prototypes and proof of concepts for data, analytic and predictive models, research products and analysis platforms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apply Software Engineering and application development skills to build robust, scalable and cost -effective Data Science applications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work directly with a wide array of audiences to structure analytical problems and approaches&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Communicate complex results to a business audience not familiar with complex Data and Analytics solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you will need to succeed:&amp;nbsp; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;Graduate/Postgraduate&lt;/span&gt; degrees in quantitative sciences (such as Computer Science, Statistics, Mathematics, Physics, Bioinformatics, Data Science&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+2 years experience in Programming language such as R, Python&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+2 years experience in Linux and scripting languages (Bash, PowerShell)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+2 years experience in Statistical analysis, deep understanding of its concepts and applications, such as hypothesis generation and testing, various kind of statistical distributions, power analysis, probability theory, dimensional reduction, cluster analysis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+2 years experience in Building and deploying predictive models, such as GLM, Decision Tree, XGBoost, Support Vector Machine, Bayesian inference&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+2 years experience in Working with deep machine learning framework such as Tensorflow, PyTorch and their applications in anomaly detection, image recognition, natural language processing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+2 years experience with SQL databases&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+2 years experience in High competency in version control tools such as Git in a collaborative coding environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+1 year experience with SageMaker and its features: training, processing, hyper parameter tuning, model monitoring&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+1 year Working experience in container technology such as Docker, Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+1 year Experience and/or training in Cloud platforms like AWS&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+1 year experience with optimising code in execution speed and memory consumption&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;+1 year experience with Machine learning framework such as Tensorflow, PyTorch&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nice to have:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Common statistical packages such as Numpy, Pandas, Scipy, Data.Table, Matplotlib, ggplot, Dyprb&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;GLM, Decision Tree, XGBoost, Support Vector Machine, Bayesian inference&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Data Visualization tools like Tableau, Python Dash, Seaborn, Matplotlib, R Shiny (desirable)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience or training in delivering IT or Analytics projects in an iterative agile like team structure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with noSQL databases DynamoDB, MongoDB, etc&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in Life Insurance, Wealth Management, or other financial services industry&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in large scale MLOps&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in languages such as SAS, Java, JavaScript, VBA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in big data technology such as Hadoop, Spark, Glue, Kafka&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Special requirements:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must be able to attain Canadian Reliability Security Clearance (administered by submitting fingerprints to the RCMP, a minimum of 5 years history checks).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;73,800/73 800 - 124,100/124 100&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;IT - Technology Services&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;01/10/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Data-Scientist_JR00047061?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Role Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Within Sun Life Canada, the Canadian Analytics Centre of Excellence (COE) was launched to support Canadian business units in their journey to leverage data and analytics as a foundational pillar in delivering business value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Reporting to the&lt;b&gt; Director, Analytics Consulting Services&lt;/b&gt; as a &lt;b&gt;Senior Data Scientist&lt;/b&gt; you will focus on supporting Canadian business units in accelerating the growth and application of analytics in driving value. &amp;nbsp;The senior data scientist will leverage practical experience in applying varied data science techniques &amp;amp; offering advice/inputs to help with the design, development and implementation of analytics use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sun Life views success in this role in demonstration of these key attributes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fierce curiosity&lt;/b&gt;. You are drawn to discovering and leveraging new data and taking on challenging business puzzles. &lt;b&gt;An inquisitive mind.&lt;/b&gt; Driven to ask questions to help lead projects to commercial value and not being afraid that the innovation attempts can and will lead to failing. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;A passion for solving problems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; The most successful data scientists&#8217; solution for what the right data to use, they solve using the most suitable (not most advanced) algorithms for the problem at hand and figure out how to execute and deliver with highest efficiency.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;Technical skills in both data and computer science.&lt;/b&gt; There are 3 core technical skills we look for: in-depth coding knowledge of an analytical tool(s) (i.e., Python); data science techniques and concepts; working with structured data (SQL) &lt;b&gt;Thirst for learning.&lt;/b&gt; You are a data scientist who is constantly updating their knowledge of data science state-of-the-art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you do?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Apply best in breed data science including descriptive, predictive, machine learning, deep learning and AI techniques from the design to implementation that impacts the business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Focus on Feature Engineering, Model Training and Model Evaluation in addition to data munging / wrangling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Identify the right algorithms and statistical techniques for a specific project as well as the best features for a model.&amp;nbsp; Advise junior members on the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Make business recommendations with effective presentations of findings at multiple levels of stakeholders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;An active contributing member to the analytics community to help foster and grow the data science community at Sun Life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Champion and support diversity and inclusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you need to succeed?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;2+ years experience in developing and implementing data science techniques (predictive, prescriptive, ML etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Comfortable writing complex SQL queries to extract and integrate data from multiple database sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proficient in using one or more statistical programming languages (i.e., Python) for data science&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Big Data Technologies: Hadoop, HDFS, Hive, HBase, Storm, Spark, Kafka&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with deep learning methodologies either in practice or in academia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Effective and concise oral and written storytelling and insights communication skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects in parallel while managing constantly changing deadlines and priorities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to document work and effectively prioritize documentation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BSc/M.S. in a statistical, mathematical, or technical field (i.e., computer science) or equivalent experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Past experience in life insurance/wealth management, or other financial services industry (e.g., retail banking, credit card, property and casualty insurance)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unique Requirements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The candidate selected for this role is required to have special clearance from the Royal Canadian Mounted Police. To see if you are eligible for this clearance, please review the section 201 on the Federal Government site (&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) &#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What\'s in it for you?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill-sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;73,800/73 800 - 124,100/124 100&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;30/09/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Senior-Data-Scientist_JR00043906?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Lead Data Scientist/ Director</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Role Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As one of Sun Life Canada&#8217;s largest business units, Insurance Solutions is responsible for designing and distributing leading-edge life and health insurance products to over 2 million individual retail Clients across Canada.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reporting to the AVP, Innovation and Analytics, the Lead Data Scientist / Director will lead machine learning and predictive analytics initiatives within Insurance Solutions to conceptualize, develop, and operationalize data science solutions for specific use cases across multiple functional areas including underwriting, sales, product management and actuarial.&amp;nbsp; The successful candidate will also provide intellectual leadership on the application of advanced analytics techniques to business problems and coach a high-performing team &lt;/span&gt;of analytics professionals&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The ideal candidate is a challenge-seeking, intellectually curious, results-oriented analytics leader with a passion for leveraging data to drive business outcomes and a thirst for continuous learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you do?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead a team to identify, develop, and operationalize high quality, robust machine learning solutions to meet the use cases of key functional areas within Insurance Solutions (e.g. underwriting, sales, product management, actuarial)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead the research, development, and enhancement of existing models (e.g. Sun Life&#8217;s accelerated underwriting model)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead the research and evaluation of new data sources, both internal and external; apply machine learning and deep learning techniques to extract actionable insights from available data; write complex SQL queries to extract and integrate data from multiple database sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Liaise with senior executives, product managers, actuaries and sales teams, to define use cases and deliver innovative solutions in order to help meet their business growth and profitability objectives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Coach and grow a high-performing team of analytics professionals with clear direction and proactive leadership, strategic assignment of responsibilities, and other training opportunities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What do you need to succeed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Genuine interest in life insurance and learning the business&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;M.S. or PhD in mathematics, computer science or other relevant fields, or equivalent work experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;7+ years of industry experience and expert knowledge in machine learning and data science, with hands-on experience building and deploying statistical / machine learning models&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3+ years experience leading data science projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3+ years experience in managing and leading a small team of data scientists&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Extensive knowledge of machine learning and deep learning tools and concepts (e.g. Random Forests, Neural Networks, XGBoost), including applications in NLP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience using one or more statistical programming languages (e.g., Python, R) to work with data sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Life and health insurance industry experience, preferably a background in underwriting, distribution, actuarial, or product management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with cloud-based big data tools and platforms: AWS, SageMaker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;In depth understanding of big data technologies: Hadoop, HDFS, Hive, HBase, Storm, Spark, Kafka&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with data analytics and data visualization best practices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;102,500/102 500 - 169,200/169 200&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;30/09/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Lead-Data-Scientist--Director_JR00046916?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Cloud Solutions Design Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid12-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid12-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-13" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The cloud Platform Engineering team is looking for a Skilled Cloud Solutions Design Engineer to be part of Sun Life&#8217;s Cloud transformation journey.&amp;nbsp; You will participate in Cloud Solutions design for strategic initiatives, and help unite the power of Cloud and Cloud Native DevOps infrastructure while scaling and transforming the existing Cloud Platform and ensuring its integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;What you will do?&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be part of a global Cloud Center of Excellence focused on delivering world class cloud solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will own and lead cloud platforms and products for internal customers from Data Science and Machine Learning, to Design and Development, to Business Analytics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partner directly with the Enterprise Architecture team to ensure proper execution, business and strategic alignment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work directly with DevOps teams, Data Scientist &amp;amp; Machine Learning teams, Designers and Developers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build automation and compliance by design using Cloud Native technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be part of an Agile development team helping the business deliver strategic initiatives&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working with new technologies and transforming legacy technology to leverage the Cloud.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make both tactical and strategic decisions including delivering Cloud Proof of Concept (PoC) initiatives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Required to move quickly but never compromise the security of our systems or the privacy of our Clients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drive forward the Cloud Infrastructure as Code roadmap.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apply best practices, standards, and ensure compliance to all company security directives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participate in security engineering to ensure compliance by design.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Help support application modernization, M&amp;amp;As, and data center migrations to the cloud.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;What you need to succeed:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;University degree/college diploma in related discipline(s) or equivalent work experience, and/or 5+ years of industry experience in the IT industry&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5 years of relevant work experience in server administration and/or cloud solution administration in an enterprise environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technical and business experience with one of the main public cloud providers (AWS, or Azure, or GCP).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in DevOps environments and the use of automation to deliver business value is useful&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in Software Engineering, Scripting, SDLC, or Infrastructure as Code.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advanced experience with programming and/or scripting languages (Python, Perl, Java, Bash, Ruby)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Systems provisioning and configuration management experience with automation tools such as Ansible, Jenkins, Terraform, Kubernetes, or Cloud Native tools.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Databases and data experience such as: PostgreSQL, Redis or similar&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You&#8217;ve engineered solutions for enterprise initiatives on a global scale.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Preferred Skills&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can context switch in real time between architecture, design, engineering, and operations discussion, and lead the conversation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills that build customers&#8217; confidence and trusted partnership.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broad technology background with ability to quickly grasp issues and translate to business impact.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ability to deliver documents, artifacts, and documentation (not just consoles and keyboards).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Note:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Applicants must have lived continuously in Canada for the last 5 years or more to be eligible to attain Reliability Status Clearance &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you&lt;/u&gt;?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Named 2021 "Best Places to Work" by Glassdoor&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work and professional development that is united by our Purpose: to help Clients and Employees achieve lifetime financial security and live healthier lives&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be part of our continuous improvement journey in developing the next greatest digital enterprise experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A common sense dress code, where you decide how you dress based on your day&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to move along a variety of career paths with amazing networking potential&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flex hours and periodic work from home options.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;73,800/73 800 - 124,100/124 100&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;IT - Technology Services&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;24/09/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Waterloo-Ontario/Cloud-Solutions-Design-Engineer_JR00043343-2?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Site Reliability Analyst</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WIF- WAI- WBI- WID- WKF- WNH- WBAB WJF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About the role:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Site Reliability Analyst works within the Event and Performance Management practice to drive excellence and innovation to support operational delivery priorities. SRA ensures critical internal and external digital services maintain reliability and uptime appropriate to client&#8217;s needs while keeping an ever-watchful eye on identifying capacity and performance concerns.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The role combines software and systems engineering to ensure applications and infrastructure are stable and performing optimally.&amp;nbsp; The SRA mindset uses engineering principles to constantly find ways to improve applications, systems and services. The role understands the big picture of how systems relate to each other to put in value-add end to end monitors, identifies optimization opportunities and improves productivity through automation.&amp;nbsp; Using a breadth of monitoring and development tools the SRA will limit the amount of time spent on operational work, provide data to prevent future incidents and take proactive actions to prevent potential outages. This mindset will help Event and Performance Management on the journey towards Artificial Intelligence for Operations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Working in a dynamic agile environment intellectual curiosity, problem solving, collaboration, valuing diversity and openness is key to success. As with many IT services, there is an expectation of availability off hours for client impacting changes or troubleshooting activities; Event and Performance Management provides services globally and therefore requires 24x7 support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;EPM Operations Command Centre Team provides round-the-clock (24 x 7 x 365), follow-the-sun operational support to our various customers. We utilize various tools to provide timely, accurate and reliable batch processing and system monitoring services across multiple platforms. We monitor core &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;applications/systems/processes,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provide solutions or escalate to appropriate support team for impact related events following defined processes and procedures. The EPM Operations environment includes shift operations and personnel to ensure uninterrupted monitoring operations, event management, batch job processing, escalations (notification and/or paging), ticketing, and centralized communications needed to support and operate in a high volume, high transaction, and dynamic operational environment. We work within established guidelines and assist with other projects (planned or ad-hoc) as required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What you will do?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Providing the IT Event console monitoring, day-to-day request handling and job scheduling services.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Collaborate with other teams&lt;/span&gt; to acknowledge, identify and triage events/alerts and subsequently to provide advice, backup and escalation to other analysts and their teams.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Helping to analyze metrics, identify trends and execute processes and strategies to address any risks to reliability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Collaborate with internal business partners, such as our IT Support Teams, for operational execution and service delivery of technology needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Create and implement knowledge documents, focusing on usability, content verification and accuracy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Participate and contribute to industry related developments and training to be shared among team members while continuously contributing to our roadmap strategy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What You Need To Succeed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Degree or diploma in computer sciences, information systems or information technology &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years working in technology or related field&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;2+ years supporting technology in an operational role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;2 years working within Enterprise delivery methodologies such as ITIL, Agile and Waterfall&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Professional designation preferred in ITIL, Scrum and/or Six Sigma&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Asset:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with operational monitoring &amp;amp; performance management tools such; BMC Suite (Patrol, TrueSight, TSOP, TSIM, BPPR), Broadcom Monitoring Suite (APM, DX APM), xMatters and other similar technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with BMC Control-M, Autosys Batch Job Scheduler suite of tools or similar&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Splunk or other software for searching, monitoring, and examining machine-generated Big Data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with CyberArk on any other similar security tool used for the security of privileged accounts through password management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in supporting network devices and knowledge of TCP/IP and related protocols&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of LAN / WAN &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;technologies/platforms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; - routers / switches / analyzers / DNS / DHCP / routing protocols / network management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Load Balancing, content filtering, VPN gateways, Firewalls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of testing and troubleshooting methodologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;Preferred Skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strong written and verbal communication, organization, strategic thinking and planning skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ability to analyze and present data using a variety of tools and techniques in the areas of business analysis and business intelligence principles to create executive dashboards and reports.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Demonstrated sensitivity to issues of ethics, diversity, equity and harassment in the workplace.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strong collaboration skills, self-starter, strategic thinker, negotiator and consensus builder.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;Notes/Unique Requirements: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must be able to obtain Reliability Status through the Government of Canada before a start date can be confirmed (includes a background check with fingerprinting by the RCMP) clearance before they can commence their EPM OCC duties in our Canadian office&#8217;s locations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;EPM OCC locations in Canada are located in Brampton OR Waterloo. Successful candidate could be asked to work out of the &lt;b&gt;Brampton (BH) office&lt;/b&gt; or Waterloo (WK) office at any given time and must be flexible to travel between the two locations when the schedule needs arise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Overtime (outside regular scheduled shifts) may be required. Candidates will need to be flexible to work irregular hours from one of SLF two major Data Centre locations: Waterloo (WK) or Brampton (BH) at any given time! This will require resources to be available beyond 8pm EST weekdays and on weekends. Resources will work rotating shifts (up to 12 hrs long) on a 24-hour schedule and will be required be \'on call\' on a rotational basis as business need arises.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Successful candidate that is part of shift rotation would be eligible for shift premium.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An environment of continuous learning and improvement&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to move along a variety of career paths with amazing networking potential&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;LI - SJ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WKL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;55,500/55 500 - 91,600/91 600&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;IT - Technology Services&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;23/09/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Brampton-Ontario/Site-Reliability-Analyst_JR00048370?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item></items>