<items><item><title>Senior Data Scientist</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WFFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WLJJ WMJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WEF- WMH- WNH- WED- WGF- WJH- WAAB WFF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Role Summary:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Canadian Operations is a diverse group of teams &#8211; each committed to creating exceptional experiences for our clients. Without a doubt, our clients lie at the forefront of everything we do.&amp;nbsp; We partner closely with each Canadian business unit to deliver the most efficient and effective customer service through training, process improvements, and technology optimization. With over 3,000 employees, our team members work in offices across Canada, including Montreal, Ottawa, Toronto and Waterloo. We also partner with our Sun Life team members in the Asia Service Centre offices in India and the Philippines to deliver exceptional customer service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As part of the BEAM (Business Excellence AI and Machine learning) team, the Senior Data Scientist will develop data science solutions for specific use cases identified in collaboration with other Operations teams. They will apply advanced machine learning and AI techniques to business problems, working closely with other data scientists and business partners. This role will report to the AVP, Data Science Strategy &amp;amp; Initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you do?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Play an active role in agile problem solving initiatives, collaborating within a cross-functional team of specialists:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Conduct end-to-end analysis that includes data gathering and requirements specification, processing, analysis, ongoing deliverables, and presentations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Build and maintain strong working relationships with Operations teams and other BUs to ensure successful delivery of initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Research and source relevant data from internal business systems, external free and commercial data products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Apply machine learning and deep learning techniques to extract insights from available data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Extract actionable insights from unstructured datasets using advanced machine learning methods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Use statistical methods to test findings through prototyping and scenario testing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Leverage business knowledge and judgement to prioritize approaches with a material financial impact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Establish model monitoring metrics and performance reporting format as appropriate to each use case&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Collaborate with implementation teams to operationalize successful use cases&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Make business recommendations with effective presentations of findings at multiple levels of stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What do you need to succeed?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;University degree in math, computer science, or other relevant fields. Graduate degrees preferred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;5+ years hands-on experience developing data science solutions in Python or R&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Extensive knowledge of machine learning and deep learning tools and concepts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working with data from systems and technologies in large operations environments, relational databases and other data warehouse structures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to maintain momentum on multiple projects in parallel and manage fluctuating deadlines and priorities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Demonstrated collaboration skills working in a team environment across multiple sites and multiple business units&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unique Requirements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The candidate selected for this role is required to have special clearance from the Royal Canadian Mounted Police. To see if you are eligible for this clearance, please review the section 201 on the Federal Government site (&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGL2"&gt;http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) &#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill-sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;73,800/73 800 - 124,100/124 100&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;10/09/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Senior-Data-Scientist_JR00044534</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Data Analyst</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WFFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WLJJ WMJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WEF- WMH- WNH- WED- WGF- WJH- WAAB WFF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As one of Sun Life Canada&#8217;s largest business units, Insurance Solutions is responsible for designing and distributing leading-edge life and health insurance products to over 2 million individual retail clients across Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Reporting to the Director, Business Intelligence, the Data Analyst will play an integral role in assembling the necessary data products to fuel a myriad of business intelligence reporting and advanced analytics initiatives within Insurance Solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The ideal candidate is a challenge-seeking, intellectually curious analytics professional with a deep passion for turning data into actionable insights to drive business decisions and solving data challenges in new and innovative ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you do?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analyze large quantities of data, draw out business insights from analytical output, and work with team leads to put together business recommendations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assemble datasets to support various business intelligence, advanced analytics, data exploration, and self-service analytics initiatives within Insurance Solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build the data infrastructure required for optimal extraction, transformation, and integration of data from disparate data sources using SQL and cloud-based big data technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Update data models to reflect the key business entities within Insurance Solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assist in design of new solutions and strategies for data capture, processing and consumption across data platforms (relational, dimensional, and NoSQL) that meet the needs of a variety of consumption patterns (visualization, analytics, and machine learning)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oversee and govern the expansion of our existing data architecture and the optimization of data query performance via best practices&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with IT partners and other analytics teams within Sun Life Canada to build out the data environment and analytics work platforms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What do you need to succeed?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Undergraduate degree in Computer Science, Mathematics, Engineering, Business, or equivalent&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years of data analysis experience, including data extraction, transformation, and loading of data from a variety of sources&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience writing efficient and complex SQL queries to extract and integrate data from multiple database sources&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding of modern data management principles (e.g. data warehousing) with hands-on relational, dimensional, and/or analytic experience (using RDBMS, dimensional, NoSQL data platform technologies, and ETL and data ingestion protocols)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience using one or more statistical programming languages (Python/R/SAS) to work with data sets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with data visualization tools, specifically Tableau&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills; able to work independently and in close collaboration with technical and business teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hands-on experience working on cloud platforms (AWS) with data processing and analytical tools such as AWS SageMaker, Apache Zeppelin, Hive SQL, Apache Spark, AWS Glue, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the Individual Insurance industry&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill-sets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;49,400/49 400 - 80,800/80 800&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;10/09/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Data-Analyst_JR00046902-3</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WFFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WLJJ WMJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WEF- WMH- WNH- WED- WGF- WJH- WAAB WFF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Role Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Do you have a passion for data? Do you enjoy influencing business decisions that impact our employees, clients and financial outcome? If you are analytical, curious, love solving complex business problems, we need you to join our high performing team to deliver exceptional value through analytics and insights that will drive the right actions for the business&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The Global Security Analytics team is looking for a Senior Data Scientist that will help us improve monitoring and control of advanced cyber threats by extracting insights hidden in vast amounts of network and security log data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Your primary focus will be building machine learning models, applying data mining techniques, performing statistical analysis and developing actionable reports with data visualizations. Your success in this role will be achieved by identifying previously undiscovered intrusions or by improving the organization&#8217;s security posture or the measurement thereof. The goal is to create new strategic and tactical value from security-relevant data through the dedicated exploration, analysis and investigation of that data using cutting-edge analytic technologies and techniques.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you need?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Perform large-scale data analysis and applying effective statistical methods and machine learning models for improving Cybersecurity detection at Sun Life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Design and develop AI/Machine Learning models for business operations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Design, develop, test, and deploy workloads on &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;AWS SageMaker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, applying models and algorithms to mine the stores of big data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Process, cleanse, and verify the integrity of data used for analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Developing complex SQL queries across multiple data sources to support analysis and optimizing workloads to reduce query runtimes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Accurately prepare and promptly complete all required supporting documentation for assigned projects/tasks (i.e., reports, models, change requests, presentations, tables, files, etc).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Present information using data visualization techniques for internal business partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What you need to succeed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;BSc/BA in Computer Science, Engineering or relevant field; graduate degree in Data Science or other quantitative field is preferred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;5+ years experience in using Python/R and SQL (Hadoop, Microsoft SQL Server, SAS, Oracle, etc.) to analyze data and gather valuable insights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;2 + years experience developing and building ML models including Predictive Modelling, Data Science application development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Minimum of 1 year experience with Amazon Web Services including Athena, Redshift, Lambda and SageMaker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Thorough knowledge and demonstrated experience in data management best practices (importing, cleaning, transforming, validating, quality and modeling data)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Conceptual understanding of the following topics:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Machine Learning (ML) techniques, and comprehension of existing algorithms and ML lifecycle components.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Database theory, ETL/data pipeline design and data modelling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Solid communication skills &#8211; have the ability to explain complexity of&amp;nbsp;data and analytical models to a non-data audience and explain the complexity of analytics to the business, IT and governance audience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Adaptable - maintains effectiveness while managing competing demands, able to deal with frequent change, delays or unexpected events&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unique Requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The candidate selected for this role is required to have special clearance from the RoyalCanadian Mounted Police. To see if you are eligible for this clearance, please review the section 201 on the Federal Government site (&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html"&gt;&lt;span class="WGL2"&gt;http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) &#8203;. Canadian Reliability Security Clearance is administered by submitting fingerprints to the RCMP, who then conduct min. 5 year history checks)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with Data Visualization and Reporting tools (Tableau Desktop, Power BI, AWS Quicksight) is nice to have&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;An environment of continuous learning and improvement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible hours and periodic work from home options&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The opportunity to move along a variety of career paths with amazing networking potential&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;73,800/73 800 - 124,100/124 100&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;IT - Technology Services&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;10/09/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/North-York-Ontario/Manager--Security-Analytics_JR00042864</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>AVP, Analytical Decision Engines</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WFFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WLJJ WMJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WEF- WMH- WNH- WED- WGF- WJH- WAAB WFF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-13" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Client Experience Office (CXO) aims to provide a holistic "One Sun Life" experience to Clients as we help them achieve lifetime financial security and live healthier lives. We design and execute clear, compelling, caring journeys to help Clients navigate some of the most important moments of their lives. Through personalized, proactive and relevant content, we act on a deep understanding of Client needs on a multitude of communication channels&#8212;so we can be there for Clients when and where they need us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;To understand our Clients, we actively listen and learn by employing experts in Client experience, engagement, marketing, strategy, and digital, data and analytics. Our Client Solutions Centre (CSC) engages directly with plan members to ensure they maximize the value of their benefit and retirement plans.&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you do?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Reporting to the VP Analytics and Insights, Client Experience Office, the Associate Vice President (AVP) &lt;b&gt;Analytics Decision Engines&lt;/b&gt; will lead the creation, implementation and evolution of data-powered &amp;nbsp;decision engines that provide recommendations and insights to clients through prescriptive analytics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The AVP will oversee a team of around &lt;b&gt;14&lt;/b&gt; people (located in Toronto and Waterloo).&amp;nbsp; This executive will leverage data analytics to identify/develop sales and service opportunities to deepen client relationships and to drive strong client satisfaction scores, high client retention, and profitable growth for Sun Life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A key responsibility of this role is to lead the &lt;b&gt;evolution of Sun Life&#8217;s autonomous prescriptive analytics&lt;/b&gt;, including &#8220;Next best Action&#8221; algorithms implemented in automated, machine learning platforms. Proven practical experience in this area is an important requirement for this role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Key priorities for this role are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead the development of the &lt;b&gt;&#8220;Next Best Action&#8221; &lt;/b&gt;recommendation engine across all client touchpoints:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead the design, architecture and delivery of client engagement and recommendation platforms, including the evolution of &lt;b&gt;autonomous prescriptive analytics&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Conceptualize and implement a model to translate value of different potential real-life actions (outbound call, send e-mail,&amp;nbsp; digital nudge) into a quantifiable measure&lt;/b&gt; that can be used by machine-learning systems to prioritize decisions based on propensity and expected impact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Work closely with the &lt;u&gt;Client Engagement&lt;/u&gt; team assessing performance of the recommendation and continuously evolving the platform, including expansion to more business units, products and touchpoints&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead the development of the&lt;b&gt; &#8220;smart assignment&#8221;&lt;/b&gt; analytical models to optimize matching of leads to the best suited advisors:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Work closely with the &lt;u&gt;Client Acquisition &lt;/u&gt;team to define the strategy and the key factors to be taken into account in matching algorithms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Derive insights from the matching data to identify other potential success drivers and continuously work to improve performance of the engine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Identify other areas of opportunity where the engine can be applied to increase recommendation success&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Embed rigorous performance management practices:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proactively develop and track metrics and measures to evaluate and determine the effectiveness of marketing programs, customer offers, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Leverage data/analytics to ensure that strong financial/commercial management practices are in place, through the efficient allocation of marketing spend across initiatives based on ROI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What do you need to succeed?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Over ten years of data analytics experience, with a minimum of 3 years in a &lt;span class="WGL2"&gt;management/leadership&lt;/span&gt; role related to prescriptive analytics&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;S/he understands statistical and machine-learning techniques, including data preparation methods such as transformations, normalization, and modeling methods including linear and nonlinear regression techniques (applied to customer and sales analytics).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The successful candidate will have a strong passion for empirical research and for answering hard questions with data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Financial services industry experience is preferred but not essential&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The successful candidate will be a strategic, conceptual thinker with strong written and oral communications skills who is able to influence the opinion of others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;S/he will have demonstrated the ability to operate in a highly matrixed environment, influencing and leveraging resources that do not report to her/him directly, and possess strong interpersonal skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proven experience in prescriptive analytics and machine learning:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Design and architecture: Ability to conceptualize prescriptive analytics from identification of data requirements to design of solution&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Delivery and results tracking: Experience in implementation of operational prescriptive analytics models, tracking of results and continuous improvement of model performance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proven track record implementing &#8220;Next Best Action&#8221; models and machine-learning algorithms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong quantitative, analytical and technical skills:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong quantitative background: Has impressive intellectual acumen and well-versed in key quantitative and data-driven disciplines as statistics, mathematics and finance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Robust understanding of data sufficiency and hypothesis-driven approach: Knows how to formulate hypothesis, design and run controlled tests to be able to conclusively identify significance in results, proving or refuting hypothesis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Broad understanding of different data &amp;amp; analytics methodologies and tools, including SAS, Open source (Python, AWS, SageMaker) and autonomous analytics (machine-learning)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Leading Teams:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Building talent: A proven leader able to build, lead, motivate and retain high performing teams. Insightful about the talent the organization needs to be successful; recruits and develops people with this in mind. Uses multiple methods to grow capability in the organization. Skillfully coaches and mentors others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Inspiring and motivating: Gets the best performance from people. Taps into people&#8217;s needs, interests and goals to motivate them to achieve. Inspires commitment from people and mobilizes teams toward high performance and goal achievement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Integrity: Adheres to the highest standards of personal and professional integrity and sets a positive example for others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being a member of the Sun Life family, a group of people united by our Purpose: to help Clients and Employees achieve lifetime financial security and live healthier lives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Joining a reputable organization with over 150 years of history&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;115,700/115 700 - 197,200/197 200&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;10/09/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/AVP--Analytical-Decision-Engines_JR00047084</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Cloud Solutions Design Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WFFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WLJJ WMJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WEF- WMH- WNH- WED- WGF- WJH- WAAB WFF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-13" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The cloud Platform Engineering team is looking for a Skilled Cloud Solutions Design Engineer to be part of Sun Life&#8217;s Cloud transformation journey.&amp;nbsp; You will participate in Cloud Solutions design for strategic initiatives, and help unite the power of Cloud and Cloud Native DevOps infrastructure while scaling and transforming the existing Cloud Platform and ensuring its integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;What you will do?&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be part of a global Cloud Center of Excellence focused on delivering world class cloud solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will own and lead cloud platforms and products for internal customers from Data Science and Machine Learning, to Design and Development, to Business Analytics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partner directly with the Enterprise Architecture team to ensure proper execution, business and strategic alignment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work directly with DevOps teams, Data Scientist &amp;amp; Machine Learning teams, Designers and Developers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build automation and compliance by design using Cloud Native technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be part of an Agile development team helping the business deliver strategic initiatives&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working with new technologies and transforming legacy technology to leverage the Cloud.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make both tactical and strategic decisions including delivering Cloud Proof of Concept (PoC) initiatives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Required to move quickly but never compromise the security of our systems or the privacy of our Clients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drive forward the Cloud Infrastructure as Code roadmap.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apply best practices, standards, and ensure compliance to all company security directives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participate in security engineering to ensure compliance by design.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Help support application modernization, M&amp;amp;As, and data center migrations to the cloud.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;What you need to succeed:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;University degree/college diploma in related discipline(s) or equivalent work experience, and/or 5+ years of industry experience in the IT industry&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5 years of relevant work experience in server administration and/or cloud solution administration in an enterprise environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technical and business experience with one of the main public cloud providers (AWS, or Azure, or GCP).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in DevOps environments and the use of automation to deliver business value is useful&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in Software Engineering, Scripting, SDLC, or Infrastructure as Code.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advanced experience with programming and/or scripting languages (Python, Perl, Java, Bash, Ruby)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Systems provisioning and configuration management experience with automation tools such as Ansible, Jenkins, Terraform, Kubernetes, or Cloud Native tools.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Databases and data experience such as: PostgreSQL, Redis or similar&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You&#8217;ve engineered solutions for enterprise initiatives on a global scale.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Preferred Skills&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can context switch in real time between architecture, design, engineering, and operations discussion, and lead the conversation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills that build customers&#8217; confidence and trusted partnership.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broad technology background with ability to quickly grasp issues and translate to business impact.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ability to deliver documents, artifacts, and documentation (not just consoles and keyboards).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Note:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Applicants must have lived continuously in Canada for the last 5 years or more to be eligible to attain Reliability Status Clearance &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you&lt;/u&gt;?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Named 2021 "Best Places to Work" by Glassdoor&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work and professional development that is united by our Purpose: to help Clients and Employees achieve lifetime financial security and live healthier lives&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be part of our continuous improvement journey in developing the next greatest digital enterprise experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A common sense dress code, where you decide how you dress based on your day&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to move along a variety of career paths with amazing networking potential&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flex hours and periodic work from home options.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WGL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;73,800/73 800 - 124,100/124 100&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;IT - Technology Services&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;24/09/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Waterloo-Ontario/Cloud-Solutions-Design-Engineer_JR00043343-2</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item></items>