<items><item><title>Lead Data Scientist/ Director, Data Science</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WJFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WCKJ WDKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WPG- WCH- WIJ- WJJ- WPE- WBH- WFJ- WBAB WAH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Role Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As one of Sun Life Canada&#8217;s largest business units, Insurance Solutions is responsible for designing and distributing leading-edge life and health insurance products to over 2 million individual retail Clients across Canada.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reporting to the AVP, Innovation and Analytics, the Lead Data Scientist / Director will lead machine learning and predictive analytics initiatives within Insurance Solutions to conceptualize, develop, and operationalize data science solutions for specific use cases across multiple functional areas including underwriting, sales, product management and actuarial.&amp;nbsp; The successful candidate will also provide intellectual leadership on the application of advanced analytics techniques to business problems and coach a high-performing team &lt;/span&gt;of analytics professionals&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The ideal candidate is a challenge-seeking, intellectually curious, results-oriented analytics leader with a passion for leveraging data to drive business outcomes and a thirst for continuous learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you do?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead a team to identify, develop, and operationalize high quality, robust machine learning solutions to meet the use cases of key functional areas within Insurance Solutions (e.g. underwriting, sales, product management, actuarial)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead the research, development, and enhancement of existing models (e.g. Sun Life&#8217;s accelerated underwriting model)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead the research and evaluation of new data sources, both internal and external; apply machine learning and deep learning techniques to extract actionable insights from available data; write complex SQL queries to extract and integrate data from multiple database sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Liaise with senior executives, product managers, actuaries and sales teams, to define use cases and deliver innovative solutions in order to help meet their business growth and profitability objectives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Coach and grow a high-performing team of analytics professionals with clear direction and proactive leadership, strategic assignment of responsibilities, and other training opportunities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What do you need to succeed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Genuine interest in life insurance and learning the business&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;M.S. or PhD in mathematics, computer science or other relevant fields, or equivalent work experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;7+ years of industry experience and expert knowledge in machine learning and data science, with hands-on experience building and deploying statistical / machine learning models&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3+ years experience leading data science projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3+ years experience in managing and leading a small team of data scientists&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Extensive knowledge of machine learning and deep learning tools and concepts (e.g. Random Forests, Neural Networks, XGBoost), including applications in NLP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience using one or more statistical programming languages (e.g., Python, R) to work with data sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Life and health insurance industry experience, preferably a background in underwriting, distribution, actuarial, or product management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with cloud-based big data tools and platforms: AWS, SageMaker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;In depth understanding of big data technologies: Hadoop, HDFS, Hive, HBase, Storm, Spark, Kafka&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with data analytics and data visualization best practices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="thebrightside@sunlife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;104,000/104 000 - 171,700/171 700&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Lead-Data-Scientist--Director_JR00046916?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Manager, Data Science (Remote)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WJFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WCKJ WDKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WPG- WCH- WIJ- WJJ- WPE- WBH- WFJ- WBAB WAH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Role Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Within Sun Life Canada, the Client Experience Office (CXO) was launched to support the design and execution of clear, compelling, and caring client journeys, helping clients navigate some of the most important moments of their lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Reporting to the&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt; AVP, Client Value and Segmentation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; as &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Manager&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Data Scientist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; you will focus on supporting the CXO in understanding our clients, the value they bring and their future with Sun Life. &amp;nbsp;The manager, data scientist will leverage practical experience in applying varied data science techniques &amp;amp; offering advice/inputs to help with the design, development and implementation of analytics use cases while also leading a team of 2-3 data scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sun Life views success in this role in demonstration of these key attributes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fierce curiosity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. You are drawn to discovering and leveraging new data and taking on challenging business puzzles. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;An inquisitive mind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Driven to ask questions to help lead projects to commercial value and not being afraid that the innovation attempts can and will lead to failing. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;A passion for solving problems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; The most successful data scientists&#8217; solution for what the right data to use, they solve using the most suitable (not most advanced) algorithms for the problem at hand and figure out how to execute and deliver with highest efficiency.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Technical skills in both data and computer science.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; There are 3 core technical skills we look for: in-depth coding knowledge of an analytical tool(s) (i.e., SAS, Python); data science techniques and concepts; working with structured data (SQL) &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thirst for learning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; You are a data scientist who is constantly updating their knowledge of data science state-of-the-art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you do?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Apply best in breed data science including descriptive, predictive, machine learning, deep learning and AI techniques from the design to implementation that impacts the business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Focus on Feature Engineering, Model Training and Model Evaluation in addition to data munging / wrangling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Identify the right algorithms and statistical techniques for a specific project as well as the best features for a model.&amp;nbsp; Advise junior members on the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Make business recommendations with effective presentations of findings at multiple levels of stakeholders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead a team of 2-3 data scientists with a strong focus on developing skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;An active contributing member to the analytics community to help foster and grow the data science community at Sun Life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Champion and support diversity and inclusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you need to succeed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;5+ years experience in developing and implementing analytic and data science techniques (descriptive, diagnostic, predictive, prescriptive, ML etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;2+ years experience as a people leader, hiring, onboarding and growing talent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Comfortable writing complex SQL queries to extract and integrate data from multiple database sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proficient in using one or more statistical programming languages (i.e., Python) for data science&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience using SAS on the job. While we will be moving to AWS &amp;amp; Python our current project is being done is SAS and strong skills are a must&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with deep learning methodologies either in practice or in academia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Effective and concise oral and written storytelling and insights communication skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects in parallel while managing constantly changing deadlines and priorities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to document work and effectively prioritize projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BSc/M.S. in a statistical, mathematical, or technical field (i.e., computer science) or equivalent experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Past experience in life insurance/wealth management, or other financial services industry (e.g., retail banking, credit card, property and casualty insurance)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Big Data Technologies: Hadoop, HDFS, Hive, HBase, Storm, Spark, Kafka&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unique Requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The candidate selected for this role is required to have special clearance from the Royal Canadian Mounted Police. To see if you are eligible for this clearance, please review the section 201 on the Federal Government site&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="https://www.tpsgc-pwgsc.gc.ca/esc-src/personnel/pdcf-rsrp-eng.html opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.tpsgc-pwgsc.gc.ca/esc-src/personnel/pdcf-rsrp-eng.html"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;https://www.tpsgc-pwgsc.gc.ca/esc-src/personnel/pdcf-rsrp-eng.html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What\'s in it for you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill-sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="thebrightside@sunlife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;74,900/74 900 - 125,900/125 900&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;06/02/2022&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Manager--Data-Science--Remote-_JR00053814?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Data Scientist</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WJFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WCKJ WDKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WPG- WCH- WIJ- WJJ- WPE- WBH- WFJ- WBAB WAH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid15-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid15-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-16" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Role Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Within Sun Life Canada, the Data Analytics &amp;amp; Insights team is a multi-disciplinary center of excellence comprised of savvy and intellectually curious professionals who are on a mission to transform how we apply data and analytics to support Sun Life clients live healthier lives and achieve financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Reporting to the&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt; Manager, Data Science &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;as a &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Data Scientist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; you will focus on supporting Canadian business units and Client Experience Office (CXO) in accelerating the growth and application of analytics in driving value. &amp;nbsp;The data scientist will leverage practical experience in applying varied data science techniques &amp;amp; offering advice/inputs to help with the design, development and implementation of analytics use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sun Life views success in this role in demonstration of these key attributes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fierce curiosity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. You are drawn to discovering and leveraging new data and taking on challenging business puzzles. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;An inquisitive mind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Driven to ask questions to help lead projects to commercial value and not being afraid that the innovation attempts can and will lead to failing. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;A passion for solving problems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; The most successful data scientists&#8217; solution for what the right data to use, they solve using the most suitable (not most advanced) algorithms for the problem at hand and figure out how to execute and deliver with highest efficiency.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Technical skills in both data and computer science.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; There are 3 core technical skills we look for: in-depth coding knowledge of an analytical tool(s) (i.e., SAS, Python); data science techniques and concepts; working with structured data (SQL) &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thirst for learning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; You are a data scientist who is constantly updating their knowledge of data science state-of-the-art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you do?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Apply best in breed data science including descriptive, predictive, machine learning and AI techniques from the design to implementation that impacts the business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Focus on Feature Engineering, Model Training and Model Evaluation in addition to data munging / wrangling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Identify the right algorithms and statistical techniques for a specific project as well as the best features for a model&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Make business recommendations with effective presentations of findings at multiple levels of stakeholders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;An active contributing member to the analytics community to help foster and grow the data science community at Sun Life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Champion and support diversity and inclusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you need to succeed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;2+ years experience in developing and implementing data science techniques (predictive, prescriptive, ML etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Comfortable writing complex SQL queries to extract and integrate data from multiple database sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proficient in using one or more statistical programming languages (i.e., SAS, Python) for data science&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Effective and concise oral and written storytelling and insights communication skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects in parallel while managing constantly changing deadlines and priorities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to document work and effectively prioritize documentation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BSc/M.S. in a statistical, mathematical, or technical field (i.e., computer science) or equivalent experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Past experience in life insurance/wealth management, or other financial services industry (e.g., retail banking, credit card, property and casualty insurance)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unique Requirements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The candidate selected for this role is required to have special clearance from the Royal Canadian Mounted Police. To see if you are eligible for this clearance, please review the section 201 on the Federal Government site (&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="https://www.tpsgc-pwgsc.gc.ca/esc-src/personnel/pdcf-rsrp-eng.html opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.tpsgc-pwgsc.gc.ca/esc-src/personnel/pdcf-rsrp-eng.html"&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;https://www.tpsgc-pwgsc.gc.ca/esc-src/personnel/pdcf-rsrp-eng.html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What\'s in it for you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range dat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;15 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Remote/ Hybrid work environment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill-sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="thebrightside@sunlife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;56,300/56 300 - 92,900/92 900&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;31/01/2022&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Data-Scientist---Client-Insights---Analytics_JR00052470-3?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Director, Pega Development</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WJFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WCKJ WDKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WPG- WCH- WIJ- WJJ- WPE- WBH- WFJ- WBAB WAH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid12-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid12-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-13" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Director, Pega Development&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The Sun Life Enterprise Case Management Centre of Excellence requires senior level development expertise to lead, at a program level, the delivery of Pega solutions across several projects. This individual will help design and develop workflow solutions with client-centric, omni-channel processes delivered through a consistent &#8220;One Sun&#8221; case management platform, achieving the goal of making it easier for our clients to do business with us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The Director, Pega Development incumbent will leverage their expertise in leading large enterprise initiatives to set design, develop, implement, and maintain an Enterprise Case Management (ECM) platform for workflow and case management solutions across Sun Life, including SLF Canada various lines of business, Corporate, and other Business Groups as they come on board to utilize the common enterprise solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you do?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Provide design and development thought leadership and work closely with fellow team members and across business and technical project dimensions, solving enterprise-wide complex business requirements and make informed decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Demonstrate forward thinking around where the business is going and how technology can support these efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Build trust relationships with senior level technical and business teams and communicate at all levels of the organization&#8217;s enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Develop deep knowledge of the capabilities of the Pega Platform and Pega Strategic Applications and deliver these capabilities to maximize speed &amp;amp; efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Collaborate with architecture team to create and maintain standards for the overall architectural vision that emphasizes a reuse strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Map existing legacy workflow &amp;amp; case management solutions to the new enterprise roadmap and develop strategies for renewal aligned to business strategies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Improve operational efficiencies through best use and implementation of industry-leading case management capabilities and increased automation through chatbots, robotics, artificial intelligence and machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Provide thought leadership and work closely with fellow team members and across business and technical project dimensions, solving enterprise-wide complex technical requirements and make informed decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Build trust relationships with senior level technical and business teams and communicate at all levels of the organization&#8217;s enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Develop deep knowledge of the capabilities of the Pega Platform and Pega Strategic Applications and champion their use to maximize speed &amp;amp; efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Collaborate with architecture team to create and maintain standards for the overall architectural vision that emphasizes a reuse strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Establish standards and best practices within the workflow &amp;amp; case management space and within the Pega framework.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Develop, implement, maintain and monitor internal controls and governance for case management workflow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Understand the Pega guardrails and promote process designs and best practices that keep teams within those guardrails.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Govern the overarching Pega support model and provide recommendations for continual improvement of the supporting infrastructure environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ensure usage of Agile methodologies and DevOps framework&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strategy development and management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What do you need to succeed?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;8+ years of solid experience working in Pega Architecture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;15+ years of leadership experience in Technology, Operations and/or Finance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;2+ years of Program Management experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with transformation strategy, approach, and planning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Excellent interpersonal, collaboration and team building skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Must have experience using Pega Survey, Knowledge Management, Product Builder, and other Pega strategic applications&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Excellent relationship management skills, problem analysis and trouble shooting skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong organizational, multi tasking and time management skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Prior experience managing director-level direct/indirect reports in a cross matrixed or virtual environment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to lead through influence in a complex and evolving environment, to meet challenging timelines and organizational goals, bringing various parties to a common action plan that is mutually beneficial for all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to identify commonality across projects to ensure streamlining of work, consistency and maintainability of solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Seasoned cross business group and business unit collaboration and strong relationship building experience, with business partners, IT groups and external vendors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diligent about enforcing standards, best practices and able to communicate benefits to stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Executive level presentation skills (written and oral) to effectively communicate and influence at all levels within the organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience leading large Enterprise Initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Work-life balance by scheduling your day around your priorities and having more time to spend on the important things&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;An environment of continuous learning and improvement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our journey in developing the next greatest digital experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The opportunity to move along a variety of career paths with amazing networking potential&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;#LI-Hybrid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="thebrightside@sunlife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;104,000/104 000 - 171,700/171 700&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;IT - Application Development&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;10/02/2022&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Director--Pega-Development_JR00054480-3?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Analyst - eMessaging</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WJFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WCKJ WDKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WPG- WCH- WIJ- WJJ- WPE- WBH- WFJ- WBAB WAH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Role Summary:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Sun Life Financial has an immediate requirement for a Support Analyst in operations for the Employee Experience Technologies - eMessaging Operations Team (aka EET eMessaging Ops). The EET eMessaging Ops team is accountable for the day-to-day operations, maintenance, performance and metrics of the technology associated with a variety of tools at Sun Life Financial.&amp;nbsp; This particular role will have a focus on supporting the eMessaging systems of Microsoft &lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;Exchange/Outlook/O365&lt;/span&gt; along with Cisco IronPort and FireEye security products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a member of this organization, you will be working in a team environment to support secure, robust and reliable collaboration solutions to meet the evolving needs of our internal clients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As the successful candidate for this role, your knowledge of EET technology, troubleshooting skills, analysis techniques and experience working in operations will help you provide decisive support and leadership for the eMessaging environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You will report to the Manager of EET eMessaging Ops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;*** The candidate selected for this role is required to have government clearance from the Royal Canadian Mounted Police to handle all machines and have access to the various OSS locations . To see if you are eligible for this clearance, please review the section 201 on the Federal Government site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &#8203;***&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Main Accountabilities:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support and maintain the infrastructure to ensure availability, capacity, currency, disaster recovery and security needs are &lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;met&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot and document to accepted engineering standards&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and implement pro-active changes to existing infrastructure and process to improve our service delivery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Communicate frequently with client service peers; client interaction is key to managing expectations, assessing needs, and customizing solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interacting with various other engineering and technical support teams including networking, servers, storage, security, service desk and on-site support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pro-actively identify and resolve team and/or individual technology knowledge gaps&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide on-call support as scheduled&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Be available for scheduled off hours work&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Core Qualifications&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;University degree/college diploma in related discipline(s) or equivalent work experience, and/or 2+ years of industry experience in the IT industry&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong investigative skills with respect to new and emerging technology solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong troubleshooting and research skills used to troubleshoot technology solutions to business needs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with development and scripting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid written and verbal communication skills as well as strong interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;General knowledge of IT infrastructure (networking, servers, data security concepts, etc)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with eMessaging systems:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Exchange&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Outlook/O365&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cisco IronPort&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;FireEye&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Active Directory&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Optional Qualifications&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working on medium to large scale enterprise infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technical background including experience with Windows O/S platforms and Mac O/S platforms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with any of these products is beneficial:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft SharePoint, One Drive&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Workplace by Facebook&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confluence Wiki&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Active Directory, Azure Active Directory, Active Directory Federated Services, Group Policy, Certificate Management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lotus Notes/Domino&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Systems Centre Configuration Manager (SCCM/SMS)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Citrix/XenApp&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;McAfee security suite including ePolicy Orchestrator&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;VMware View/VSphere/ESX&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mobile Device Management (Airwatch, Intune)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="thebrightside@sunlife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;56,300/56 300 - 92,900/92 900&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;IT - Technology Services&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/North-York-Ontario/Analyst---eMessaging_JR00053023?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item></items>