<items><item><title>Lead Data Scientist/ Director, Data Science</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WJFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WCKJ WDKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WPG- WCH- WIJ- WJJ- WPE- WBH- WFJ- WBAB WAH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Role Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As one of Sun Life Canada&#8217;s largest business units, Insurance Solutions is responsible for designing and distributing leading-edge life and health insurance products to over 2 million individual retail Clients across Canada.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reporting to the AVP, Innovation and Analytics, the Lead Data Scientist / Director will lead machine learning and predictive analytics initiatives within Insurance Solutions to conceptualize, develop, and operationalize data science solutions for specific use cases across multiple functional areas including underwriting, sales, product management and actuarial.&amp;nbsp; The successful candidate will also provide intellectual leadership on the application of advanced analytics techniques to business problems and coach a high-performing team &lt;/span&gt;of analytics professionals&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The ideal candidate is a challenge-seeking, intellectually curious, results-oriented analytics leader with a passion for leveraging data to drive business outcomes and a thirst for continuous learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you do?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead a team to identify, develop, and operationalize high quality, robust machine learning solutions to meet the use cases of key functional areas within Insurance Solutions (e.g. underwriting, sales, product management, actuarial)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead the research, development, and enhancement of existing models (e.g. Sun Life&#8217;s accelerated underwriting model)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead the research and evaluation of new data sources, both internal and external; apply machine learning and deep learning techniques to extract actionable insights from available data; write complex SQL queries to extract and integrate data from multiple database sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Liaise with senior executives, product managers, actuaries and sales teams, to define use cases and deliver innovative solutions in order to help meet their business growth and profitability objectives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Coach and grow a high-performing team of analytics professionals with clear direction and proactive leadership, strategic assignment of responsibilities, and other training opportunities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What do you need to succeed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Genuine interest in life insurance and learning the business&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;M.S. or PhD in mathematics, computer science or other relevant fields, or equivalent work experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;7+ years of industry experience and expert knowledge in machine learning and data science, with hands-on experience building and deploying statistical / machine learning models&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3+ years experience leading data science projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3+ years experience in managing and leading a small team of data scientists&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Extensive knowledge of machine learning and deep learning tools and concepts (e.g. Random Forests, Neural Networks, XGBoost), including applications in NLP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience using one or more statistical programming languages (e.g., Python, R) to work with data sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Life and health insurance industry experience, preferably a background in underwriting, distribution, actuarial, or product management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with cloud-based big data tools and platforms: AWS, SageMaker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;In depth understanding of big data technologies: Hadoop, HDFS, Hive, HBase, Storm, Spark, Kafka&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with data analytics and data visualization best practices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="thebrightside@sunlife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;104,000/104 000 - 171,700/171 700&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Lead-Data-Scientist--Director_JR00046916?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WJFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WCKJ WDKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WPG- WCH- WIJ- WJJ- WPE- WBH- WFJ- WBAB WAH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Role Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Within Sun Life, the Analytics &amp;amp; Insights teams are comprised of savvy and intellectually curious professionals who are on a mission to transform how we apply data and analytics to support Sun Life becoming client-centric. An integral part of the Analytics &amp;amp; Insights organization, the Data Science team supports Canadian business units in their journey to leverage data and analytics as a foundational pillar in delivering business value&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Reporting to the&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt; Director, Data Science, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;as a &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Senior Data Scientist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; you will focus on supporting Canadian business units in accelerating the growth and application of analytics in driving value. &amp;nbsp;The senior data scientist will leverage practical experience in applying varied data science techniques &amp;amp; offering advice/inputs to help with the design, development and implementation of analytics use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sun Life views success in this role in demonstration of these key attributes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fierce curiosity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. You are drawn to discovering and leveraging new data and taking on challenging business puzzles. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;An inquisitive mind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Driven to ask questions to help lead projects to commercial value and not being afraid that the innovation attempts can and will lead to failing. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;A passion for solving problems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; The most successful data scientists&#8217; solution for what the right data to use, they solve using the most suitable (not most advanced) algorithms for the problem at hand and figure out how to execute and deliver with highest efficiency.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Technical skills in both data and computer science.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; There are 3 core technical skills we look for: in-depth coding knowledge of an analytical tool(s) (i.e., Python); data science techniques and concepts; working with structured data (SQL) &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thirst for learning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; You are a data scientist who is constantly updating their knowledge of data science state-of-the-art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you do?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Apply best in breed data science including descriptive, predictive and machine learning techniques from the design to implementation that impacts the business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Focus on Feature Engineering, Model Training and Model Evaluation in addition to data munging / wrangling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Identify the right algorithms and statistical techniques for a specific project as well as the best features for a model.&amp;nbsp; Advise junior members on the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Make business recommendations with effective presentations of findings at multiple levels of stakeholders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;An active contributing member to the analytics community to help foster and grow the data science community at Sun Life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Champion and support diversity and inclusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you need to succeed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BSc/M.S. in a statistical, mathematical, or technical field (i.e., computer science) or equivalent experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3+ years experience in developing and implementing data science techniques (predictive, prescriptive, ML etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Comfortable writing complex SQL queries to extract and integrate data from multiple database sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proficient in using one or more statistical programming languages (i.e., Python) for data science&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with AWS services including SageMaker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with machine learning including supervised and unsupervised models&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Demonstrated experience in data transformation &amp;amp; data manipulation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working with Structured vs. Unstructured data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with Big Data Technologies: Hadoop, HDFS, Hive, HBase,, Spark is strongly desirable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Effective and concise oral and written storytelling and insights communication skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects in parallel while managing constantly changing deadlines and priorities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to document work and effectively prioritize documentation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Past experience in life insurance/wealth management, or other financial services industry (e.g., retail banking, credit card, property and casualty insurance)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unique Requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The candidate selected for this role is required to have special clearance from the Royal Canadian Mounted Police. To see if you are eligible for this clearance, please review the section 201 on the Federal Government site (&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html opens new window" target="_blank" href="http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) &#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What\'s in it for you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill-sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="thebrightside@sunlife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;74,900/74 900 - 125,900/125 900&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;30/01/2022&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Senior-Data-Scientist_JR00044795?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist (Remote)</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WJFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WCKJ WDKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WPG- WCH- WIJ- WJJ- WPE- WBH- WFJ- WBAB WAH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid16-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid16-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-17" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Role Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Within Sun Life, the Analytics &amp;amp; Insights teams are comprised of savvy and intellectually curious professionals who are on a mission to transform how we apply data and analytics to support Sun Life becoming client-centric. An integral part of the Analytics &amp;amp; Insights organization, the Data Science team supports Canadian business units in their journey to leverage data and analytics as a foundational pillar in delivering business value&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Reporting to the&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt; Director, Data Science, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;as a &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Senior Data Scientist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; you will focus on supporting Canadian business units in accelerating the growth and application of analytics in driving value. &amp;nbsp;The senior data scientist will leverage practical experience in applying varied data science techniques &amp;amp; offering advice/inputs to help with the design, development and implementation of analytics use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sun Life views success in this role in demonstration of these key attributes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fierce curiosity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. You are drawn to discovering and leveraging new data and taking on challenging business puzzles. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;An inquisitive mind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Driven to ask questions to help lead projects to commercial value and not being afraid that the innovation attempts can and will lead to failing. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;A passion for solving problems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; The most successful data scientists&#8217; solution for what the right data to use, they solve using the most suitable (not most advanced) algorithms for the problem at hand and figure out how to execute and deliver with highest efficiency.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Technical skills in both data and computer science.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; There are 3 core technical skills we look for: in-depth coding knowledge of an analytical tool(s) (i.e., Python); data science techniques and concepts; working with structured data (SQL) &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thirst for learning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; You are a data scientist who is constantly updating their knowledge of data science state-of-the-art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you do?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Apply best in breed data science including descriptive, predictive and machine learning techniques from the design to implementation that impacts the business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Focus on Feature Engineering, Model Training and Model Evaluation in addition to data munging / wrangling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Identify the right algorithms and statistical techniques for a specific project as well as the best features for a model.&amp;nbsp; Advise junior members on the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Make business recommendations with effective presentations of findings at multiple levels of stakeholders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;An active contributing member to the analytics community to help foster and grow the data science community at Sun Life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Champion and support diversity and inclusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you need to succeed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BSc/M.S. in a statistical, mathematical, or technical field (i.e., computer science) or equivalent experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3+ years experience in developing and implementing data science techniques (predictive, prescriptive, ML etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Comfortable writing complex SQL queries to extract and integrate data from multiple database sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proficient in using one or more statistical programming languages (i.e., Python) for data science&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with AWS services including SageMaker is required for some roles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with machine learning including supervised and unsupervised models&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Demonstrated experience in data transformation &amp;amp; data manipulation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working with Structured vs. Unstructured data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with Big Data Technologies: Hadoop, HDFS, Hive, HBase, Spark is strongly desirable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Effective and concise oral and written storytelling and insights communication skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects in parallel while managing constantly changing deadlines and priorities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to document work and effectively prioritize documentation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Past experience in life insurance/wealth management, or other financial services industry (e.g., retail banking, credit card, property and casualty insurance)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unique Requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The candidate selected for this role is required to have special clearance from the Royal Canadian Mounted Police. To see if you are eligible for this clearance, please review the information on Federal Government site (&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="https://www.tpsgc-pwgsc.gc.ca/esc-src/personnel/pdcf-rsrp-eng.html opens new window" target="_blank" href="https://www.tpsgc-pwgsc.gc.ca/esc-src/personnel/pdcf-rsrp-eng.html"&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;https://www.tpsgc-pwgsc.gc.ca/esc-src/personnel/pdcf-rsrp-eng.html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What\'s in it for you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Remote/ Hybrid Work environment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill-sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="thebrightside@sunlife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;74,900/74 900 - 125,900/125 900&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;23/01/2022&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Montreal-Quebec/Senior-Data-Scientist--Remote-_JR00045958?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Intermediate Cloud Infrastructure Analyst</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WJFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WCKJ WDKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WPG- WCH- WIJ- WJJ- WPE- WBH- WFJ- WBAB WAH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Description du poste&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Le poste d&#8217;analyste interm&#233;diaire, infrastructure infonuagique, est un pilier essentiel de l&#8217;&#233;quipe Op&#233;rations et infrastructure infonuagique. Ce groupe tr&#232;s estim&#233; au sein du secteur Donn&#233;es et analytique joue un r&#244;le crucial en mati&#232;re de m&#233;gadonn&#233;es, d&#8217;apprentissage machine et d&#8217;analytique par la conception, le d&#233;veloppement et l&#8217;entretien des infrastructures d&#8217;analytique et des technologies d&#8217;intergiciels sur les plateformes infonuagiques.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Les fonctions &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Travailler avec les composantes logiciel en tant que service (SaaS) et plateforme en tant que service (PaaS) d&#8217;Amazon Web Services (AWS), l&#8217;administration d&#8217;Hadoop et d&#8217;autres technologies connexes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&#201;valuer les fonctions et les caract&#233;ristiques des services infonuagiques et des technologies connexes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participer &#224; des projets d&#8217;infrastructure de petite et de moyenne envergure tout au long de leur cycle de vie ainsi que d&#233;finir et g&#233;rer les r&#233;sultats attendus, en plus d&#8217;en faire le suivi au moyen de technologies d&#233;finies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborer &#233;troitement avec les autres membres de l&#8217;&#233;quipe, les responsables techniques, les chefs d&#8217;&#233;quipe, la direction, les secteurs des TI sp&#233;cialis&#233;s et les &#233;quipes de soutien des applications pour assurer l&#8217;uniformit&#233; de la prestation et de la qualit&#233; des services infonuagiques.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tenir &#224; jour les documents et les proc&#233;dures pour l&#8217;ensemble des plateformes infonuagiques et d&#233;finir les exigences en collaboration avec d&#8217;autres d&#233;veloppeurs et sp&#233;cialistes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&#201;laborer des scripts et des fonctions pour soutenir les processus internes et am&#233;liorer la performance des syst&#232;mes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;D&#233;finir, consigner et mettre en &#339;uvre des normes et des proc&#233;dures coh&#233;rentes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partager &#224; tour de r&#244;le la responsabilit&#233; des fonctions de garde en tout temps, du soutien des changements apr&#232;s les heures normales de travail et des mises &#224; l&#8217;essai des plans antisinistres.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Les aptitudes pour r&#233;ussir&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent dossier universitaire et dipl&#244;me universitaire en informatique, en math&#233;matiques, en sciences ou dans un domaine connexe. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Connaissance et exp&#233;rience du secteur des technologies de l&#8217;information avec un excellent dossier universitaire dans un domaine connexe.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Capacit&#233; de comprendre, de d&#233;crire et de mettre en pratique des concepts complexes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellentes aptitudes pour la communication verbale et &#233;crite.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Passion pour les donn&#233;es et l&#8217;analytique en tant que carri&#232;re.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent sens de l&#8217;organisation et capacit&#233; de mener plusieurs t&#226;ches de front.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Capacit&#233; &#224; faire preuve d&#8217;initiative et &#224; apprendre de fa&#231;on ind&#233;pendante.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Exigences particuli&#232;res&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;La personne choisie doit obtenir une habilitation de s&#233;curit&#233; (et doit avoir le statut de r&#233;sident canadien depuis au moins 5&amp;nbsp;ans).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Les atouts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ma&#238;trise de Linux.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Connaissance ou exp&#233;rience de l&#8217;environnement Amazon Web Services (AWS).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du d&#233;veloppement Web, des outils d&#8217;alimentation ETL (extraire, transformer et charger) et de l&#8217;&#233;tablissement de rapports.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exp&#233;rience avec les langages de script (Linux Bash, Microsoft Powershell, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des concepts des bases de donn&#233;es comme le mappage des donn&#233;es et la mod&#233;lisation logique et physique des donn&#233;es.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exp&#233;rience pour donner des pr&#233;sentations &#224; divers publics comprenant des intervenants, des Clients, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Les avantages pour vous &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prendre part &#224; notre parcours qui vise &#224; d&#233;velopper la meilleure exp&#233;rience num&#233;rique qui soit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Des garanties &#224; la carte d&#232;s votre premier jour de travail pour r&#233;pondre &#224; vos besoins et &#224; ceux de votre famille.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Des programmes de mieux-&#234;tre qui soutiennent les trois piliers de votre sant&#233;&amp;nbsp;: sant&#233; mentale, physique et financi&#232;re.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Un syst&#232;me de soutien solide pour la formation continue comprenant des cours offerts par l&#8217;entreprise, des acc&#232;s &#224; des plateformes d&#8217;apprentissage en ligne, des occasions de rotation, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Un horaire de travail flexible qui doit inclure une plage horaire habituelle de travail.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Role Summary&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As an Intermediate Cloud Analyst, you will be an essential part of the Cloud Infrastructure &amp;amp; Operations team; a highly recognized group within the Data &amp;amp; Analytics division that plays a direct role in Big Data, Machine Learning and Analytics technologies by designing, building and supporting Analytics infrastructure, and middleware technologies on Cloud platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you do? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand and work with Amazon Web Services (AWS) Platform as a Service (Paas), Software as a Service (SaaS), and Hadoop administration and related technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Evaluate functions and features of cloud services and related technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Involvement with small and medium size infrastructure projects, and participate in projects throughout the entire project lifecycle, and define, manage and track project deliverables using defined technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work closely with other team members, technical/team leads, management, specialized IT areas and application support teams to ensure consistent delivery and quality of platform and cloud services.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintain up-to-date documentation and procedures for all supported cloud-related platforms, and define requirements in cooperation with Developers and other Specialists.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop scripts and functions to support internal processes and improve system performance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Define, document and implement consistent standards and procedures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Share the responsibility of 7X24 rotational on-call duties, after hour change support and disaster recovery support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you need to succeed?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High academic credentials and University level degree in Computer Science, Mathematics, Science or a related field. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 years of experience in Information Technology with high academic credentials in a related field.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand, can describe and can put into action complex concepts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Passion for data and analytics as a career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills with the ability to handle several tasks efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to take initiative and learn independently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Experience that would be nice to have:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Linux.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and/or experience with Amazon Web Services (AWS) environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Web development, Extract, Transform and Load (ETL) and Report development.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scripting languages (Linux Bash, Microsoft Powershell, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of database concepts such as data mapping, logical and physical data modeling.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience giving presentations to a wide variety of audiences including stakeholders, clients, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Being part of our journey in developing the next greatest digital experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A &#8216;dress for the day&#8217; dress code, where you dictate how you dress based on your day.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wellness programs that support the three pillars of your health &#8211; mental, physical and financial.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An extensive support system for continual learning including company-run courses, access to online learning platforms, opportunity for rotations, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A flexible work schedule, so long it includes core working hours.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="thebrightside@sunlife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;56,300/56 300 - 92,900/92 900&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;IT - Technology Services&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;17/02/2022&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Montreal-Quebec/Intermediate-Cloud-Infrastructure-Analyst_JR00052023?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Intermediate Cloud Infrastructure Analyst</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WJFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WCKJ WDKJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WPG- WCH- WIJ- WJJ- WPE- WBH- WFJ- WBAB WAH-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Description du poste&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Le poste d&#8217;analyste interm&#233;diaire, infrastructure infonuagique, est un pilier essentiel de l&#8217;&#233;quipe Op&#233;rations et infrastructure infonuagique. Ce groupe tr&#232;s estim&#233; au sein du secteur Donn&#233;es et analytique joue un r&#244;le crucial en mati&#232;re de m&#233;gadonn&#233;es, d&#8217;apprentissage machine et d&#8217;analytique par la conception, le d&#233;veloppement et l&#8217;entretien des infrastructures d&#8217;analytique et des technologies d&#8217;intergiciels sur les plateformes infonuagiques.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Les fonctions &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Travailler avec les composantes logiciel en tant que service (SaaS) et plateforme en tant que service (PaaS) d&#8217;Amazon Web Services (AWS), l&#8217;administration d&#8217;Hadoop et d&#8217;autres technologies connexes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&#201;valuer les fonctions et les caract&#233;ristiques des services infonuagiques et des technologies connexes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participer &#224; des projets d&#8217;infrastructure de petite et de moyenne envergure tout au long de leur cycle de vie ainsi que d&#233;finir et g&#233;rer les r&#233;sultats attendus, en plus d&#8217;en faire le suivi au moyen de technologies d&#233;finies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborer &#233;troitement avec les autres membres de l&#8217;&#233;quipe, les responsables techniques, les chefs d&#8217;&#233;quipe, la direction, les secteurs des TI sp&#233;cialis&#233;s et les &#233;quipes de soutien des applications pour assurer l&#8217;uniformit&#233; de la prestation et de la qualit&#233; des services infonuagiques.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tenir &#224; jour les documents et les proc&#233;dures pour l&#8217;ensemble des plateformes infonuagiques et d&#233;finir les exigences en collaboration avec d&#8217;autres d&#233;veloppeurs et sp&#233;cialistes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&#201;laborer des scripts et des fonctions pour soutenir les processus internes et am&#233;liorer la performance des syst&#232;mes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;D&#233;finir, consigner et mettre en &#339;uvre des normes et des proc&#233;dures coh&#233;rentes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partager &#224; tour de r&#244;le la responsabilit&#233; des fonctions de garde en tout temps, du soutien des changements apr&#232;s les heures normales de travail et des mises &#224; l&#8217;essai des plans antisinistres.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Les aptitudes pour r&#233;ussir&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent dossier universitaire et dipl&#244;me universitaire en informatique, en math&#233;matiques, en sciences ou dans un domaine connexe. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Connaissance et exp&#233;rience du secteur des technologies de l&#8217;information avec un excellent dossier universitaire dans un domaine connexe.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Capacit&#233; de comprendre, de d&#233;crire et de mettre en pratique des concepts complexes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellentes aptitudes pour la communication verbale et &#233;crite.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Passion pour les donn&#233;es et l&#8217;analytique en tant que carri&#232;re.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent sens de l&#8217;organisation et capacit&#233; de mener plusieurs t&#226;ches de front.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Capacit&#233; &#224; faire preuve d&#8217;initiative et &#224; apprendre de fa&#231;on ind&#233;pendante.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Exigences particuli&#232;res&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;La personne choisie doit obtenir une habilitation de s&#233;curit&#233; (et doit avoir le statut de r&#233;sident canadien depuis au moins 5&amp;nbsp;ans).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Les atouts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ma&#238;trise de Linux.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Connaissance ou exp&#233;rience de l&#8217;environnement Amazon Web Services (AWS).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Connaissance du d&#233;veloppement Web, des outils d&#8217;alimentation ETL (extraire, transformer et charger) et de l&#8217;&#233;tablissement de rapports.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exp&#233;rience avec les langages de script (Linux Bash, Microsoft Powershell, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Connaissance des concepts des bases de donn&#233;es comme le mappage des donn&#233;es et la mod&#233;lisation logique et physique des donn&#233;es.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exp&#233;rience pour donner des pr&#233;sentations &#224; divers publics comprenant des intervenants, des Clients, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Les avantages pour vous &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prendre part &#224; notre parcours qui vise &#224; d&#233;velopper la meilleure exp&#233;rience num&#233;rique qui soit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Des garanties &#224; la carte d&#232;s votre premier jour de travail pour r&#233;pondre &#224; vos besoins et &#224; ceux de votre famille.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Des programmes de mieux-&#234;tre qui soutiennent les trois piliers de votre sant&#233;&amp;nbsp;: sant&#233; mentale, physique et financi&#232;re.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Un syst&#232;me de soutien solide pour la formation continue comprenant des cours offerts par l&#8217;entreprise, des acc&#232;s &#224; des plateformes d&#8217;apprentissage en ligne, des occasions de rotation, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Un horaire de travail flexible qui doit inclure une plage horaire habituelle de travail.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Role Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As an Intermediate Cloud Infrastructure Analyst, you will be an essential part of the Cloud Infrastructure &amp;amp; Operations team; a highly recognized group within the Data &amp;amp; Analytics division that plays a direct role in Big Data, Machine Learning and Analytics technologies by designing, building and supporting Analytics infrastructure, and middleware technologies on Cloud platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you do? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand and work with Amazon Web Services (AWS) Platform as a Service (Paas), Software as a Service (SaaS), and Hadoop administration and related technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Evaluate functions and features of cloud services and related technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Involvement with small and medium size infrastructure projects, and participate in projects throughout the entire project lifecycle, and define, manage and track project deliverables using defined technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work closely with other team members, technical/team leads, management, specialized IT areas and application support teams to ensure consistent delivery and quality of platform and cloud services.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintain up-to-date documentation and procedures for all supported cloud-related platforms, and define requirements in cooperation with Developers and other Specialists.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop scripts and functions to support internal processes and improve system performance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Define, document and implement consistent standards and procedures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Share the responsibility of 7X24 rotational on-call duties, after hour change support and disaster recovery support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What you need to succeed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High academic credentials and University level degree in Computer Science, Mathematics, Science or a related field. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience in Information Technology with high academic credentials in a related field.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understand, can describe and can put into action complex concepts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Passion for data and analytics as a career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong organizational skills with the ability to handle several tasks efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to take initiative and learn independently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unique Requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to receive Security clearance is required for this role [minimum of 5 consecutive years of residency in Canada].&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;a&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with Linux.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity and/or experience with Amazon Web Services (AWS) environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Web development, Extract, Transform and Load (ETL) and Report development.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scripting languages (Linux Bash, Microsoft Powershell, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of database concepts such as data mapping, logical and physical data modeling.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience giving presentations to a wide variety of audiences including stakeholders, clients, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Being part of our journey in developing the next greatest digital experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wellness programs that support the three pillars of your health &#8211; mental, physical and financial.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An extensive support system for continual learning including company-run courses, access to online learning platforms, opportunity for rotations, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A flexible work schedule, so long it includes core working hours.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="thebrightside@sunlife.com opens new window" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WEN2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;56,300/56 300 - 92,900/92 900&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;IT - Technology Services&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;17/02/2022&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/North-York-Ontario/Intermediate-Cloud-Infrastructure-Analyst_JR00051291-1?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item></items>