<items><item><title>Senior Data Scientist</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Role Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Within Sun Life Canada, the Canadian Analytics Centre of Excellence (COE) was launched to support Canadian business units in their journey to leverage data and analytics as a foundational pillar in delivering business value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Reporting to the&lt;b&gt; Director, Analytics Consulting Services&lt;/b&gt; as a &lt;b&gt;Senior Data Scientist&lt;/b&gt; you will focus on supporting Canadian business units in accelerating the growth and application of analytics in driving value. &amp;nbsp;The senior data scientist will leverage practical experience in applying varied data science techniques &amp;amp; offering advice/inputs to help with the design, development and implementation of analytics use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sun Life views success in this role in demonstration of these key attributes:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fierce curiosity&lt;/b&gt;. You are drawn to discovering and leveraging new data and taking on challenging business puzzles. &lt;b&gt;An inquisitive mind.&lt;/b&gt; Driven to ask questions to help lead projects to commercial value and not being afraid that the innovation attempts can and will lead to failing. &lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;A passion for solving problems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; The most successful data scientists&#8217; solution for what the right data to use, they solve using the most suitable (not most advanced) algorithms for the problem at hand and figure out how to execute and deliver with highest efficiency.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;b&gt;Technical skills in both data and computer science.&lt;/b&gt; There are 3 core technical skills we look for: in-depth coding knowledge of an analytical tool(s) (i.e., Python); data science techniques and concepts; working with structured data (SQL) &lt;b&gt;Thirst for learning.&lt;/b&gt; You are a data scientist who is constantly updating their knowledge of data science state-of-the-art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you do?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Apply best in breed data science including descriptive, predictive, machine learning, deep learning and AI techniques from the design to implementation that impacts the business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Focus on Feature Engineering, Model Training and Model Evaluation in addition to data munging / wrangling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Identify the right algorithms and statistical techniques for a specific project as well as the best features for a model.&amp;nbsp; Advise junior members on the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Make business recommendations with effective presentations of findings at multiple levels of stakeholders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;An active contributing member to the analytics community to help foster and grow the data science community at Sun Life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Champion and support diversity and inclusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you need to succeed?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;2+ years experience in developing and implementing data science techniques (predictive, prescriptive, ML etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Comfortable writing complex SQL queries to extract and integrate data from multiple database sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proficient in using one or more statistical programming languages (i.e., Python) for data science&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Big Data Technologies: Hadoop, HDFS, Hive, HBase, Storm, Spark, Kafka&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with deep learning methodologies either in practice or in academia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Effective and concise oral and written storytelling and insights communication skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects in parallel while managing constantly changing deadlines and priorities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to document work and effectively prioritize documentation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BSc/M.S. in a statistical, mathematical, or technical field (i.e., computer science) or equivalent experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Past experience in life insurance/wealth management, or other financial services industry (e.g., retail banking, credit card, property and casualty insurance)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unique Requirements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The candidate selected for this role is required to have special clearance from the Royal Canadian Mounted Police. To see if you are eligible for this clearance, please review the section 201 on the Federal Government site (&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) &#8203;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What\'s in it for you?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill-sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;73,800/73 800 - 124,100/124 100&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;31/10/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Senior-Data-Scientist_JR00044795?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Role Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Sun Life Financial is a leading international financial services organization providing a diverse range of insurance, wealth and asset management solutions to individual and corporate Clients. Canadian Group Benefits business is the largest private payer of healthcare in Canada with over 3 million members. Our goal is to help Canadians lead healthier lives through workplace benefit programs, ensure outstanding experience when they engage with Sun Life and equip them with tools to manage their health needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Group Benefits (GB) Strategy, Digital and Analytics (SDA) team has a mandate to work across functions to deliver insights critical for business decisions, identify growth opportunities and use data to improve health and financial outcomes. The team collaborates closely with Canadian Data &amp;amp; Analytics and Enterprise Services teams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Reporting to AVP, Analytics and Strategy as a Senior Data Scientist, you will accelerate the growth and application of analytics across Group Benefits. You will also leverage practical experience in applying varied data science techniques and design, develop and implement analytics use cases. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you do?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Extract, organize and model the data from structured and unstructured sources including Enterprise Data Lake and SQL Server &#8211; core technologies include &lt;b&gt;Glue, SQL and ETL Development&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Apply best in breed data science methodologies including descriptive, predictive, machine learning, deep learning and AI techniques from design to implementation - core technologies include &lt;b&gt;Python, Graph and Network Analysis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Focus on Feature Engineering, Model Training and Model Evaluation in addition to data wrangling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Identify the right algorithms and statistical techniques to address a use case as well as the best features and optimization techniques for a model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Deploy models at scale in the cloud and schedule refreshes &#8211; core technologies include &lt;b&gt;AWS S3, HUE, HIVE, Cron and SageMaker&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Incorporate best data visualization techniques that surface insights for the end user in a &#8216;blink and think&#8217; manner and enable self-serve capability for the end user &#8211; core technologies include &lt;b&gt;Tableau and Python Seaborn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Provide effective recommendations based on actionable insights &#8211; delivered in a way that is understandable by the business and answers the &#8216;so what?&#8217; question&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Actively contribute to the Sun Life Analytics community to help foster and grow the data science culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Champion and support diversity and inclusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you need to succeed?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3+ years of experience in developing and implementing data science techniques (predictive, prescriptive and neural networks)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Comfortable writing complex SQL and Glue queries to extract and integrate data from multiple data sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proficient in using one or more statistical programming languages (i.e., Python) for data science&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Knowledge of Big Data Technologies: Hadoop, HDFS, Hive, Storm, Spark, and Kafka&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with deep learning methodologies applied in an insurance or financial services industry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong cross-functional collaboration ability and comfort with ambiguity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Effective and concise oral and written storytelling and insights communication skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to work on multiple projects in parallel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;BSc/M.S. in a statistical, mathematical, or technical field (i.e., computer science) or equivalent experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Past experience in Group Benefits and Insurance or Financial Services Industry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unique Requirements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The candidate selected for this role is required to have special Government clearance from the Royal Canadian Mounted Police.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;To see if you are eligible for this clearance, please review the section 201 on the Federal Government site (&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html"&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;http://iss-ssi.pwgsc-tpsgc.gc.ca/msi-ism/ch2-prt1-eng.html&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill-sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;73,800/73 800 - 124,100/124 100&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;11/10/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Senior-Data-Scientist_JR00048757?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Senior Data Scientist</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Role Summary&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Analytics &amp;amp; Insights is a multi-disciplinary center of excellence comprised of savvy and intellectually curious professionals who are on a mission to transform how we apply data and analytics to support Sun Life becoming client-centric. An integral part of the Analytics &amp;amp; Insights organization, the Data Science team works closely with various lines of business to build a Smart Assignment engine by leveraging big data and AI/Machine Learning algorithms!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexibility and an entrepreneurial mindset are critical in this role, as part of your responsibility will be to build quick PoCs in an imperfect way to perfectly test &amp;amp; validate ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you do?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Design and develop AI/Machine Learning models for business operations (Leads Assignment):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; With access to enormous open source, third party and Sunlife data, you would be connecting different data sets and testing different AI algorithms to examine their business value. Once the value is proven, the model needs to be deployed and monitored in our production environment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Research new algorithms, document them, and share your findings with the team:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &amp;nbsp;Data science is a fast-evolving field, every day there is a new algorithm out there that we can use and/or monitor them for future use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Formally apply &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;statistical/scientific&lt;/span&gt; rigors to the problems at hand:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt; As much as we like our gut feelings but for a business to succeed, we need to make sure our solutions are scientifically correct.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Share what you see in the data as a story:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Data on its own can be a bit dull, so we need to make it colorful by connecting the dots and telling a compelling story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Analyze data to support model development and to identify potential areas for improvement:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Data analysis could be about existing challenges, but it may also help identify areas for improvement and bring them to surface to get resolved &#8211; We need both!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work with the team to document data models, architecture, algorithms:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; we work in an Agile environment, but it is not equivalent to no documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you need to succeed?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Minimum of master\'s degree in Statistics, Software Engineering, Mathematics, Econometrics, Physic or equivalent. PhD degree preferred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3 + years of programming experience Python or R&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Go-getter with agile mind set&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Demonstrated data transformation &amp;amp; manipulation experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Deep understanding of machine learning including and supervised and unsupervised models&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Thirst for learning new methodologies and models&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Detail oriented but do not get lost there!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Working experience in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Big data platforms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Agile framework&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;AWS services including SageMaker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Structured vs. Unstructured data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Insurance and finance services industry preferred&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill-sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;73,800/73 800 - 124,100/124 100&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;11/10/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Senior-Data-Scientist_JR00048563-2?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Lead Data Scientist/ Director - Actuarial Analytics</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Role Summary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As one of Sun Life Canada&#8217;s largest business units, Insurance Solutions is responsible for designing and distributing leading-edge life and health insurance products to over 2 million individual retail Clients across Canada.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reporting to the AVP, Innovation and Analytics, the Lead Data Scientist / Director will lead machine learning and predictive analytics initiatives within Insurance Solutions to conceptualize, develop, and operationalize data science solutions for specific use cases across multiple functional areas including underwriting, sales, product management and actuarial.&amp;nbsp; The successful candidate will also provide intellectual leadership on the application of advanced analytics techniques to business problems and coach a high-performing team &lt;/span&gt;of analytics professionals&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;The ideal candidate is a challenge-seeking, intellectually curious, results-oriented analytics leader with a passion for leveraging data to drive business outcomes and a thirst for continuous learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will you do?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead a team to identify, develop, and operationalize high quality, robust machine learning solutions to meet the use cases of key functional areas within Insurance Solutions (e.g. underwriting, sales, product management, actuarial)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead the research, development, and enhancement of existing models (e.g. Sun Life&#8217;s accelerated underwriting model)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Lead the research and evaluation of new data sources, both internal and external; apply machine learning and deep learning techniques to extract actionable insights from available data; write complex SQL queries to extract and integrate data from multiple database sources&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Liaise with senior executives, product managers, actuaries and sales teams, to define use cases and deliver innovative solutions in order to help meet their business growth and profitability objectives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Coach and grow a high-performing team of analytics professionals with clear direction and proactive leadership, strategic assignment of responsibilities, and other training opportunities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What do you need to succeed?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Genuine interest in life insurance and learning the business&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;M.S. or PhD in mathematics, computer science or other relevant fields, or equivalent work experience&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;7+ years of industry experience and expert knowledge in machine learning and data science, with hands-on experience building and deploying statistical / machine learning models&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3+ years experience leading data science projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;3+ years experience in managing and leading a small team of data scientists&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Extensive knowledge of machine learning and deep learning tools and concepts (e.g. Random Forests, Neural Networks, XGBoost), including applications in NLP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience using one or more statistical programming languages (e.g., Python, R) to work with data sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What will be nice to have?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Life and health insurance industry experience, preferably a background in underwriting, distribution, actuarial, or product management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with cloud-based big data tools and platforms: AWS, SageMaker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;In depth understanding of big data technologies: Hadoop, HDFS, Hive, HBase, Storm, Spark, Kafka&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with data analytics and data visualization best practices&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;20 days vacation per year and an innovative sabbatical program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A friendly, collaborative and inclusive culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Being part of our Analytics community, where we share best practices and broaden skill sets&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible Benefits from the day you join to meet the needs of you and your family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Fitness and wellness programs that help you balance work and life and enjoy a healthier lifestyle&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;104,000/104 000 - 171,700/171 700&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Advanced Analytics&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;17/10/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Toronto-Ontario/Lead-Data-Scientist--Director_JR00046916?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item><item><title>Software Developer, Data Platform Engineering</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid12-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid12-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-13" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are as unique as your background, experience and point of view. Here, you&#8217;ll be encouraged, empowered and challenged to be your best self. You\'ll work with dynamic colleagues - experts in their fields - who are eager to share their knowledge with you. Your leaders will inspire and help you reach your potential and soar to new heights. Every day, you\'ll have new and exciting opportunities to make life brighter for our Clients - who are at the heart of everything we do. Discover how you can make a difference in the lives of individuals, families and communities around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Role Summary:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Data &amp;amp; Analytics Engineering our team is focused on enabling analytics at Sun Life through delivering robust, scalable, secure and reusable platforms and services that operate within our Enterprise Cloud, API and DevOps environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are looking for a software developer to join our fast paced and high performing Data Engineering team to provide data and analytics capabilities to our business. You will use your engineering prowess and experience building out data platforms to help us deliver core data and application pipelines, frameworks and infrastructure that enable our business to provide insights and respond to the needs of our clients in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Sun Life values diversity and does not discriminate based on background or personal experience. We encourage everyone with a passion for developing great software to apply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;What will you do?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work within an Agile pod to build core data and analytics platforms, applications and self-service capabilities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build robust data pipelines that integrate data from various sources to enable analytics in our Cloud environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build and deploy APIs and highly available services that adhere to internal governance controls and deployment platforms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work closely with our data science and analytics partners to deliver useful integration and delivery pipelines to facilitate various analytics use-cases like recommendation systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Operate in a Shift-Left testing environment and prioritize writing efficient, tested and clear code&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participate in improving the supportability and transparency of the applications and services we build by creating clear and comprehensive documentation, monitoring/alert systems and centralized logging&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;What you need to succeed? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelors Degree in Computer Science or Technology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience working with the following:&amp;nbsp;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scala, Java 8+ and Python3 programming languages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Docker and &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;container-orchestration&lt;/span&gt; tools like Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jenkins, Artifactory, and Ansible&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;traditional Big Data suite (e.g. HDFS, &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;MapReduce/Spark/etc.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;streaming technologies, such as Kafka&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SQL databases, such as Postgres&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;a Cloud Service Provider (e.g. Amazon Web Services, Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the Microservice Architectures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with various NoSQL database designs (e.g. Key-Value, Document, Wide-Column, Graph, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of basic Machine Learning concepts (e.g. classification versus regression, bias-variance tradeoff, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Preferred Skills&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills (both written and oral), combined with strong interpersonal skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with either Kanban or Scrum working methodologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;This role requires reliability check, this means that you have resided in Canada for the last 5 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;What&#8217;s in it for you:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Competitive salary and bonus structure influenced by market range data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Pension, stock and savings programs to help build and enhance your future financial security&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;An environment of continuous learning and improvement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Flexible hours and periodic work from home options&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;LI- SJ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Base Pay range is for the primary location for which the job is posted.&amp;nbsp; It may vary depending on the work location of the successful candidate or other factors.&amp;nbsp; In addition to Base Pay, eligible Sun Life employees participate in various incentive plans, payment under which is discretionary and subject to individual and company performance.&amp;nbsp; Certain sales focused roles have sales incentive plans based on individual or group sales results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Diversity and inclusion have always been at the core of our values at Sun Life. A diverse workforce with wide perspectives and creative ideas benefits our clients, the communities where we operate and all of us as colleagues. We welcome applications from qualified individuals from all backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Persons with disabilities who need accommodation in the application process or those needing job postings in an alternative format may e-mail a request to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="mailto:thebrightside@sunlife.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;thebrightside@sunlife.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Sun Life we strive to create a flexible work environment where our employees are empowered to do their best work. Several flexible work options are available and can be discussed throughout the selection process depending on the role requirements and individual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We thank all applicants for showing an interest in this position. Only those selected for an interview will be contacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Salary Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;55,500/55 500 - 91,600/91 600&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Category:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;IT - Technology Services&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Posting End Date:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;28/10/2021&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://sunlife.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Experienced-Jobs/job/Waterloo-Ontario/Software-Developer--Data-Platform-Engineering_JR00047123-3?utm_source=Vector_Institute</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298821/Logo.png</logo><company>Sun Life Financial</company></item></items>