<items><item><title>CONTRACTS MANAGER / LEGAL COUNSEL</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="ats-description"&gt;Location: Toronto, Canada&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales people architect solutions that support 85 million mainline and suburban passenger journeys, worldwide, every day. Our Rail Signalling and Communication systems are used on metro lines across major cities, and 72,000 kms of route, 52,000 trains per day in 16 countries are controlled by our Traffic Management Systems. Together We deployed the first-ever nationwide ticketing system which processes over 50 million ticketing transactions in 100 cities daily.&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales provides world-leading Communications-Based Train Control (CBTC) and interlocking for mass rail transit applications globally. The Centre of Competence for Urban Rail Signalling is located right before you at mid-town Toronto. As the largest office in Canada, we house a department for every step of the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC)! This includes Software, Hardware, Systems Design, Verification &amp;amp; Validation, Operations, etc. The supporting corporate shared services teams in Finance, Human Resources and IT is also located at the office. Our office space was designed to provide a sustainable, healthy workplace that expresses TRSS&#8217;s brand while increasing collaboration. Features include Greenguard furniture, EnergyStar appliances, low-emitting adhesives, sealants, and sliding glass doors on internal offices provide daylight and views to the outside. Come join the big Transport family, here in Toronto!&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Contract Manager / Legal Counsel is required to manage the bids and proposals cycle for the Contracts group: to be responsible for risk identification, risk mitigation recommendations, preparation of compliance statements and sales contracts and related agreements. To ensure compliance and governance procedures are implemented in the bids and proposals cycle.&amp;nbsp; To draft and negotiate terms and conditions to ensure protection of company interests and the preservation of project profitability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Accountabilities:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To review RFPs and customer contracts to identify and prioritize legal and commercial risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To develop contractual positions and provide contract interpretation to the bids and proposals team, project team and senior management.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To prepare contract compliance matrices, risk assessment questionnaires and other pre-bid documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To manage the development and implementation of a negotiation strategy for contract negotiations, from pre-award to execution;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To draft and negotiate contractual documentation including preliminary agreements, intra-unit agreements and customer and/or supplier contracts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;To ensure compliance with Thales governance policies for new business contracts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liaise directly to bids &amp;amp; proposals team, finance, legal and other departments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liaise directly with risk management analysts, brokers and sureties in connection with all contract bonding and insurance related matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;International travel to Customers&#8217; facilities as required representing Contracts in the discussion and negotiation of commercial/contractual issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oversees large, complex contracts held both locally with the Canadian government and/or Canadian business, as well as internationally.&amp;nbsp; Manages risk associated with each contract; ensures all risks associated with operations is anticipated, identified and managed.&amp;nbsp; Participates in negotiations as required.&amp;nbsp; Resolves legal points of contention with customer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Works positively with other specialist groups (Finance, Bids, Legal, Tax etc) within a matrix organization to develop complex bids and proposals as part of a multi-functional bid team with the common objective of winning new and profitable orders;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Post-secondary education- in Law, engineering, business or equivalent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minimum 3-5 years experience in a complex international engineering or high-technology environment or equivalent or in house legal department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Legal concepts underlying commercial contracts including claims management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent communication, presentation and inter-personal skills with international cultural awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Financial concepts underlying commercial contracts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ability to assimilate different commercial approaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strong English writing capabilities, particularly with respect to the drafting of legal and commercial provisions in proposals and contracts, is a mandatory qualification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Negotiation skills and ability to effectively reach negotiated compromises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organize and prioritize contractual and commercial risks and issues&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Able to work independently as well as part of a team environment;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Able to perform detailed analysis and drafting as well as appreciate the broad business and strategic context&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Able to identify key commercial and legal risks, assess degree of severity and probability and articulate clearly to senior management in both written and presentation form, together with proposed mitigations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Able to represent the company professionally and with competence in negotiations with international clientele.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Able to adapt to different contractual and commercial approaches, and navigate cultural norms, to arrive at negotiated compromises within approved parameters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This position requires direct or indirect access to hardware, software, technology or technical data controlled under the Canadian Export Control List and/or the US the Export Administration Regulations (EAR). All applicants must be eligible, or able to obtain authorization, for such access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Additional language skill preferred (written and oral).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Thales is an equal opportunity employer which values diversity and inclusivity in the workplace. Thales is committed to providing accommodations in all parts of the interview process. Applicants selected for an interview who require accommodation are asked to advise accordingly upon the invitation for an interview. We will work with you to meet your needs. All accommodation information provided will be treated as confidential and used only for the purpose of providing an accessible candidate experience.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://jobs.thalesgroup.com/job/toronto/contracts-manager-legal-counsel/1766/11242059456</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/298823/thales-logo_1_.jpg</logo><company>Thales</company></item></items>