<items><item><title>Senior Data Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WFFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WHJJ WIJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WME- WEH- WFH- WMC- WOE- WBH- WAAB WNE-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid9-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You will be responsible for &lt;span&gt;designing and implementing data models and ETL pipelines&lt;/span&gt; to meet product requirements, design of product functions, troubleshooting and resolving product defects, unit and integration testing. Active interaction with internal customers, other developers, Quality Assurance, Business System Analysts is an integral part of the role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;About the Role:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;In the role of Sr. Data Engineer you will:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Participate in project/work planning sessions: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;To analyze and understand requirements to the level of being able to contribute to their creation, in collaboration with capability/product and/or business owners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work in a hands-on data engineering role in a team-based cross-functional environment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Develop and deliver&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Integrate applications per specification and translate technical requirements into application code and modules&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Approach development work with a DevOps and continuous integration mindset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ensure consistency with cloud architectural guiding principles for assigned projects&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Develop prototype or "proof of concept" implementations of projects where the technical solution is unknown or unproven&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proactive in raising problems, identifying solutions and giving/receiving feedback&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Assist in identifying and correcting software performance bottlenecks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be collaborative&lt;/b&gt;: Work in a highly collaborative and dynamic agile team environment with multiple levels of technology staff across various geographical locations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Coach and mentor&lt;/b&gt;: Providing technical expertise and peer code reviews to other team members and assist team leads and project managers in work break down and story planning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;About You &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You\'re a fit for Sr. Data Engineer if you have:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s in computer science or equivalent work experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;7+ years of experience in application development with demonstrable, proven expertise in design and development of high volume, high velocity data ingestion, complex data transformation using traditional ETL technologies or modern data ingestion/processing technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Minimum 4 years of experience working with relational databases like Oracle, Postgres or similar using SQL. Should have hands on experience in writing performant queries/procedures handling complex functionalities. Experience in NoSQL databases and dealing with unstructured data will be good to have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Hands on experience in developing data warehousing and big data analytics applications using big data frameworks like Hadoop, Spark and/or Flink and leveraging services such as AWS EMR or Google DataProc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong understanding of concepts of ETL, ELT and data modeling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hands-on experience in development of cloud native applications in Google Cloud.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hands-on experience in BigQuery / Google DataProc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Exposure to reporting via looker would be an advantage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Professional Google Cloud certification would be good to have.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Preferred familiarity with SQL-on-Hadoop technologies such as Spark SQL, Hive, and/or Presto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Minimum 2 year of strong experience in python.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Programming experience in languages such as Java, C# etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience in orchestration tools like Apache Airflow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience in troubleshooting performance issues resulted from high volume data during processing from upstream &amp;amp; serving to the downstream applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Prefer experience working with Linux or Unix based environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Other skills required:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Proven strong analytical design, problem solving and trouble-shooting skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong understanding of Cloud computing Technologies and related emerging technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Highly accountable for meeting all commitments and deadlines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Effective communication skills, both written and verbal for technical and non-technical audiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Must be able to work independently as well as collaboratively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Drive for continuous process improvement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it For You?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Thomson Reuters, our people are our greatest assets. Here are some of the benefits we offer for your personal and professional growth:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;On-the-job coaching &amp;amp; learning, tuition reimbursement, exposure to leading-edge technology&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Career growth - ability to work on multiple projects and/or with various teams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Access to Hackathons, Unconferences, Harvard Manage Mentor and more, we offer learning opportunities for everyone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Flexible work arrangements, comprehensive health coverage that&#8217;s effective day one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Perks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Social events &amp;amp; activities, employee discount programs through corporate perks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Flexibility&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: We\'ve been named as one of Forbes, Best Companies for Work/Life Balance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Global Opportunities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&amp;nbsp; We have employees in over 90 countries, working across 3 different industries&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Your wellbeing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: &amp;nbsp;We offer a program that focuses on making our lives healthier&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Accessibility&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a global business, we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WOK2"&gt;Opportunity/Affirmative&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Action Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protect yourself from fraudulent job postings &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.thomsonreuters.com/content/dam/ewp-m/documents/careers/en/pdf/onboarding/fake_job_posting_scam_careers_site.pdf"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;to know more.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://thomsonreuters.com"&gt;thomsonreuters.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External_Career_Site/job/CAN-Toronto-120-Bremner-Blvd/Lead-Data-Analytics-Engineer_JREQ144150</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/294572/tr_v_lg_rgb_ps.png</logo><company>Thomson Reuters</company></item><item><title>Data Governance Analyst</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WFFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WHJJ WIJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WME- WEH- WFH- WMC- WOE- WBH- WAAB WNE-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The &lt;b&gt;Data Governance Analyst role&lt;/b&gt; within the Commercial Data Office will be responsible for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;developing and implementing data standards, guaranteeing metadata is captured correctly, and creating methods for monitoring and reporting any data incidents. The Data Governance analyst will monitor applications to ensure they are complying to data governance procedures. They may also create and maintain common business glossaries for data and the tools or methods that support data standards for an organization.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the Role:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Perform data profiling and database structure/model research in order to understand relevant data elements along with their definitions and use.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participate in data governance policy and standard creation, management, and analyzing potential impacts of policy choices under consideration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Document and maintain data standards, partnering with functional and business data owners to map existing commercial data structures, usage, and common definitions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, build, and execute efficient and accurate control structures to assess data quality and compliance to data governance policy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide consultative support for commercial data clients, advising on policies, standards, and guidelines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support the Data Governance team in establishing Working groups, as needed to drive consistency and decisioning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support the Data Governance team in establishing and operating the company&#8217;s critical data forums (data councils, working groups, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drive adoption of the company&#8217;s data governance focused policies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About You:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s degree required with 3+ years of experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about the benefits of accurate and actionable data, you drive consistency and enjoy partnering with others to accomplish the task&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are a solutions-oriented critical thinker&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have technical knowledge and experience in data management, data governance, and/or data quality&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comfortable leading team meetings and possess strong influencing and networking skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You demonstrate the ability to translate business issues and requirements into actionable plans, and to deliver against those plans&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have the exceptional ability to make timely and effective decisions to meet fluid deadlines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have the capability to work autonomously and make independent decisions to meet deliverables with minimal oversight&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are passionate about continuous improvement with a strong desire to continue learning in order to stay relevant to business changes and industry trends&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can effectively handle and maintain confidential information&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have at a minimum basic proficiency in SQL with a thorough understanding of data and systems\' infrastructures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge/experience in Alteryx preferred&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expert level Excel user&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proficient in BI tools such as Tableau&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;What\'s in it For You&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;At Thomson Reuters, our people are our greatest assets. Here are some of the benefits we offer for your personal and professional growth:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: On-the-job coaching &amp;amp; learning, tuition reimbursement, exposure to leading-edge technology, LinkedIn learning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Benefits&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Flexible work arrangements, comprehensive health coverage that\'s effective day one&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Perks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Social events &amp;amp; activities, employee discount programs through corporate perks, 16 hours of paid volunteer time off yearly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Accessibility&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a global business, we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WOK2"&gt;Opportunity/Affirmative&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Action Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://thomsonreuters.com" target="_blank"&gt;thomsonreuters.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External_Career_Site/job/USA-Eagan-610-Opperman-Dr/Data-Governance-Analyst_JREQ142249</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/294572/tr_v_lg_rgb_ps.png</logo><company>Thomson Reuters</company></item><item><title>Data Architect</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WFFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WHJJ WIJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WME- WEH- WFH- WMC- WOE- WBH- WAAB WNE-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are responsible for designing and delivering core technology platforms that provide tools for editorially enhancing and delivering content to our customers.&amp;nbsp; We are looking for a motivated and innovative &lt;span&gt;Data Architect&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; In this role, you will work across geographical boundaries with all levels of software engineers, technical management, and business partners.&amp;nbsp; You will set the data architectural direction for projects delivering new and re-engineered functionality.&amp;nbsp; The ideal candidate will have experience in making technology decisions on large, enterprise-scale software development programs.&amp;nbsp;The candidate will also have extensive skills in the areas of design, development, mentoring and directing co-workers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About the Role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In this opportunity as a Data Architect, you will:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Design and deliver:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Creates the information architecture vision and strategy for the assets under the purview of the group&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Defines the group&#8217;s governance and standards to deliver a cohesive information architecture for the organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Delivers innovative and elegant information solutions that drive growth, and leverage to ensure faster time-to-market&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Translates user requirements and business use cases to conceptual, logical, and physical data models and workflow processes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Translates a business glossary into logical and physical data models, and coach/ supports data modelers and engineers in their development/ testing/ implementation effort.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Identify appropriate sources for external teams&#8217; (R&amp;amp;D, Product Management, Editorial, Technology and other Content organizations) data needs, create the necessary data mapping and transformation rules, with a focus on business objectives and processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensures solutions meet the compliance and security needs of TR&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be Collaborative:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Communicates designs and solutions through formal and informal means to business unit executives, technology management, peers and development staff, and other colleagues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Coach and mentor:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mentor junior staff in Data Modeling and other Information Architecture activities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be curious and innovative:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assists in the technology decisions for &lt;span&gt;data strategy, workflow processes, and infrastructure&lt;/span&gt; for a wide range of system solutions for the Thomson Reuters Editorial and Content Operations teams.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About You&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You\'re a fit for the role of&lt;b&gt; Data Architect&lt;/b&gt; if you have:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;5+ years&#8217; experience as a Data Modeler/ Data Architect, in an integrated business and IT collaborative environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Combination of strategic thinking and detail orientation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to balance being inquisitive, curious, continuously learning, and realistic vs. visionary, technology savvy, and business orientation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent critical thinking, troubleshooting, and problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to operate across organizational boundaries and to influence all stakeholders, (e.g., technology staff, business partners, and vendors) having an impact on the community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expert-level proficiency in data modeling for relational, dimensional, and big data platforms. Experience with a broad range of data schemas (e.g., ontologies, taxonomies, DTDs etc.), as well as strong SQL skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Additional broad experience in enterprise use of the following technologies: Messaging Technologies (e.g., IBM MQ, Kafka), Big Data (Hadoop, HDFS, HBase, Spark), CSS, XML (DOM, SAX), DHTML/ XHTML/ HTML5, Web Services, Cognitive Computing, Classification, Machine Learning, NLP, NLG, Public Cloud (AWS &amp;amp; MS Azure), &amp;amp; MS Teams Foundation Server/Azure DevOps&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal skills supported by exceptional written and oral communication skills: strong hands-on documentation experience and collaboration skills working across geographical sites.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Agile software design methodologies and tools.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it For You?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Thomson Reuters, our people are our greatest assets. Here are some of the benefits we offer for your personal and professional growth:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;On-the-job coaching &amp;amp; learning, tuition reimbursement, exposure to leading-edge technology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Career growth - ability to work on multiple projects and/or with various teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access to Hackathons, Unconferences, Harvard Manage Mentor and more, we offer learning opportunities for everyone&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Flexible work arrangements, comprehensive health coverage that&#8217;s effective day one&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Perks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Social events &amp;amp; activities, employee discount programs through corporate perks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Flexibility&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: We\'ve been named as one of Forbes, Best Companies for Work/Life Balance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Global Opportunities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&amp;nbsp; We have employees in over 90 countries, working across 3 different industries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Your wellbeing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: &amp;nbsp;We offer a program that focuses on making our lives healthier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Accessibility&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a global business, we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WOK2"&gt;Opportunity/Affirmative&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Action Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://thomsonreuters.com" target="_blank"&gt;thomsonreuters.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External_Career_Site/job/CAN-Toronto-120-Bremner-Blvd/Data-Architect_JREQ141040-1</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/294572/tr_v_lg_rgb_ps.png</logo><company>Thomson Reuters</company></item></items>