<items><item><title>Sr. Data Architect</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are responsible for designing and delivering core technology platforms that provide tools for editorially enhancing and delivering content to our customers.&amp;nbsp; We are looking for a motivated and innovative &lt;span&gt;Data Architect&lt;/span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; In this role, you will work across geographical boundaries with all levels of software engineers, technical management, and business partners.&amp;nbsp; You will set the data architectural direction for projects delivering new and re-engineered functionality.&amp;nbsp; The ideal candidate will have experience in making technology decisions on large, enterprise-scale software development programs.&amp;nbsp;The candidate will also have extensive skills in the areas of design, development, mentoring and directing co-workers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About the Role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In this opportunity as a Sr. Data Architect, you will:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Design and deliver:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Creates the information architecture vision and strategy for the assets under the purview of the group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Defines the group&#8217;s governance and standards to deliver a cohesive information architecture for the organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Delivers innovative and elegant information solutions that drive growth, and leverage to ensure faster time-to-market&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Translates user requirements and business use cases to conceptual, logical, and physical data models and workflow processes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Translates a business glossary into logical and physical data models, and coach/ supports data modelers and engineers in their development/ testing/ implementation effort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Identify appropriate sources for external teams&#8217; (R&amp;amp;D, Product Management, Editorial, Technology and other Content organizations) data needs, create the necessary data mapping and transformation rules, with a focus on business objectives and processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ensures solutions meet the compliance and security needs of TR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be Collaborative:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Communicates designs and solutions through formal and informal means to business unit executives, technology management, peers and development staff, and other colleagues&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Coach and mentor:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Mentor junior staff in Data Modeling and other Information Architecture activities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be curious and innovative:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Assists in the technology decisions for &lt;span&gt;data strategy, workflow processes, and infrastructure&lt;/span&gt; for a wide range of system solutions for the Thomson Reuters Editorial and Content Operations teams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About You&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You\'re a fit for the role of&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Sr. Data Architect if you have:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;5+ years&#8217; experience as a Data Modeler/ Data Architect, in an integrated business and IT collaborative environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Combination of strategic thinking and detail orientation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Demonstrated ability to balance being inquisitive, curious, continuously learning, and realistic vs. visionary, technology savvy, and business orientation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Excellent critical thinking, troubleshooting, and problem-solving skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to operate across organizational boundaries and to influence all stakeholders, (e.g., technology staff, business partners, and vendors) having an impact on the community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Expert-level proficiency in data modeling for relational, dimensional, and big data platforms. Experience with a broad range of data schemas (e.g., ontologies, taxonomies, DTDs etc.), as well as strong SQL skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Additional broad experience in enterprise use of the following technologies: Messaging Technologies (e.g., IBM MQ, Kafka), Big Data (Hadoop, HDFS, HBase, Spark), CSS, XML (DOM, SAX), DHTML/ XHTML/ HTML5, Web Services, Cognitive Computing, Classification, Machine Learning, NLP, NLG, Public Cloud (AWS &amp;amp; MS Azure), &amp;amp; MS Teams Foundation Server/Azure DevOps&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Strong interpersonal skills supported by exceptional written and oral communication skills: strong hands-on documentation experience and collaboration skills working across geographical sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with Agile software design methodologies and tools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it For You?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Thomson Reuters, our people are our greatest assets. Here are some of the benefits we offer for your personal and professional growth:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;On-the-job coaching &amp;amp; learning, tuition reimbursement, exposure to leading-edge technology&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Career growth - ability to work on multiple projects and/or with various teams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Access to Hackathons, Unconferences, Harvard Manage Mentor and more, we offer learning opportunities for everyone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Flexible work arrangements, comprehensive health coverage that&#8217;s effective day one&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Perks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Social events &amp;amp; activities, employee discount programs through corporate perks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Flexibility&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: We\'ve been named as one of Forbes, Best Companies for Work/Life Balance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Global Opportunities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;:&amp;nbsp; We have employees in over 90 countries, working across 3 different industries&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Your wellbeing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: &amp;nbsp;We offer a program that focuses on making our lives healthier&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;#LI-JS1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accessibility&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a global business, we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;Opportunity/Affirmative&lt;/span&gt; Action Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protect yourself from fraudulent job postings &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.thomsonreuters.com/content/dam/ewp-m/documents/careers/en/pdf/onboarding/fake_job_posting_scam_careers_site.pdf"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to know more.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://thomsonreuters.com"&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;https://thomsonreuters.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External_Career_Site/job/CAN-Toronto-120-Bremner-Blvd/Data-Architect_JREQ141040-1?SourceID-APPLICANT_SOURCE-3-713</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/294572/tr_v_lg_rgb_ps.png</logo><company>Thomson Reuters</company></item><item><title>Associate Architect/Architect - Data Engineering</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Associate Architect&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a technologist at Thomson Reuters, you will help shape the global knowledge economy. Our technology ensures that professionals around the world have the answers they need. You will work with the brightest thinkers on diverse projects, creating next-generation solutions that deliver powerful results. As the world&#8217;s top provider of intelligent information, we want your unique perspective to create the solutions that advance our business&#8212;and your career. Bring your passion for innovation, and together we&#8217;ll make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About the Role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;In this role you will:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be a Technical Leader&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &#8211; provide thought leadership and guidance in setting the architecture vision and direction for an extendible and maintainable set of editorial system and publishing capabilities. Work with technology teams and beyond to realize their &lt;span&gt;implementation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be a&amp;nbsp;Team Player&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8211;&amp;nbsp;ability to work in a &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;collaborative&amp;nbsp;and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; inclusive &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;team-oriented&amp;nbsp;environment,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; partner with cross functional and remote teams, draw out strong design ideas from diverse teams and high performing engineers, and translate requirements into actionable architecture&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be an Effective &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;Communicator&amp;nbsp;&#8211;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;ability&amp;nbsp;to concisely and completely &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;articulate&amp;nbsp;complex&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; technical issues; ability to target your audience, actively listen, and value diverse ideas&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be an&amp;nbsp;Agile Person&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8211;&amp;nbsp;with a strong sense of urgency and a desire to work in a fast-paced dynamic environment to deliver solutions against strict timelines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be&amp;nbsp;Curious &amp;amp; Innovative&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8211; ability to question the status quo.&amp;nbsp; Continuously update yourself with&amp;nbsp;industry trends, next &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;generation&amp;nbsp;technology,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and software development best practices.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About You&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in software design, methodologies (especially Agile), and tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broad experience in enterprise-class system, full-stack, design and development including use of the following technologies: Java, Front-End Technologies (e.g., JavaScript, jQuery, Angular), XML (DOM, SAX), DHTML/XHTML/HTML5, CSS, Database and SQL (e.g., Oracle, SQL Server), as well as NoSQL, Messaging Technologies (e.g., IBM MQ, Kafka), APIs (e.g., REST, SOAP), Web Services (e.g, Tomcat), MS ADO, Eclipse, Ant, Maven, Junit&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must be an excellent communicator when speaking, writing, and in diagramming&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills with an ability to operate across organizational boundaries and to influence business stakeholders, as well as technology peers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advanced analytical skills with the ability to synthesize business requirements with technology capabilities to produce coherent technical designs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to quickly learn and analyze new technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have 5+years relevant experience in large distributed systems, including 1+ years architecture/ design experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You may also have:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cloud experience (AWS or Azure)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in Cognitive Computing (e.g, Machine Learning, NLP, Classification, Clustering)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Architecting API-first solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in processing large volumes of data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;System load and scale testing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it For You&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Thomson Reuters, our people are our greatest assets. Here are some of the benefits we offer for your personal and professional growth:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: On-the-job coaching &amp;amp; learning, tuition reimbursement, exposure to cutting-edge technology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: Flexible work arrangements, comprehensive health coverage that&#8217;s effective day one&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Perks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: Social events &amp;amp; activities, employee discount programs through corporate perks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;#LI-JS1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accessibility&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a global business, we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;Opportunity/Affirmative&lt;/span&gt; Action Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protect yourself from fraudulent job postings &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.thomsonreuters.com/content/dam/ewp-m/documents/careers/en/pdf/onboarding/fake_job_posting_scam_careers_site.pdf"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to know more.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://thomsonreuters.com"&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;https://thomsonreuters.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External_Career_Site/job/CAN-Toronto-120-Bremner-Blvd/Associate-Architect_JREQ145372?SourceID-APPLICANT_SOURCE-3-713</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/294572/tr_v_lg_rgb_ps.png</logo><company>Thomson Reuters</company></item><item><title>Senior Applied Research Scientist - NLP</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Are you excited about working at the forefront of applied research in an industry setting?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="http://tr.com/ai-jobs"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thomson Reuters Labs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;in&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Toronto &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;and &lt;b&gt;Minneapolis&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;is seeking scientists with a passion for solving problems using state-of-the-art Information Retrieval, Machine Learning and Natural Language Processing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;What does&amp;nbsp;Thomson Reuters Labs&amp;nbsp;do?&lt;/b&gt; We experiment, we build, we deliver. We support the organization and our customers through applied research and the development of new products and technologies. TR Labs innovates collaboratively across our core segments in Legal, Tax &amp;amp; Accounting, Government, and Reuters News. We undertake a diverse portfolio of projects today while investing in long-term research for the future.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;a&amp;nbsp;scientist&amp;nbsp;in&amp;nbsp;Labs,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; you will be part of a global interdisciplinary team of experts. &lt;/span&gt;We hire specialists across a variety of AI research areas, as well as Engineering and Design, to drive the company\'s digital transformation&lt;span&gt;. &lt;span&gt;TR Labs is known for delivering innovative AI products that serve Thomson Reuters customers in new and exciting ways.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;More about Thomson Reuters Labs - &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://nam02.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Ftr.com%2Fai-jobs&amp;amp;data=04%7C01%7CSuneet.Joshi%40thomsonreuters.com%7C3b86dda15ceb421f0fcf08d91c8d74c1%7C62ccb8646a1a4b5d8e1c397dec1a8258%7C0%7C0%7C637572216146487262%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C1000&amp;amp;sdata=bH8feQMWWotDBf7sA032WPZnvfAkxg9DCJnpXY90grY%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;http://tr.com/ai-jobs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;In this opportunity &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;you will:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experiment and Develop:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;You will drive the end-to-end model development lifecycle, championing&lt;/span&gt; best practices to ensure reproducible research and well-managed software delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Collaborate:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Working on a collaborative cross-functional team, you will share information, value diverse ideas, and partner effectively with colleagues across the globe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Delivery:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;You will be accountable for timely, well-managed deliverables.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Innovate&lt;/b&gt;: You will be empowered to try new approaches and learn new technologies. &lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;You will&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;foster&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;innovative ideas to solve real-world challenges.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Inspire:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;You will be a proactive communicator who is excited to share your work. You will be articulate and compelling in describing ideas to both technical and non-technical audiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are a fit for the role &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;if you have:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ph.D.&amp;nbsp;in a relevant discipline &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;or&amp;nbsp;Master\'s&amp;nbsp;plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; a comparable level of experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;At least 5+ years of relevant experience building&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;IR/NLP/ML&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;systems&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Solid software engineering skills for prototyping&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience as a technical leader, coordinating and guiding the work of others&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Preferred qualifications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;8+ years of academic or industry experience building&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;IR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;NLP&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;systems with the demonstrated ability to translate cutting edge research into working applications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Demonstrated ability to translate customer needs into well-structured research/project plans&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Proficiency in&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Python&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Java&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;, or&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Scala&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;and experience delivering minimum viable products in a large enterprise environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Outstanding communication, organization, and data-driven decision making&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Publications at relevant venues such as ACL, EMNLP, NAACL, NeurIPS, ICLR, SIGIR, KDD or similar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What\'s in it for you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;At Thomson Reuters, our people are our greatest assets. In addition to rewarding and challenging work with exceptional colleagues, we offer the following benefits for your personal and professional growth:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: On-the-job coaching &amp;amp; learning, tuition reimbursement, exposure to leading-edge technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Our&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Scientists and Engineers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;get to play with big data sets to discover new products, capabilities, and insights for our customers. Thomson Reuters is most well-known for the globally respected Reuters News agency, but our company is also the leading source of information for legal, corporate and tax professionals. We have over 60,000 TBs worth of legal, regulatory, news, and tax data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Flexible work arrangements, comprehensive health coverage effective day one, savings and investment plans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Perks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Social events &amp;amp; activities, employee discount programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Social Impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Paid time off for volunteering virtually or in your community&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;#LI-SJ1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accessibility&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a global business, we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;Opportunity/Affirmative&lt;/span&gt; Action Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protect yourself from fraudulent job postings &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.thomsonreuters.com/content/dam/ewp-m/documents/careers/en/pdf/onboarding/fake_job_posting_scam_careers_site.pdf"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to know more.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://thomsonreuters.com"&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;https://thomsonreuters.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External_Career_Site/job/CAN-Toronto-120-Bremner-Blvd/Senior-Applied-Research-Scientist---NLP_JREQ145720?SourceID-APPLICANT_SOURCE-3-713</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/294572/tr_v_lg_rgb_ps.png</logo><company>Thomson Reuters</company></item><item><title>Lead Software Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid10-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-11" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Thomson Reuters is the Answer Company&#8482;. We provide authoritative content, advanced technologies and human expertise to help our customers find trusted answers. We enable professionals in the financial and risk, legal, tax and accounting, and media markets to make the decisions that matter most, all powered by the world\'s most trusted news organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lead Software Engineer &#8211; Lynx Insight, News Technology&lt;/b&gt;: Software Engineering Lead to help create an analytics &amp;amp; machine learning platform to support opportunities through the expansion of investable insights within the Reuters news content &#8211; thru signal detection, analytics, noise reduction and news automation, as well as to support Reuters&#8217; journalist throughout the News production lifecycle &#8211; from discovery of news worthy events to researching the story to publication, and all that at the speed of light in an increasingly competitive landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are seeking an experienced engineering lead to help maintain and improve the Lynx Insight ecosystem. You will bring hands-on knowledge about the emerging field of streaming analytics and machine learning, and will have experience in deploying those technologies for the benefit of the business. Ability to collaborate with and influence a team of talented engineers, data scientists, R&amp;amp;D and subject matter experts will be essential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About the role;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a Lead Software Engineer you will:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;A savvy technical leader. You will lead and support a seasoned &amp;amp; talented engineering team and partner with business owners, product managers and enable successful delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Design and lead:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You will lead projects with significant risk and complexity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You are a team player, focusing on results, collaboration and winning as a team. You are a great partner for other teams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Your team consistently delivers and delights its customers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Follow agile methodology:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;An "agile" person. You can work with different SDLC methodologies &#8211; Agile, waterfall and hybrid approaches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You desire a fast-paced, dynamic environment. You can operate with ambiguous requirements and changing priorities, all while having a strong sense of ownership of the solutions that you deliver&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mentor and coach:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You are a mentor and you help your team realize their full potential&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;About You:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You are a fit for the role if you have:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Education:&lt;/b&gt; Minimum Bachelor Degree in Computer Science and Engineering or equivalent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requirements&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;7+ yrs in Software Development, 2+ yrs experience in BigData technologies and Analytics platforms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;2+yrs hands-on experience working with AWS and AWS services like AWS Lambda, API Gateway, DynamoDB etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;Node.js/Java/Scala/Python/MySQL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience partnering with internal business owners&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability and passion to learn new technologies quickly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience in service-oriented architecture, and distributed scalable systems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Ability to lead or conduct technology evaluations against specific objectives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience working with global teams&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Team player and self-starter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Desired&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with machine learning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with Natural Language Processing and Natural Language Generation technologies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;DevOps Experience in AWS, Git, Jenkins, Maven, Docker, Shell scripting a big plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Experience with Statistical modelling, and programming language R a big plus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it For You?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You will join our inclusive culture of world-class talent, where we are committed to your personal and professional growth through:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Hybrid Work Model: Currently, as part of our COVID-19 response, our employees are working remotely and following local COVID-19 bylaws and guidelines with the majority of our offices planning to remain remote throughout 2021. Upon return, we will embrace a hybrid work environment consisting of in-office and remote work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Culture: Globally recognized and award-winning reputation for equality, diversity and inclusion, flexibility, work-life balance, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Wellbeing: Comprehensive benefit plans; company-wide Mental Health Day Off; Headspace app subscription; retirement, savings, tuition reimbursement, and employee incentive programs; resources for mental, physical, and financial wellbeing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development: LinkedIn Learning access; internal Talent Marketplace with opportunities to work on projects cross-company; Ten Thousand Coffees Thomson Reuters caf&#233; networking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;Social Impact: Eight employee-driven Business Resource Groups; two paid volunteer days annually; Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) initiatives for local and global impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;#LI-JS1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accessibility&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a global business, we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;Opportunity/Affirmative&lt;/span&gt; Action Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protect yourself from fraudulent job postings &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.thomsonreuters.com/content/dam/ewp-m/documents/careers/en/pdf/onboarding/fake_job_posting_scam_careers_site.pdf"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to know more.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://thomsonreuters.com"&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;https://thomsonreuters.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External_Career_Site/job/CAN-Toronto-120-Bremner-Blvd/Lead-Software-Engineer_JREQ149450-1?SourceID-APPLICANT_SOURCE-3-713</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/294572/tr_v_lg_rgb_ps.png</logo><company>Thomson Reuters</company></item><item><title>Lead Software Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do you love creating innovative solutions for customers? We are seeking a passionate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt; Lead Software Engineer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; proficient in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Java or Python&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;cloud-native&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; application development.&amp;nbsp;As a member of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Thomson Reuters Labs &lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;in&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt; Toronto&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;, you will have a direct impact on our company by helping to guide the creation of new and innovative capabilities that will delight our customers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What do we do?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; At &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.thomsonreuters.com/en/artificial-intelligence/join-thomson-reuters-labs.html"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thomson Reuters Labs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, we experiment, build and deliver. We work with big data sets to discover what new products, services, or insights we can create for our customers. We then work across the organization to build and deliver these &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;capabilities.&amp;nbsp;Thomson&lt;/span&gt; Reuters is perhaps most well-known for the Reuters News agency. The company is also one of the top sources of information for legal professionals, corporations and tax professionals. We have over 60,000 TBs worth of legal, regulatory, news and tax data. We work across all business segments of Thomson Reuters.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You will be part of a diverse, agile and interdisciplinary innovation team located in Toronto - collaborating with colleagues located in the United States of America, Switzerland, United Kingdom and India. You will work closely with other engineers, designers, data scientists and stakeholders to build solutions that use data analysis and AI, like machine learning (ML). The science and engineering of AI are rapidly &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;evolving.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;We&lt;/span&gt; are looking for an adaptable learner who can think in code and likes to learn and develop new skills as they are needed; someone comfortable with jumping into new problem spaces; who enjoys directing and supporting the efforts of others.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Is this you? Come join us!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;About the Role&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In the role of a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lead Software Engineer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; in Labs, you will:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Guide:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Direct the efforts of a small team of developers to deliver AI-based features.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Manage&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Ensuring a high-performance culture &#8211; nurturing your team&#8217;s career development and managing their performance expectations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Develop and Deliver:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Applying modern software development practices, you will be involved in the entire software development lifecycle, designing, building, testing and delivering high-quality solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Solve Complex Problems&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;:&amp;nbsp;You will create large-scale data processing pipelines to help researchers build and train novel machine learning &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;algorithms.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;You&lt;/span&gt; will develop high performing scalable systems in the context of large online delivery environments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be a Team Player:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Working in a collaborative team-oriented environment, you will share information, value diverse ideas, partner with cross-functional teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be an Agile Person:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;With a strong sense of urgency and a desire to work in a fast-paced, dynamic environment, you will deliver timely solutions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be Innovative:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are empowered to try new approaches and learn new technologies. You will contribute innovative ideas, create solutions, and be accountable for end-to-end deliveries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be an Effective Communicator:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Through dynamic engagement and communication with cross-functional partners and team members, you will effectively articulate ideas and collaborate on technical developments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;About You&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In Labs, we see technology as a tool to solve problems.&amp;nbsp; Technologies tend to quickly change in the, rapidly developing, AI space.&amp;nbsp; If you prefer to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;solve problems&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &#8220;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;think in code&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&#8221; over &#8220;developing in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;technology-X&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;&#8221; you may be a good fit for Labs engineering. You should be curious and comfortable with change and learning new things as needed.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fundamentals are key&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; You should be well-practiced in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;software development lifecycle (SDLC)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&amp;nbsp; As a lead software engineer, you will help drive the problem-solving process &#8211; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;directing, coaching, and mentoring&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; others. We will look to you to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;influence and promote&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; new ideas and ways of solving problems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Basic qualifications:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;9+ years of professional software development&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; experience&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s degree&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; in computer science or equivalent experience&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Proficient in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Java and/or Python&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; software development stacks and ecosystems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Proficient in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;system analysis &amp;amp; design&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;managing a small (3-5) team&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;public cloud&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; services and cloud-native applications, e.g. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;AWS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; (preferred), Azure, or a similar cloud platform; DevOps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Preferred qualifications:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Python/Java &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;frameworks/libraries&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Pandas, Flask, SpaCey, SciPy, etc.) (Spring Core, Apache Commons), &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Object Oriented (OO)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Functional&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; programming paradigms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;artificial intelligence&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; (AI) and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Machine Learning&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; (ML), e.g. Natural Language Processing (NLP),&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience with deploying AI-based applications to production e.g. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;ModelOPs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;AWS SageMaker&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;, Azure ML,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience with big &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;data processing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; (transformation, analysis) using Apache Spark/Hadoop, AWS serverless variants, e.g. PySpark, Scala, MapReduce, AWS Glue, &#8230;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2+ Years &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;AWS software engineering experience&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; in AWS, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;AWS certification&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The work we do in Labs has an impact on our customers and the world!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp; Thomson Reuters is a trusted source of news and other information.&amp;nbsp; By making connections in information our customers use, surfacing it to them in timely and targeted manner we enable them to do their work better and faster.&amp;nbsp; The work we do is very challenging.&amp;nbsp; Sometimes our research does not yield results.&amp;nbsp; We pivot or move on.&amp;nbsp; If this sounds exciting to you, you may be a good fit for Labs! Would you like to learn more about Labs? Check out - &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://nam02.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Ftr.com%2Fai-jobs&amp;amp;data=04%7C01%7CRiya.Patel1%40thomsonreuters.com%7Ca7a52c093dd748e29af808d91c8fb182%7C62ccb8646a1a4b5d8e1c397dec1a8258%7C0%7C0%7C637572225749759928%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C1000&amp;amp;sdata=1RGyR%2BCx6XppWvG8FbbF08Ly5MDr1a5DAfT3cAYYFwo%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;http://tr.com/ai-jobs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;What&#8217;s in it For You?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You will join our inclusive culture of world-class talent, where we are committed to your personal and professional growth through:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hybrid Work Model:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; Currently, as part of our COVID-19 response, our employees are working remotely and following local COVID-19 bylaws and guidelines with the majority of our offices planning to remain remote throughout 2021. Upon return, we will embrace a hybrid work environment consisting of in-office and remote work.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Culture:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; Globally recognized and award-winning reputation for equality, diversity and inclusion, flexibility, work-life balance, and more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wellbeing:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; Comprehensive benefit plans; company-wide Mental Health Day Off; Headspace app subscription; retirement, savings, tuition reimbursement, and employee incentive programs; resources for mental, physical, and financial wellbeing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; LinkedIn Learning access; internal Talent Marketplace with opportunities to work on projects cross-company; Ten Thousand Coffees Thomson Reuters caf&#233; networking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Social Impact:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; Eight employee-driven Business Resource Groups; two paid volunteer days annually; Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) initiatives for local and global impact.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Want to hear from our Technologists on how it is like&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/hashtag/workingattr"&gt;&lt;i&gt;#WorkingatTR&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;? Check it out-&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6HcPr8kgm3U"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Video 1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U2MK3TkE54Y"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Video 2&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;#LI-RP1&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accessibility&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a global business, we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;Opportunity/Affirmative&lt;/span&gt; Action Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protect yourself from fraudulent job postings &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.thomsonreuters.com/content/dam/ewp-m/documents/careers/en/pdf/onboarding/fake_job_posting_scam_careers_site.pdf"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to know more.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://thomsonreuters.com"&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;https://thomsonreuters.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External_Career_Site/job/CAN-Toronto-120-Bremner-Blvd/Lead-Software-Engineer_JREQ148797-1?SourceID-APPLICANT_SOURCE-3-713</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/294572/tr_v_lg_rgb_ps.png</logo><company>Thomson Reuters</company></item><item><title>Applied Research Scientist - NLP</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Are you excited about working at the forefront of applied research in an industry setting?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="http://tr.com/ai-jobs"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Thomson Reuters Labs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;in&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Toronto &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;and &lt;b&gt;Minneapolis&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;is seeking scientists with a passion for solving problems using state-of-the-art Information Retrieval, Machine Learning and Natural Language Processing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;What does&amp;nbsp;Thomson Reuters Labs&amp;nbsp;do?&lt;/b&gt; We experiment, we build, we deliver. We support the organization and our customers through applied research and the development of new products and technologies. TR Labs innovates collaboratively across our core segments in Legal, Tax &amp;amp; Accounting, Government, and Reuters News. We undertake a diverse portfolio of projects today while investing in long-term research for the future.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;a&amp;nbsp;scientist&amp;nbsp;in&amp;nbsp;Labs,&lt;/span&gt; you will be part of a global interdisciplinary team of experts. &lt;/span&gt;We hire specialists across a variety of AI research areas, as well as Engineering and Design, to drive the company\'s digital transformation&lt;span&gt;. &lt;span&gt;TR Labs is known for delivering&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;innovative AI products that serve Thomson Reuters customers in new and exciting ways.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;More about Thomson Reuters Labs - &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://nam02.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Ftr.com%2Fai-jobs&amp;amp;data=04%7C01%7CSuneet.Joshi%40thomsonreuters.com%7C3b86dda15ceb421f0fcf08d91c8d74c1%7C62ccb8646a1a4b5d8e1c397dec1a8258%7C0%7C0%7C637572216146487262%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C1000&amp;amp;sdata=bH8feQMWWotDBf7sA032WPZnvfAkxg9DCJnpXY90grY%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;http://tr.com/ai-jobs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About the role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;In this opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt; you will:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experiment and Develop:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;You will execute the entire model development lifecycle, &lt;span&gt;from prototype to delivery, while applying best practices for reproducible research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and well-managed software delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Collaborate:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;Working on a collaborative cross-functional team, you will share information, value diverse ideas, and partner effectively with colleagues across the globe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Delivery:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;You will be accountable for timely, well-managed deliverables.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Innovate&lt;/b&gt;: You will be empowered to try new approaches and learn new technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Inspire:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;You will be a proactive communicator who is excited to share your work. You will be articulate and compelling in describing ideas to both technical and non-technical audiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are a fit for the role &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;if you have:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ph.D.&amp;nbsp;in a relevant discipline &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;or&amp;nbsp;Master\'s&amp;nbsp;plus&lt;/span&gt; a comparable level of experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;At least one year of industry experience &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;building&amp;nbsp;IR/NLP/ML&amp;nbsp;systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Solid software engineering skills for prototyping&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Preferred qualifications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;5+ years academic or industry experience building IR, ML or NLP&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;systems with the demonstrated ability to translate cutting edge research into working applications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Proficiency &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;in&amp;nbsp;Python,&amp;nbsp;Java,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;or&amp;nbsp;Scala&amp;nbsp;and&lt;/span&gt; experience delivering minimum viable products in a large enterprise environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Proven communication skills and ability to work on deliverables independently&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Publications at workshops or conferences such as ACL, EMNLP, NAACL, SIGIR, NeurIPS, or similar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What\'s in it for you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;At Thomson Reuters, our people are our greatest assets. In addition to rewarding and challenging work with exceptional colleagues, we offer the following benefits for your personal and professional growth:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: On-the-job coaching &amp;amp; learning, tuition reimbursement, exposure to leading-edge technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Our&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Scientists and Engineers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;get to play with big data sets to discover new products, capabilities, and insights for our customers. Thomson Reuters is most well-known for the globally respected Reuters News agency, but our company is also the leading source of information for legal, corporate and tax professionals. We have over 60,000 TBs worth of legal, regulatory, news, and tax data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Flexible work arrangements, comprehensive health coverage effective day one, savings and investment plans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Perks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Social events &amp;amp; activities, employee discount programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Social Impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Paid time off for volunteering virtually or in your community&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;#LI-SJ1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accessibility&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a global business, we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;Opportunity/Affirmative&lt;/span&gt; Action Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protect yourself from fraudulent job postings &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.thomsonreuters.com/content/dam/ewp-m/documents/careers/en/pdf/onboarding/fake_job_posting_scam_careers_site.pdf"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to know more.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://thomsonreuters.com"&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;https://thomsonreuters.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External_Career_Site/job/CAN-Toronto-120-Bremner-Blvd/Applied-Research-Scientist---NLP-ML_JREQ145643-1?SourceID-APPLICANT_SOURCE-3-713</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/294572/tr_v_lg_rgb_ps.png</logo><company>Thomson Reuters</company></item><item><title>Associate Architect</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Associate Architect&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a technologist at Thomson Reuters, you will help shape the global knowledge economy. Our technology ensures that professionals around the world have the answers they need. You will work with the brightest thinkers on diverse projects, creating next-generation solutions that deliver powerful results. As the world&#8217;s top provider of intelligent information, we want your unique perspective to create the solutions that advance our business&#8212;and your career. Bring your passion for innovation, and together we&#8217;ll make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About the Role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;In this role you will:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be a Technical Leader&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &#8211; provide thought leadership and guidance in setting the architecture vision and direction for a robust and scalable set of services that enable the creation and deployment of AI/ML solutions for processing documents. Work with technology teams and beyond to realize their &lt;span&gt;implementation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be a&amp;nbsp;Team Player&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8211;&amp;nbsp;ability to work in a &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;collaborative&amp;nbsp;and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; inclusive &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;team-oriented&amp;nbsp;environment,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; partner with cross functional and remote teams, draw out strong design ideas from diverse teams and high performing engineers, and translate requirements into actionable architecture.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be an Effective &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;Communicator&amp;nbsp;&#8211;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;ability&amp;nbsp;to concisely and completely &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;articulate&amp;nbsp;complex&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; technical issues &#8211; verbal and visual; ability to target your audience, actively listen, and value diverse ideas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be an&amp;nbsp;Agile Person&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8211;&amp;nbsp;with a strong sense of urgency and a desire to work in a fast-paced dynamic environment to deliver solutions against strict timelines.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Be&amp;nbsp;Curious &amp;amp; Innovative&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8211; ability to question the status quo.&amp;nbsp; Continuously update yourself with&amp;nbsp;industry trends, next &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;generation&amp;nbsp;technology,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and software development best practices.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;About You&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in software design, methodologies (Agile), and tools (MS ADO, Lucidchart)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broad experience in cloud based (AWS), full-stack, design and development including use of the following technologies: Java, Python, Front-End Technologies (e.g., JavaScript, Angular), XML (DOM, SAX), Database and Storage (Postgres, Oracle, DynamoDB, S3), Messaging Technologies (SQN/SNS), APIs (Microservices and Serverless), Big Data (Glue, Spark, Parquet), MLOps (Sagemaker).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Must be an excellent communicator when speaking, writing, and in diagramming.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills with an ability to operate across organizational boundaries and to influence business stakeholders, as well as technology peers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advanced analytical skills with the ability to synthesize business requirements with technology capabilities to produce coherent technical designs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to quickly learn, analyze and prototype new technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have 5+years relevant experience in large distributed/cloud systems, including 1+ years architecture / design experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You may also have:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cloud experience (AWS or Azure)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in Cognitive Computing (e.g, Machine Learning, NLP/NER, Classification, Clustering)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Architecting API-first solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in processing large volumes of data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;System load and scale testing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CICD and Automation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it For You&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;At Thomson Reuters, our people are our greatest assets. Here are some of the benefits we offer for your personal and professional growth:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: On-the-job coaching &amp;amp; learning, tuition reimbursement, exposure to cutting-edge technology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: Flexible work arrangements, comprehensive health coverage that&#8217;s effective day one&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Perks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;: Social events &amp;amp; activities, employee discount programs through corporate perks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a global business we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under country or local law. We are proud to be an Equal Employment Opportunity Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accessibility&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a global business, we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;Opportunity/Affirmative&lt;/span&gt; Action Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protect yourself from fraudulent job postings &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.thomsonreuters.com/content/dam/ewp-m/documents/careers/en/pdf/onboarding/fake_job_posting_scam_careers_site.pdf"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to know more.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://thomsonreuters.com"&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;https://thomsonreuters.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External_Career_Site/job/CAN-Toronto-120-Bremner-Blvd/Associate-Architect_JREQ147166?SourceID-APPLICANT_SOURCE-3-713</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/294572/tr_v_lg_rgb_ps.png</logo><company>Thomson Reuters</company></item><item><title>Lead Software Engineer</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div data-automation-id="decorationWrapper" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input" class="WHFG"&gt;&lt;div class="WNJJ WOJJ"&gt;&lt;div class="WJF- WBI- WCI- WJD- WLF- WOH- WBAB WKF-" data-automation-id="richTextEditor" id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input" data-metadata-id="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription" data-uxi-widget-editable="true" aria-invalid="false" aria-labelledby="richTextArea.jobPosting.jobDescription-input--uid11-input-formLabel"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" style="display: none;"&gt;&lt;textarea class="gwt-TextArea" name="gwt-uid-12" data-automation-id="richTextHiddenTextArea"&gt;&lt;/textarea&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="GWTCKEditor-Disabled" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lead Software Engineer &#8211; Checkpoint US&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Thomson Reuters Checkpoint product is a research and guidance tool for tax and accounting professionals, trusted by 200,000 users. It delivers the latest in artificial intelligence, cognitive computing, and machine learning technologies, combined with the tax and accounting expertise of our editorial staff.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Legal Research Product team is seeking a Lead Software Engineer for our Checkpoint US team. The candidate in this position will lead the design and implementation of Checkpoint features and enhancements. Checkpoint is Thomson Reuters&#8217; premier AI-enabled research and guidance product for tax professionals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;About the Role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In this opportunity as a&amp;nbsp;Lead Software Engineer,&amp;nbsp;you will:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Build and Develop&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&#8211; You will be involved in the entire development, operational support, monitoring, automation, building, testing, and delivering high-quality solutions for the Engineering team including ensuring performance and quality of the delivered solutions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be a Team Player&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8211; Partner closely with our Product Owners, Delivery Managers, Architects, and other cross-functional lead to work in a collaborative team-oriented environment, share information, and value diverse ideas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Show Leadership&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8211; Be the team role model. Lead a global and diverse engineering team in designing solutions and issue resolutions. Provide guidance, coaching, and mentoring to software development engineers and influence the product technology roadmap through innovation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be Curious &amp;amp; Innovative&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8211; Continuously update yourself with next-generation technology, development tools, and contribute to process development practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be Agile&lt;/b&gt;&#8211; Actively determine and resolve potential problems/issues including the authoring of technical design. Work on multiple projects and manage time effectively, assessing risk and dependencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Be an Effective Communicator&lt;/b&gt; &#8211;&amp;nbsp;Regularly inform the manager or team lead on the progress of the project, identifying risks early in the process. Effectively communicate with project partners of varying degrees of technical knowledge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Take Ownership&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&#8211; Responsible for performance, reliability, and implement changes for improving the efficiency of a technical component. Mentor junior team members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;About you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;You&#8217;re a fit for the role of Lead Software Engineer if you have:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s degree in computer science or equivalent required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;5+ years of software engineering &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;experience&amp;nbsp;including&#183;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Proven ability to learn new technologies quickly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Proven ability to solve complex problems independently&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Creative problem solving, troubleshooting skills, and critical thinking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Designing &amp;amp; developing software for a critical enterprise n-tier web product&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hands -experience with Restful APIs, SaaS technologies, microservice architecture, Java and SQL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Expertise in Angular or similar application frameworks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Development Experience with large scale software and applications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Working Experience in designing and building applications using AWS managed services and capabilities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hands-on experience with Java technology stack including but not limited to Spring Boot, J2EE, AWS, Python, Shell Scripting, and CI/CD tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hands-on experience in the design and development of web-based applications using JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, XML, JSON, and Relational databases&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hands-on experience with Scrum framework with hands-on agile delivery experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hands-on experience with design and development of cost-efficient AWS solutions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Demonstrated ability in the following behaviors:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Effective time management, ability to plan and prioritize work, and manage a diverse workload&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Take ownership of problems, identify solutions, and drive resolution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work well within a team environment and independently&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strong interpersonal and communication skills, both oral and written&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience with AI/ML applications including Model training, tuning, and evaluation preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Excellent critical thinking, troubleshooting, and collaborative problem-solving skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span&gt;What&#8217;s in it For You:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;You will join our inclusive culture of world-class talent, where we are committed to your&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hybrid Work Model:&lt;/b&gt; Currently, as part of our COVID-19 response, our employees are working remotely and following local COVID-19 bylaws and guidelines with the majority of our offices planning to remain remote throughout 2021. Upon return, we will embrace a hybrid work environment consisting of in-office and remote work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Culture:&lt;/b&gt; Globally recognized and award-winning reputation for equality, diversity and inclusion, flexibility, work-life balance, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wellbeing:&lt;/b&gt; Comprehensive benefit plans; company-wide Mental Health Day Off; Headspace app subscription; retirement, savings, tuition reimbursement, and employee incentive programs; resources for mental, physical, and financial wellbeing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Learning &amp;amp; Development:&lt;/b&gt; LinkedIn Learning access; internal Talent Marketplace with opportunities to work on projects cross-company; Ten Thousand Coffees Thomson Reuters caf&#233; networking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Social Impact:&lt;/b&gt; Eight employee-driven Business Resource Groups; two paid volunteer days annually; Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) initiatives for local and global impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you want to be part of a team helping re-invent the way knowledge professionals work? How about a team that works every day to create a more transparent, just and inclusive future? At Thomson Reuters, we&#8217;ve been doing just that for almost 160 years. Our industry-leading products and services include highly specialized information-enabled software and tools for legal, tax, accounting and compliance professionals combined with the world&#8217;s most global news services &#8211; Reuters. We help these professionals do their jobs better, creating more time for them to focus on the things that matter most: advising, advocating, negotiating, governing and informing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We are powered by the talents of 25,000 employees across more than 75 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments that celebrate diversity and inclusion. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Accessibility&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;As a global business, we rely on diversity of culture and thought to deliver on our goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment &lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;Opportunity/Affirmative&lt;/span&gt; Action Employer providing a drug-free workplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protect yourself from fraudulent job postings &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://www.thomsonreuters.com/content/dam/ewp-m/documents/careers/en/pdf/onboarding/fake_job_posting_scam_careers_site.pdf"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to know more.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="DEFAULT" style="text-align:inherit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="LTR" style="text-align:left"&gt;More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" href="https://thomsonreuters.com"&gt;&lt;span class="WLL2"&gt;https://thomsonreuters.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External_Career_Site/job/USA-Eagan-610-Opperman-Dr/Lead-Software-Engineer_JREQ149199?SourceID-APPLICANT_SOURCE-3-713</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/294572/tr_v_lg_rgb_ps.png</logo><company>Thomson Reuters</company></item></items>