<items><item><title>Applied Machine Learning Specialist AI Engineering &amp; Technology &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;As a Vector &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Applied Machine Learning Specialist&lt;/span&gt;, you will contribute to developing reusable software to apply and scale research breakthroughs in machine learning and AI. You will collaborate with some of the best and brightest AI developers and machine learning researchers and will work with leading industry sponsors and healthcare institutions to apply AI.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work on AI software development projects following an agile methodology with teams that can include Vector AI software developers, professional staff, researchers, and industry sponsors;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and develop reference applications and model templates that apply AI research to real-world problems using public and private data sets, providing software for training, testing, operating, and updating models;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and develop open source software for applying AI research techniques to common problems;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mentor industry sponsors on industry projects that apply AI research to shared problems, mentoring on engineering best practices, and assisting with operational issues;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mentor researchers on software engineering best practices;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop prototypes and proofs of concept; and,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Report and present on software development including status and results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor\'s degree in computer science, mathematics, electrical engineering, or related discipline; MSc/MEng preferred&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 2 years of experience in industry; experience across industries considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in machine learning and/or statistics&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated software engineering background with experience in production deployment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated data engineering background working with messy real-world data&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated analytical skills to identify signal in data and feasibility of prediction&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge and experience of Python and preferably C/C++ and C#&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with parameter and architecture tuning of deep learning algorithms is preferred&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in leading open source deep learning software frameworks (PyTorch, Tensorflow, and CUDA)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;User interaction/design expertise with Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) engineering considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Kailyn Burke, Human Resources Business Partner&lt;/span&gt;, using the link provided.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Review of applications will begin on &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 19, 2021&lt;/span&gt;. We thank all applicants for their interest in this exciting opportunity and will be in touch with those whose qualifications most closely match with our needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please note that all interviews are currently being held remotely due to the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are indigenous, LGBT2Q+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://vectorinstituteai-my.sharepoint.com/personal/catherine_kirby_vectorinstituteai_onmicrosoft_com/Documents/HR%20Shared/Recruitment/Job%20Descriptions/AI%20Engineering%20&amp;amp;%20Technology/hr@vectorinstitute.ai%C2%A0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=143&amp;source=other</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Applied Machine Learning Specialist (ML Systems) AI Engineering &amp; Technology &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;As an &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Applied Machine Learning Specialist (ML Systems) &lt;/span&gt;you will provide technical leadership and contribute to focused research applications to solve real-world problems with machine learning and AI. You will provide guidance and work with some of the best and brightest data specialists and machine learning engineers from leading industry and healthcare organizations. You will collaborate with some of the leading machine learning researchers, data specialists and engineers. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Research and implement state of the art machine learning techniques to solve real world problems;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work in collaboration with Researchers, Machine learning specialists, Vector team members and Vector affiliates to build demos, minimum viable products (MVP) and prototypes;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide advice regarding building machine learning applications and ML product roadmaps&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide oversight for Vector-led or co-led efforts to prepare and open source specific datasets for machine learning research;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Serve as the an AI Engineering team representative to research computing and HPC team;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Serve as an expert and facilitate identification of experts among the Vector research community for external stakeholders (e.g., health and other sectors) to advise on machine learning research trends and applications; and,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Other related duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A degree in computer science or computer engineering with a research focus on machine learning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strong software engineering and coding skills, with the ability to write high-performance and production-level code&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated expertise in &lt;span&gt;building systems for applying machine learning algorithms for solving business challenges&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience applying machine learning research to novel problems and data sets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge and experience of Python&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with large scale machine learning operations such as distributed training, parameter and architecture tuning of deep learning models&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience using deep learning software frameworks (PyTorch, Tensorflow, JAX, or CUDA)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Demonstrated experience with SLURM and bash programming is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with high-performance-computing and GPU execution model is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with CI/CD and software development life-cycles is a plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Kailyn Burke, Human Resources Business Partner&lt;/span&gt;, using the link provided.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Review of applications will begin on &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 19, 2021&lt;/span&gt;. We thank all applicants for their interest in this exciting opportunity and will be in touch with those whose qualifications most closely match with our needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please note that all interviews are currently being held remotely due to the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are indigenous, LGBT2Q+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://vectorinstituteai-my.sharepoint.com/personal/catherine_kirby_vectorinstituteai_onmicrosoft_com/Documents/HR%20Shared/Recruitment/Job%20Descriptions/AI%20Engineering%20&amp;amp;%20Technology/hr@vectorinstitute.ai%C2%A0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=144&amp;source=other</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Manager, Scientific Computing AI Engineering &amp; Technology &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Vector Institute is seeking a &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Manager, Scientific Computing t&lt;/span&gt;o join our growing team in Toronto as we continue the work of making Canada a center of expertise for AI in the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Manager of Scientific Computing will build and coach a highly-skilled team who will develop and maintain tools that support transparent growth and appropriate resource sharing policies for advanced research computing in artificial intelligence. The Manager will report directly to the VP of AI Engineering and Chief Information Officer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The incumbent will play a key role in the building and future maintenance of an artificial intelligence high-performance computing environment for world class research in machine learning. This role will primarily support scientific computing needs such as library support, compiling, and hardware and software evolution.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;This leadership position is expected to have a hands-on, problem-solving approach to managing and troubleshooting environments and a proven track record of integrating best-in-class software systems in budget and on time and within budget.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Along with members of Vector&#8217;s senior management team, build, develop, and manage a team of information technology support personnel to execute Vector&#8217;s scientific computing objectives;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Oversee the planning, general execution and maintenance of complex computing arrangements, equipment, and appropriate technical support necessary for research in deep learning, machine learning, and applied artificial intelligence research;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Develop, operate, and maintain Vector&#8217;s scientific computing needs in accordance with Vector&#8217;s policies;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Provide advice to Vector&#8217;s senior management team and serve as an expert point of contact within Vector on computing equipment and information technology;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Work with the senior management team to advise on the communication of corporate strategy and reporting requirements in respect to computing equipment and information technology, including public reporting;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Manage Vector&#8217;s scientific computing equipment and technology requirements within budget;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Support researchers in all their computing needs;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Assist in general enterprise IT operations as required;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Collaborate with the AI engineering team to develop and integrate new software capabilities;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Work with Vector&#8217;s partners in the Advanced Research Computing (ARC) community to define and execute a strategy to provide specialized AI compute capabilities to the Vector research community, including input on program design for public funding;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Work with partners to provide specialized compute for health sector research and development; and,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Define and execute cybersecurity policies and controls to support productivity and mitigate risks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"&gt;SUCCESS MEASURES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Ensures the smooth &lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;functioning&lt;/span&gt; of the scientific computing systems, by undertaking troubleshooting, maintenance, and installation tasks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Effectively manages and develops a team of scientific computing support personnel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Researchers, engineers, sponsors, and partners feel supported in all other scientific computing needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Builds and maintains tools that facilitate the automated or direct administration of network and computing infrastructure, in private data centre, public cloud, and local workstations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Graduate degree in computer science, engineering or another relevant field preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;3-5 years of managerial experience in a fast-paced, innovative environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Experience in a systems administration or management role in a UNIX/Linux environment or complex computing environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Demonstrated proficiency in programming and automation, with experience in devops and/or systems reliability engineering preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Experience in managing and troubleshooting environments using mostly open-source software&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills with the ability to lead technical discussions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Experience working within a research environment is considered an asset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Ability to work autonomously, prioritize, multi-task, and problem solve in a fast-paced and dynamic environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Effective conflict and dispute resolution skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Ability to be proactive, addressing potential problems before they occur&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Strong attention to detail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Systems engineering and troubleshooting skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Kailyn Burke, Human Resources Business Partner&lt;/span&gt;, using the link provided.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Review of applications will begin on &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 23, 2021&lt;/span&gt;. We thank all applicants for their interest in this exciting opportunity and will be in touch with those whose qualifications most closely match with our needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please note that all interviews are currently being held remotely due to the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are indigenous, LGBT2Q+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://vectorinstituteai-my.sharepoint.com/personal/catherine_kirby_vectorinstituteai_onmicrosoft_com/Documents/HR%20Shared/Recruitment/Job%20Descriptions/AI%20Engineering%20&amp;amp;%20Technology/hr@vectorinstitute.ai%C2%A0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=142&amp;source=other</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Program Coordinator, Talent Initiatives (Contract) Academic Partnerships &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif; font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;The Vector Institute is seeking a&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Program Coordinator, Talent Initiatives &lt;/span&gt;to join our growing team in Toronto. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Reporting to the Director, Academic Partnerships, the Program Coordinator, Talent Initiatives is a key contributor to the team&#8217;s targeted initiatives to develop future generations of top AI talent. In this dynamic role, you will perform administrative and business functions to support the Academic Partnerships team members and programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif; font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;EMPLOYMENT TYPE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;Contract (12 months)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif; font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;Administer the daily operations behind the Vector &lt;em&gt;Digital Talent Hub&lt;/em&gt;, including approving candidate profiles, posting curated roles, removing expired roles, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;Support the maintenance, cleaning, and analysis of data relating to the Talent Hub (Gsheets), alumni employment outcomes (SQL), recruitment contact data (Gsheets and Salesforce) and other AI-talent related data &lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;applying sound data analysis techniques while gleaning and presenting key insights from the data&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;Assist with outgoing talent-related communications to affiliated employers, including executing MailMerge campaigns, creating relevant slide presentations and managing correspondence to talent-related inbox.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;Track alumni outcome data to measure workforce attachment to Ontario, &lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;manipulating large amounts of data from different sources and using strong data visualization skills (Google Data Studio) to share the results.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;Assist with the creation of resume books showcasing Vector Talent.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;Assist in the coordination of recruitment-oriented internal and external-facing events, with sponsors and other stakeholder organizations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;Other duties as assigned.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif; font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;PROFILE OF IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;You are passionate about growing Canada&#8217;s global leadership in AI research.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;You are highly organized, with strong time management and multi-tasking skills and are motivated to work in a fast-paced environment with different stakeholders, including professional staff, students and alumni, as well as academics.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;You are action oriented and have a demonstrated ability to take direction and turn it into actionable results.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;You are creative and enjoy collaborating within a small entrepreneurial environment that is results-driven.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;You possess a positive attitude, integrity, a sense of humour, are tactful, and bring positive energy and outlook to a not-for-profit corporate culture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;You have excellent verbal and written English communication skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;You possess a high level of proficiency with GSuite or the Microsoft Suite of applications, Excel or Gsheets in particular (with an emphasis on data manipulation and visualization skills).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;Having proficiency with the following applications is a plus: relational databases (e.g., MS Access, SQL) and data visualization software (e.g., Google Data Studio, Power BI).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;You have a keen eye for detail, design and data presentation (e.g., charts and graphs).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;You understand how to turn data into insight and can produce basic statistics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Tolu Onajin, Human Resources Business Partner,&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;using the link provided&lt;/span&gt;. Review of applications will begin&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 27, 2021&lt;/span&gt;. We thank all applicants for their interest in this exciting opportunity and will be in touch with those whose qualifications most closely match with our needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;Please note that all interviews are currently being held remotely due to the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are indigenous, LGBT2Q+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact&amp;nbsp;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&amp;nbsp;and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=146&amp;source=other</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Technical Education Specialist Industry Innovation &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Technology is accelerating at an unprecedented rate, and more so in the field of artificial intelligence (AI). With this acceleration comes changes in the workforce, including new and exciting roles! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;The role of &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Technical Education Specialist&lt;/span&gt; combines data science machine learning skills, technical education, business insights, and the social impact of AI. This interdisciplinary role requires an understanding of data science and machine learning methods and approaches, as well as a wholistic commitment to life-long-learning and professional development.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;This role resides in the Professional Development (PD) team, which forms part of the broader the Industry Innovation team at Vector. The PD team takes the cutting-edge research in AI by Vector&#8217;s world-class researchers and packages it into programming that industry can absorb, through courses, workshops, talks, academic papers, blogs and events.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with Vector Sponsors, the Director of Professional Development, and select third parties to determine needs, requirements, and content for courses that support the deployment and operationalization of AI.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, build, implement, and continue to improve upon artificial intelligence and machine learning training programs for executives and non-technical stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, build, implement, and continue to improve upon machine learning training programs for data scientists and engineers related to data science and machine learning.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure learning and performance objectives are appropriate to the audience, and that the training materials meet the learning and performance objectives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regularly undertake a variety of administrative tasks to help organize and facilitate the activities of the Professional Development (PD) team including:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage educational programming events such as ESS and Business Insights;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage registrations and user updates in the D2L Learning Management System;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Management content in the D2L Learning Management System (e.g., generating, uploading lessons or slides);&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage attendance and all other completion requirements (including assignments and grades) for the courses and workshops in collaboration with various members of the course team (Manager, Instructors, and TAs);&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assist with calls for speakers from Industry, including working with the Directors of Industry Innovation to ensure appropriate engagement from industry sponsors;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage cross-functional relationships i.e., activities performed in collaboration with other teams inside Vector (e.g., Communications/Events, Academic Partnerships, Health, Research, etc.); and,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage PD administrative documents and content.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Overall data management and reporting for the Professional Development team including contact metrics for internal and external (including government) reporting purposes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Other relevant duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;SUCCESS MEASURES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Industry Innovation team reaches its metrics and targets (i.e., renewal and sponsorship growth) as approved by Vector&#8217;s President &amp;amp; CEO and Board of Directors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The professional development education and upskilling program trains a minimum of 3,000 participants by 2023.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Internal and external stakeholder feedback is such that Vector\'s Industry Innovation team provides high quality service, support, and impactful data/resources as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have, at minimum, a graduate degree in computer science, engineering, business administration, business analytics, statistics, mathematics or another relevant field&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You demonstrate interdisciplinary interests that include technical and non-technical fields such as engineering, business analytics, computer science, ethics, graphic design etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a combination of domain expertise in machine learning and practical industry experience. This experience may include designing, planning, and delivering on professional development courses or other programs for technical and non-technical audiences&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are an educator at heart who enjoys translating technical concepts to different audiences&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience facilitating workshops for diverse audiences&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have excellent organizational and management skills and are committed to forging relationships that will advance AI education and related activities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are a creative problem solver and enjoy collaborating within a small results-driven intrapreneurial environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have impeccable verbal, presentation, and written English communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have strong time management and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable working with a diverse range of clients (e.g., leadership teams, operations staff, graduate students, and external partners), maintaining confidentiality and providing all with a trusted, respectful point of contact&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are technology savvy and are open to learning and mastering new software&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are motivated by continuous learning and the opportunity to make a difference and a real contribution to the AI ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You possess a positive attitude, integrity, a sense of humour, and bring positive energy and outlook to a high performing team&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Kailyn Burke, Human Resources Business Partner&lt;/span&gt;, using the link provided.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Review of applications will begin on &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 26, 2021&lt;/span&gt;. We thank all applicants for their interest in this exciting opportunity and will be in touch with those whose qualifications most closely match with our needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please note that all interviews are currently being held remotely due to the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are indigenous, LGBT2Q+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://vectorinstituteai-my.sharepoint.com/personal/catherine_kirby_vectorinstituteai_onmicrosoft_com/Documents/HR%20Shared/Recruitment/Job%20Descriptions/AI%20Engineering%20&amp;amp;%20Technology/hr@vectorinstitute.ai%C2%A0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=145&amp;source=other</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>MANAGER, MARKETING Marketing &amp; Communications &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reporting to the &lt;/span&gt;Director, Marketing and Communications, the &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Manager, Marketing &lt;/span&gt;will develop and execute the strategic marketing plan for Vector, using a data driven approach to grow the Vector brand and achieve long-term strategic objectives. This will include but is not limited to development of; thought leadership, content strategy and collateral, digital marketing programs, partnership and co-marketing programs, and primary and secondary competitive research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, you will oversee the Marketing Analytics function and work closely with our communications and events team members to ensure our marketing plans are aligned and executed with a view to achieving Vector&#8217;s overall business objectives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&#8217;re looking for someone who thinks out of the box, who can design innovative marketing and content programs that tell great stories, bring Vector&#8217;s offerings to life while achieving measurable results for the enterprise as well as specific goals from key stakeholders internally and externally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Working with the Director, Marketing and Communications, as well as, senior leadership team, develop, implement, and lead Vector&#8217;s annual marketing strategy;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Lead and conduct a comprehensive annual review of marketing needs, to inform the annual marketing plan;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Manage a growing team, currently one direct report (&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;Digital Marketing &amp;amp; Analytics Specialist&lt;/span&gt;), you will lead the development and expansion of our marketing function, working with various stakeholders to develop value added marketing programs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Using performance and growth marketing principles, establish and lead the development of processes, data collection, metrics, analytics and actionable insights to continuously improve the effectiveness of Vector marketing, events and communications initiatives;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;In collaboration with internal program leads and workstreams; develop, execute, and optimize project-specific marketing plans, including capturing data to measure and evaluate outcomes for continuous improvement;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Conduct market research, competitive analysis, and gather stakeholder insights, present recommendations, and coordinate effective action plans to help Vector&#8217;s teams improve their offerings, positioning, and value propositions;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Map and track Vector&#8217;s participant/customer journeys and develop content strategies to maximize conversion rates for Vector&#8217;s diverse programs;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Develop content strategies while working closely with the communications team to integrate the current editorial calendar with our marketing and web content pipeline - providing clear and effective communication of project requirements across stakeholders and functions (editorial, paid media, social media, email, etc).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Identify content-driven opportunities to boost SEO performance and work with our Marketing Analyst and agency partners to implement recommendations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Oversee and lead all aspects of digital marketing, included but not limited to; website maintenance/development, social media channels and digital advertising&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Develop channel strategies and identifying potential partnerships to optimize paid content distribution, maximizing reach and impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Oversee the strategy, production and discoverability of video content on Youtube and other emerging channels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Manage a rich content calendar that supports a regular cadence of various types of content (e.g. interactive tools, blog posts, ebooks, video series, infographics, product guides) that are aligned to Vector&#8217;s audience and stakeholder&#8217;s journey&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Develop briefs and scopes of work to derive maximum value from external agency resources;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Develop key messages and value propositions as new segments, initiatives, and offerings emerge;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Champion and steward the Vector Institute brand ensuring high quality and consistent messaging and branding across all channels and materials for all audiences&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Collaborate strategically with leading organizations in Canada&#8217;s AI ecosystem (e.g., industry sponsors, universities, government investment offices) to reach target audiences and strengthen partnerships; and,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Undertake other related duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;KEY SUCCESS MEASURES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Progress towards Vector&#8217;s strategic objectives (i.e., as they relate to Industry Innovation, Research Operations, Health, Academic Partnerships, AI Engineering) is enhanced by the development and implementation of marketing strategies; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Measurable increases in brand awareness, consideration, and program participation across all key segments (i.e., sponsors, talent/alumni, government);&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Measurable increase in reach and frequency of communication to target segments (e.g., via growth in email marketing lists); &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Increased frequency of success and impact stories, testimonials, and value proposition reaching and resonating with target audiences including executive decision-makers;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Increase in co-branded content shared on partner channels; and, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Internal feedback indicates that the marketing function provides high-quality service and support.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s degree in business, marketing or related discipline.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Minimum 7 years of marketing/communications experience, with a focus on strategy, planning and implementing integrated marketing communications campaign programs designed to drive&lt;span&gt; business results (e.g., customer acquisition, revenue growth) and generating brand awareness, consideration, and leads.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Previous experience &lt;/span&gt;managing&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;coaching&lt;span&gt; high-performing teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience developing plans, building processes, and using analytics to execute successful marketing strategies in a fast-paced, dynamic environment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience managing digital marketing in compliance with Canadian Anti-Spam Legislation and privacy legislation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Experience in developing marketing and communications strategies that are aligned to business strategy and sales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Strong communication skills, both verbal and written French would be an asset but not required&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strong critical and strategic thinker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ability to work independently on several projects concurrently and maintain focus and professionalism in high pressure environments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills with an ability to work successfully with various organizational levels, including colleagues, senior executives, and external partners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Deep interest &lt;/span&gt;in Canada\'s AI ecosystem&lt;span&gt; and knowledge economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ability to create visually compelling and professional documents, in alignment with established visual identity guidelines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Tolu Onajin, Human Resources Business Partner,&amp;nbsp;using the link provided. Review of applications will begin&amp;nbsp;September 14, 2021. We thank all applicants for their interest in this exciting opportunity and will be in touch with those whose qualifications most closely match with our needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Please note that all interviews are currently being held remotely due to the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are indigenous, LGBT2Q+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact&amp;nbsp;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&amp;nbsp;and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=147&amp;source=other</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Postdoctoral Fellow Research &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;ACCEPTING APPLICATIONS FOR OCTOBER 2021 COHORT!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Are you an&amp;nbsp;early career researcher&amp;nbsp;with the potential to become a world-class machine learning scientist? The Vector Institute invites applications for Postdoctoral Fellows who are working on cutting-edge fundamental research in machine learning and deep learning algorithms and their applications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Our areas of research include:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Computer Vision&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Generative Models&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Healthcare &#8211; computational biology, genomics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Natural Language Processing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Optimization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Reinforcement Learning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Statistical Learning Theory&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Sequential Decision Making&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Security, Privacy &amp;amp; Fairness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Quantum Computing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The standard term for a Postdoctoral Fellow position is 1&#8211;2 years, with a possible extension to 3 years. Also available is the opportunity for eligible individuals to complete a&amp;nbsp;placement at Vector before going on to take a faculty role elsewhere.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Postdoctoral Fellows at the Vector Institute are&amp;nbsp;early career researchers&amp;nbsp;with the potential to become world-class researchers. Like postdoctoral researchers in a university lab, Postdoctoral Fellows at the Vector Institute are tasked with and supported in carrying out state-of-the-art research, publishing at the highest international level, and contributing to the academic life and reputation of the Institute. The Vector Institute offers a dynamic environment, and research freedom and opportunity to collaborate within and across research areas. They are part of a thriving research community of over 500 Vector Faculty Members, Faculty Affiliates, Postgraduate Affiliates, Postdoctoral Fellows, and graduate students.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Postdoctoral Fellows at the Vector Institute have access to the resources of a well-funded institute dedicated solely to machine learning and deep learning, and are encouraged to work with any of our over&amp;nbsp;30 world-class faculty in machine learning and deep learning, though they will work primarily with 1&#8211;2 faculty members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;They&amp;nbsp;will be expected to propose work on research topics of their interest related to machine learning and deep learning and carry out that research with a great deal of independence. Should they be so inclined, Postdoctoral Fellows may teach and mentor at the Institute; engage in entrepreneurial activities; and/or work with existing companies to enhance their research. They have the ability to collaborate with the graduate students of the machine learning group at the University of Toronto, as well as the graduate students of other affiliated faculty, who spend the bulk of their time at the Institute.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;ABOUT&amp;nbsp;VECTOR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Vector Institute is an independent non-profit corporation, with Faculty Members and Affiliates from the University of Toronto, University of Waterloo, and other Canadian universities. It is supported with generous funding from the provincial and federal governments, as well as Canadian industry sponsors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Vector Institute is located in the MaRS Discovery District building, spanning nearly the entire 7th floor and overlooking downtown Toronto and the beautiful Queen&#8217;s Park. On any given day, the Vector Institute houses over a hundred students, dozens of Faculty Members, supported with state-of-the-art compute power, and dedicated professional staff. The daily life and concentration of expertise in the Institute fosters collaboration and the exchange of ideas among its members through talks, seminar series, visitors, and tutorials.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Vector Institute&#8217;s vision is to drive excellence in the creation of artificial intelligence, to use it to foster economic growth, and to improve the lives of Canadians. To that end, the Vector Institute has close ties to both academia and industry. This puts our Postdoctoral Fellows in a unique position to contribute broadly. A successful contribution can range from developing core algorithmic techniques and theoretical analyses of machine learning algorithms, to working closely with existing companies and health organization, to engaging in entrepreneurial activities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;In addition to their research, Postdoctoral Fellows have the opportunity to work with industry to develop machine-learning-based solutions for their problems or engage in related entrepreneurial activities. We have dedicated staff facilitating all aspects of engaging with Vector sponsors and affiliated institutions, as well as close ties to incubators for entrepreneurial activities. The Vector Institute has extensive access to computing resources and datasets. We have a team of AI Engineers who help improve research productivity through software platform development, ensuring research reproducibility, publishing open source code and data, and in readying code for commercial use.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;WHO SHOULD APPLY?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;We are looking for people with interests across a broad spectrum from core machine learning or deep learning research to more applied and entrepreneurial activities. We are also looking for people who have excelled in other areas and are interested in moving into deep learning or machine learning more broadly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;PhD or equivalent in Computer Science, Statistics, Electrical Engineering, or a closely related field. You must have completed all requirements of your doctoral degree no more than three years before the application deadline;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;An excellent publication record in machine learning;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Expertise in a core area of machine learning, such as deep, unsupervised, and reinforcement learning, optimization, and theory; and/or applied machine learning, such as natural language, health, vision, robotics, medicine, biology, transportation, media, and finance;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;For those looking to pivot to machine learning from a field with technical overlap, we are looking for an excellent publication record in your field as well as expertise in an area with some potential relevance to machine learning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;APPLICATION REQUIREMENTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Please note that all documents have to be converted and merged into &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;a single PDF document&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt; and uploaded &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;as one PDF file&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;A cover letter, including identifying a Vector Faculty Member as potential supervisor. We encourage applicants to contact Faculty Members before submitting their application.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;A &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;curriculum vit&#230;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Links to at least three recent publications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;A research statement outlining a proposed program of research.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Reference Letters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Three reference letters. One referee should be your PhD supervisor. If referees prefer to submit reference letters directly, they can be sent to&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;research@vectorinstitute.ai.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;DEADLINE&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;October Cohort&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;To be considered for the October cohort application and reference letters must be received in full by October 31st. Any applications received after this date will be added to the next cohort.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;February Cohort&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;If you wish to be considered for the February cohort application and reference letters must be received in full by February 28th. Any applications received after this date will be added to the next cohort.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;June Cohort&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;To be considered for the June cohort application and reference letters must be received in full by June 30th. Any applications received after this date will be added to the next cohort.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Hiring Committee reviews applications on a rolling basis three times a year: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;November, March, and July&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Please submit applications,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;using the link provided, ensuring all required materials are included in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;one PDF document&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;INTERVIEWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Please note that all interviews are currently being held remotely due to the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;We thank all applicants for their interest in this exciting opportunity and will be in touch with those whose qualifications most closely match with our needs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Achieving a more equitable, diverse and inclusive research institute is essential to creating excellent, innovative, and impactful research. The Vector Institute is committed to employment equity and diversity in the workplace and welcomes applications from women, racialized persons/visible minorities, Indigenous peoples, persons with disabilities, and LGBTQ+ persons. Should you wish to self-identify, please indicate this in your cover letter. All qualified candidates are encouraged to apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Further, we are committed to fostering an environment of inclusivity and accessibility. If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="denied:mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=136&amp;source=other</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item></items>