<items><item><title>Associate Applied Machine Learning Specialist &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;As an Associate ML Specialist, you will develop reusable software to apply and scale research breakthroughs in machine learning and AI. You will collaborate with some of Vector&#8217;s best and brightest ML engineers and data scientists, and leading industry and health organizations. In addition, you will collaborate with some of the best and brightest machine learning researchers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Deliver software and models for AI development projects following an agile methodology with teams that can include Vector Applied ML specialists, Applied ML scientists, professional staff, researchers, graduate students, and sponsors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Design and develop reference applications and model templates that apply AI research to real-world problems using public and private data sets, providing software for training, testing, operating, and updating models&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Design, develop and contribute to open-source software that applies AI research techniques to common problems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Mentor sponsor engineers and student researchers on industry collaboration projects that apply AI research to shared problems, mentor engineering best practices, and assist with operational issues&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Develop prototypes and proofs of concept&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Report and present software development outcomes for team efforts, including demos, status, and results&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Bachelor\'s degree in computer science, mathematics, electrical engineering, or related discipline; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Experience applying machine learning research to novel problems and data sets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Demonstrated experience in machine learning and statistics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Demonstrated data engineering background working with messy real-world data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Demonstrated analytical skills to identify signals in data and feasibility of prediction&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Knowledge and understanding of Python and preferably C/C++ and C#&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Software engineering background with experience in production deployment is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Experience working on teams that land high-quality software successfully in production is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Experience with parameter and architecture tuning of deep learning algorithms is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Experience in leading open-source deep learning software frameworks (PyTorch, Tensorflow, JAX, and CUDA) is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;User interaction/design expertise with Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) engineering considered an asset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Sameera Ali, Talent Acquisition Specialist, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 27, 2022.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Please note this is an internal posting only and should not be forwarded outside of the Vector Institute. An internal candidate has been identified who meets the qualifications of the role, however, we invite all internal applicants who are interested to apply for this exciting opportunity. All internal applicants will be contacted.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=211&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Project Manager &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Reporting to the Director Applied AI Projects, Industry Innovation, the Project Manager will act as an interface between external industry sponsors and internal Vector research activities and ensure the coordination and delivery of Vector industry projects that meet the direct needs of industry sponsors ranging from large enterprises to small startups. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;This role is responsible for the ideation and articulation of new projects, as well as all project management functions including monitoring and reporting on project traction and progress, coordinating the development discussion, and approval of corrective action and/or contingency plans.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Engage with industry sponsors to propose AI projects based on specific technical themes, recruit and coordinate project participants, and develop project plans and other required project documentation;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work closely with project participants to define project milestones, success measures, risks and mitigation measures;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop use cases and pilot projects in collaboration with industry sponsors and facilitate the development of new algorithms and methodologies;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Capture project success stories that can be used for public relations;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prepare reporting as required for industry sponsors, Vector&#8217;s senior staff &amp;amp; its Board of Directors;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Provide support and insight on industry sponsors to the Industry Innovation team; and,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Other related duties as assigned.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;KEY SUCCESS MEASURES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Vector achieves its goals for its industry sponsor relationships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Industry sponsorship growth and retention goals are met.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Industry sponsor feedback via informal and formal feedback mechanisms validates that Vector is providing appropriate services and support through effective working relationships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Holds, at minimum, a university degree in a business or technical field such as computer science, computer engineering or related field; PMP or PMI certification preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience leading medium-large size projects for a period of two or more years, with consulting or financial industry background preferred.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adept at building and effectively managing multidisciplinary project teams, prioritizing conflicting needs, managing limited resources, handling matters expeditiously, and following through on tasks to successful completion.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Possesses exceptional verbal and written English communication skills; effective in presenting to a diverse set of stakeholders from the business and technology ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Brings a positive attitude and energy, integrity, a sense of humour, and outlook to a corporate culture, and are motivated by continuous learning and the desire to make a difference and a real contribution to AI.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Sameera Ali, Talent Acquisition Specialist, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 12, 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=208&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Project Manager, Business Computing &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;The Vector Institute is seeking a &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Project Manager, Business Computing&lt;/span&gt;, to join our growing team in Toronto as we continue the work of making Canada a centre of expertise for AI in the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Reporting to the Systems Operations Manager, the incumbent will ensure the management, coordination, and timely execution of business IT development plans and projects&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue;"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;liaising with internal and external stakeholders to advance discussions, plans, and completion of project deliverables.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #6aa84f;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Planning and project management of Business Co&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;mputing portfolio initiatives:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Manage and support existing business technology projects or collaborations based on specific strategic themes e.g., customer relationship management software, cybersecurity/data governance, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Project plan creation, engagement with stakeholders, identifying and managing risks, and milestone tracking; and,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coordinate and liaison with project participants.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work with staff to assess feasibility of prospective business IT projects and collaborations;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Act as a liaison between work stream leaders, researchers, and business stakeholders;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Develop processes and methods to share best practices and business knowledge within the organization;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Analyze project data and prepare reporting as required for various internal and external stakeholders, up to and including the Board of Directors;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Provide business analysis and procurement support to both the Scientific Computing and AI Engineering teams, as required;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Other related duties as assigned.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;KEY SUCCESS MEASURES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: blue;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;The Business Computing team achieves its goals; and,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Internal and external stakeholder feedback is such that the Business Computing team provides high-quality service and support through effective working relationships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Holds, at minimum, a university degree in a business or technical field.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Two (2) to three (3) years experience managing projects including scoping, planning, implementation, monitoring, and project closure; Project Management Professional (PMP) certification is preferred or actively working towards a PMP designation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Experience with technology projects and platforms is considered an asset e.g., hands-on experience with project and work management tools (ClickUp, SharePoint, Google Sites);&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Adept at building and effectively communicating with multidisciplinary project teams, prioritizing conflicting needs, managing limited resources, handling matters expeditiously, and following through on tasks to successful completion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Possesses exceptional verbal and written English communication skills; effective in presenting to a diverse set of stakeholders in the business and technology ecosystems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;Brings a positive attitude and energy, integrity, a sense of humour, and outlook to a corporate culture, and is motivated by continuous learning and the desire to make a difference and a real contribution to AI.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Sameera Ali, Talent Acquisition Specialist, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 12, 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=204&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Senior Project Manager (Contract) &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt;Reporting to the Director Applied AI Projects, Industry Innovation, in this 12 month contract, the Senior Project Manager will act as an interface between external industry sponsors and internal Vector research activities and ensure the coordination and delivery of Vector industry projects that meet the direct needs of industry sponsors ranging from large enterprises to small startups. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt;This role is responsible for the ideation and articulation of new projects, as well as all project management functions including monitoring and reporting on project traction and progress, coordinating the development discussion, and approval of corrective action and/or contingency plans.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Lead engagements with industry sponsors to ideate advanced AI projects based on specific technical themes, recruit and coordinate project participants, and develop project plans and other required documentation;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Manage Project Management Interns and provide mentorship for Project Managers on project management best practices and assist with operational challenges;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Work closely with project participants to define project milestones, success measures, risks and mitigation measures;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Develop use cases and pilot projects in collaboration with industry sponsors and facilitate the development of new algorithms and methodologies;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Capture project success stories that can be used for public relations;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Prepare reporting as required for industry sponsors, Vector&#8217;s senior staff &amp;amp; its Board of Directors; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Provide support and insight on industry sponsors to the Industry Innovation team; and,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Other related duties as assigned. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt;KEY SUCCESS MEASURES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt;Vector achieves its goals for its industry sponsor relationships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Industry sponsorship growth and retention goals are met.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt;Industry sponsor feedback via informal and formal feedback mechanisms validates that Vector is providing appropriate services and support through effective working relationships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt;Holds, at minimum, a university degree in a business or technical field such as computer science, computer engineering or related field; PMP or PMI certification preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Experience leading medium-large size projects for a period of five or more years, with consulting or financial industry background preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Adept at building and effectively managing multidisciplinary project teams, prioritizing conflicting needs, managing limited resources, handling matters expeditiously, and following through on tasks to successful completion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Possesses exceptional verbal and written English communication skills; effective in presenting to a diverse set of stakeholders from the business and technology ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt;Brings a positive attitude and energy, integrity, a sense of humour, and outlook to a corporate culture, and are motivated by continuous learning and the desire to make a difference and a real contribution to AI.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Sameera Ali, Talent Acquisition Specialist, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 12, 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=209&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Technical Education Specialist &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technology is accelerating at an unprecedented rate, and more so in the field of artificial intelligence (AI). With this acceleration comes changes in the workforce, including new and exciting roles!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The role of&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Technical Education Specialist&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;combines data science machine learning skills, technical education, business insights, and the social impact of AI. This interdisciplinary role requires an understanding of data science and machine learning methods and approaches, as well as a wholistic commitment to life-long-learning and professional development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This role resides in the Professional Development (PD) team, which forms part of the broader Industry Innovation team at Vector. The PD team takes the cutting-edge research in AI by Vector&#8217;s world-class researchers and packages it into programming that the industry can absorb, through courses, workshops, talks, academic papers, blogs, and events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work with Vector industry sponsors, the Director of Professional Development, and select third parties to determine needs, requirements, and content for courses that support the deployment and operationalization of AI.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, build, implement, and continue to improve upon artificial intelligence and machine learning training programs for executives and non-technical stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, build, implement, and continue to improve upon machine learning training programs for data scientists and engineers related to data science and machine learning.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure learning and performance objectives are appropriate to the audience, and that the training materials meet the learning and performance objectives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regularly undertake a variety of administrative tasks to help organize and facilitate the activities of the Professional Development (PD) team including:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage educational programming events such as Endless Summer School (ESS) and Business Insights;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage registrations and user updates in the D2L Learning Management System;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Management content in the D2L Learning Management System (e.g., generating, uploading lessons or slides);&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage attendance and all other completion requirements (including assignments and grades) for the courses and workshops in collaboration with various members of the course team (Manager, Instructors, and TAs);&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Assist with calls for speakers from Industry, including working with the Directors of Industry Innovation to ensure appropriate engagement from industry sponsors;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage cross-functional relationships i.e., activities performed in collaboration with other teams inside Vector (e.g., Communications/Events, Academic Partnerships, Health, Research, etc.); and,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manage PD administrative documents and content.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Overall data management and reporting for the Professional Development team including contact metrics for internal and external (including government) reporting purposes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Other relevant duties as assigned.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;KEY SUCCESS MEASURES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Industry Innovation team reaches its metrics and targets (i.e., renewal and sponsorship growth) as approved by Vector&#8217;s President &amp;amp; CEO and Board of Directors.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The professional development education and upskilling program trains a minimum of 3,000 participants by 2023.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Internal and external stakeholder feedback is such that Vector\'s Industry Innovation team provides high quality service, support, and impactful data/resources as required.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have, at minimum, a graduate degree in computer science, engineering, business administration, business analytics, statistics, mathematics or another relevant field&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You demonstrate interdisciplinary interests that include technical and non-technical fields such as engineering, business analytics, computer science, ethics, graphic design etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a combination of domain expertise in data science and/or machine learning and practical industry experience. This experience may include designing, planning, and delivering on professional development courses or other programs for technical and non-technical audiences&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are an educator at heart who enjoys translating technical concepts to different audiences&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience facilitating workshops for diverse audiences&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have excellent organizational and management skills and are committed to forging relationships that will advance AI education and related activities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are a creative problem solver and enjoy collaborating within a small results-driven intrapreneurial environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have impeccable verbal, presentation, and written English communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have strong time management and organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are comfortable working with a diverse range of clients (e.g., leadership teams, operations staff, graduate students, and external partners), maintaining confidentiality and providing all with a trusted, respectful point of contact&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are technology savvy and are open to learning and mastering new software&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are motivated by continuous learning and the opportunity to make a difference and a real contribution to the AI ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You possess a positive attitude, integrity, a sense of humour, and bring positive energy and outlook to a high performing team&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Sameera Ali, Talent Acquisition Specialist, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 12, 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=210&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Applied Machine Learning Specialist AI Engineering &amp; Technology &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;As an Applied ML Specialist, you will contribute to developing reusable software to apply and scale research breakthroughs in machine learning and AI. You will collaborate with some of the best and brightest ML engineers and data scientists at Vector and leading industry and healthcare organizations. You will also collaborate with some of the best and brightest machine learning researchers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Deliver software and models for AI development projects following an agile methodology with teams that can include Vector Applied ML specialists, Applied ML scientists, professional staff, researchers, students and sponsors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Design and develop reference applications and model templates that apply AI research to real-world problems using public and private data sets, providing software for training, testing, operating and updating models&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Design, develop and contribute to open-source software that applying AI research techniques to common problems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Mentor sponsor engineers and student researchers on industry collaboration projects that apply AI research to shared problems, mentoring on engineering best practices, and assisting with operational issues&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Develop prototypes and proofs of concept&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Report and present software development outcomes for team efforts including demos, status and results&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Bachelor\'s degree in computer science, mathematics, electrical engineering, or related discipline;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Experience applying machine learning research to novel problems and data sets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Demonstrated experience in machine learning and/or statistics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Demonstrated data engineering background working with messy real-world data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Demonstrated analytical skills to identify signal in data and feasibility of prediction&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Knowledge and experience of Python and preferably C/C++ and C#&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Software engineering background with experience in production deployment is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Experience working on teams that land high quality software successfully in production is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Experience with parameter and architecture tuning of deep learning algorithms is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Experience in leading open source deep learning software frameworks (PyTorch, Tensorflow, and CUDA) is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;User interaction/design expertise with Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) engineering considered an asset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Sameera Ali, Talent Acquisition Specialist, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;May 23, 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=188&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Senior Applied Machine Learning Specialist AI Engineering &amp; Technology &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;As a Senior Applied ML Specialist, you will contribute to developing reusable software to apply and scale research breakthroughs in machine learning and AI. You will collaborate with some of the best and brightest ML engineers and data scientists at Vector and leading industry and healthcare organizations. You will also collaborate with some of the best and brightest machine learning researchers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Deliver software and models for AI development projects following an agile methodology with teams that can include Vector Applied ML specialists, Applied ML scientists, professional staff, researchers, students and sponsors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Design and develop reference applications and model templates that apply AI research to real-world problems using public and private data sets, providing software for training, testing, operating and updating models&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Design, develop and contribute to open source software that applying AI research techniques to common problems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Lead and support Associate ML Specialists in ML projects through requirements scoping, delegation of tasks, model validation, and advisory on implementation-related issues&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Mentor sponsor engineers and student researchers on industry collaboration projects that apply AI research to shared problems, mentoring on engineering best practices, and assisting with operational issues&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Develop prototypes and proofs of concept&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Report and present software development outcomes for team efforts including demos, status and results&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Master\'s degree in computer science, mathematics, electrical engineering, or related discipline;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Experience applying machine learning research to novel problems and data sets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Demonstrated experience in machine learning and/or statistics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Demonstrated data engineering background working with messy real-world data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Demonstrated analytical skills to identify signal in data and feasibility of prediction&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Knowledge and experience of Python and preferably C/C++ and C#&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Software engineering background with experience in production deployment is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Experience working on teams that land high quality software successfully in production is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Experience with parameter and architecture tuning of deep learning algorithms is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Experience in leading open-source deep learning software frameworks (PyTorch, Tensorflow, and CUDA) is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;User interaction/design expertise with Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) engineering considered an asset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family: \'Arial\',sans-serif;"&gt;Candidates with more than two years of work experience are preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Sameera Ali, Talent Acquisition Specialist, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;June 28, 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=193&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Director, Human Resources &amp; Corporate Services (Contract) Human Resources &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;POSITION SUMMARY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this 14 - 16month contract, the Director, Human Resources &amp;amp; Corporate Services will provide leadership in key operational and strategic planning at the Vector Institute, an independent, not-for-profit corporation dedicated to research in the field of artificial intelligence, excelling in machine learning and deep learning.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the Chief Operations Officer, the successful incumbent will provide leadership support across all areas of Human Resources, Office Services, and other corporate services including the ideation and oversight of the implementation of new policies, programs, activities, and processes that contribute to the achievement of organizational goals and a positive and productive workplace culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leads in the strategic planning of annual initiatives for the Human Resources, Office Services teams and other corporate services, overseeing execution of this work, development and implementation of policies, programs, activities, and processes, and ensuring legal and policy compliance; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Provides leadership and development support to members of the Human Resources and Office Services teams;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Collaborates with senior staff to make personnel, policy, and environment recommendations to support organizational goals and strategies and develop and maintain a productive and engaging workplace culture; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Supports the Human Resources and Office Services teams in resolving escalated and sensitive workplace matters; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Develops, monitors, and controls staffing-related budgets; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Acting as Vector&#8217;s corporate secretary, directs an effective governance framework and ensures compliance at the Board level;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Takes a leadership role in the organization and execution of meetings of the Board of Directors including the coordination of meeting materials and creation of meeting minutes; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Takes a leadership role in the preparation and execution of meetings of the Human Resources &lt;/span&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;span&gt; Compensation Committee, ensuring follow-though of all identified action items and points of feedback; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;In partnership with the Director, Finance and Manager, Finance, provide oversight in the preparation and execution of meetings of the Audit &amp;amp; Finance Committee, ensuring follow-though of all identified action items and points of feedback; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Oversight over Vector corporate metrics including metrics collection, verification, and distribution; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hosting of external Vector presentations and delegations as required; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 13px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Other related duties as assigned. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;KEY SUCCESS MEASURES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Feedback from Vector staff and other stakeholders validates that HR and Office Services are viewed as approachable, trusted, respected, and for providing valued services, counsel and support;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Staff reporting to the Director are effectively managed with performance and developmental support provided;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HR, Office Services, and other corporate services goals are well crafted and supportive of the achievement of broader organizational strategy;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HR, Office Services, and other corporate services objectives under their annual and strategic business plans are achieved;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;People processes at Vector run smoothly, accurately and error free;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Employee relations matters are resolved in an ethical fair manner in alignment with Vector&#8217;s policies and culture that mitigates risk for the Vector Institute.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vector maintains legislative compliance with its employment and governance policies and programs;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;5+ years of relevant HR leadership experience in complex, intellectually challenging, and fast-paced, high-growth organizations; CHRL designation or in progress;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A graduate from an HR post-grad diploma programme or holds an undergraduate degree in a related field;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience or training in broader corporate governance;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to manage a broad portfolio of HR responsibilities spanning a variety of corporate services functional areas, in an organized and detailed manner, while maintaining a calm, professional demeanour and ensuring legal and policy compliance;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience successfully leading high functioning teams;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated commitment to diversity, human rights, accessibility, and equity;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Highly effective client and candidate relationship management skills, working with stakeholders ranging from Executives to employees and world-class faculty and students;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Accurate and has highly developed and effective written and verbal communication skills; and&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Passionate about supporting and developing talent and in contributing to Vector&#8217;s success in achieving its mission and strategic objectives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Sameera Ali, Talent Acquisition Specialist, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 19, 2022.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=205&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>FastLane Program Business Analyst Industry Innovation &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reporting to the Executive Director of Applied AI Programs, the FastLane Program Business Analyst will play a key role in the implementation of the program to accelerate adoption of AI in Canadian SMEs.&amp;nbsp; This position is part of Vector&#8217;s Industry Innovation team with a mission to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d;"&gt;expand partnerships with Canadian industry through programs for talent, training, and applied AI projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Develop insights and recommendations on program strategy, SME engagement, and growth opportunities;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lead, implement, and participate in program-related activities as required;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Identify ongoing improvements to the program;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Outreach to AI and innovation ecosystem partners to identify areas of collaboration;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Build, foster, and maintain business connections with ecosystem partners and high-potential SMEs;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Perform research on high-potential SMEs/sectors;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Inform program statuses and liaise with others in the Industry Innovation and Technology workstreams;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Develop and track program metrics;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Provide assistance to build out PD programming with industry-focused associations; and,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Other duties as assigned.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span&gt;SUCCESS MEASURES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Industry Innovation team reaches its metrics and targets (i.e., client satisfaction and sponsorship growth) as approved by Vector&#8217;s President &amp;amp; CEO and Board of Directors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Internal and external stakeholder feedback is such that Vector\'s Industry Innovation team provides high quality service, support, and impactful data/resources as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sponsor and SME feedback is such that Vector\'s programs and offerings are valuable and help to improve and inform various internal processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bachelor&#8217;s degree in business, technology, or related discipline.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;1-3 years of work experience working with technology startups and scaleups.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Understanding of the competitive landscape as it relates to small- and medium-sized enterprises.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Experience in program design, implementation, and evaluation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Experience communicating with technical, business, and external stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience developing plans, building processes, and using analytics to execute successful programs in a fast-paced, dynamic environment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;An understanding of not-for-profit organizations is an asset.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Strong critical and strategic thinker.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ability to work independently on several projects concurrently and maintain focus and professionalism in high pressure environments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills with an ability to work successfully with various organizational levels, including colleagues, senior executives, and external partners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Deep interest &lt;/span&gt;in Canada\'s AI ecosystem&lt;span&gt; and knowledge economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ability to create visually compelling and professional documents, in alignment with established visual identity guidelines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Julie Semak, Human Resources Manager, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;July 15, 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=195&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Chief Executive Officer (CEO) President &amp; CEO &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-weight: bold;"&gt;Overview&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The Vector Institute (Vector) is an independent, not-for-profit corporation dedicated to research in the field of artificial intelligence (AI), excelling in deep learning and machine learning more broadly. It was founded with a vision to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. Vector was launched in March 2017 with generous support from the Government of Canada, Government of Ontario, and private industry, in partnership with the University of Toronto and other universities. Since then, Vector&#8217;s programs have helped Ontario companies apply AI across sectors and secured the province&#8217;s position as a world-leading AI hub of both talent and investment attraction. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The Vector Institute is governed by a highly accomplished volunteer &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://vectorinstitute.ai/about/#team-leadership" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Board of Directors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt; drawn from private sector, public sector, academic and research communities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Vector is among the catalysts for AI and tech-related investments that has generated a ten-fold+ return on governments&#8217; investments over a five-year period. Over the past year alone, Ontario has created approximately 22,000 AI jobs and helped retain an additional nearly 60,000 more, with over 270+ companies having invested in the Ontario AI ecosystem last year alone. Vector trained over 6,300 participants in 2021-22, including professionals from 40+ companies, through applied AI projects, upskilling workshops, and knowledge transfer programs. With Vector&#8217;s leadership and support, Ontario is expected to graduate more than 1,000 students from AI master&#8217;s programs over the past year, exceeding the province&#8217;s 2023 target ahead of schedule, which contribute to a highly-skilled workforce in Ontario and the largest AI ecosystem in North America outside of Silicon Valley.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The Vector Institute&#8217;s &lt;em&gt;vision&lt;/em&gt; is to drive excellence and leadership in Canada\'s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. Its &lt;em&gt;mission&lt;/em&gt; is to: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #002e5d; font-size: 15px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Lead Ontario&#8217;s efforts to build and sustain AI-based innovation, growth and productivity in Canada by focusing on the transformative potential of deep learning and machine learning. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #002e5d; font-size: 15px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Work with Canadian industry, in collaboration with public institutions and other AI partners, to ensure that they have the people, skills, and resources to be best in class at the use of AI. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #002e5d; font-size: 15px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;To support Canada&#8217;s innovation clusters in AI with a focus on helping startups grow to become Canadian-based global leaders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #002e5d; font-size: 15px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;To attract the best global talent focused on research excellence &#8211; where researchers and academic partners become part of a vibrant ecosystem of innovative problem-solvers, working across disciplines on both curiosity-driven and applied research.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Below are some selected areas where the Vector Institute is having impact:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #002e5d; font-size: 15px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Vector&#8217;s expert teams work directly with Ontario businesses to foster AI applications that create value by equipping industry professionals with hands-on experience working with applied AI models and providing tools and 1-on-1 guidance to simplify AI implementation. Vector also delivers training and knowledge transfer around applied AI for thousands of industry professionals, helping companies stay current with the latest advances in AI. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #002e5d; font-size: 15px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Vector ensures cutting-edge research moves beyond the lab to serve as foundations for applications in financial services, manufacturing, information technology, and health. Vector supports intellectual property (IP) commercialization as a key objective, which includes supporting entrepreneurial researchers and startup founders in filing and commercializing IP to benefit Ontarians. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #002e5d; font-size: 15px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Vector&#8217;s &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Smart Health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt; initiative is driving health innovation that improves efficiencies and care across Ontario. Specifically, Vector&#8217;s health team works with its partners to develop frameworks to improve access to data for AI with a focus on security, privacy, and confidentiality. Vector supports Ontario hospitals in the adoption of machine learning applications and partners on health data initiatives, and it also plays a vital role in scaling and deploying health innovations across Ontario by hiring AI practitioners and working with health partners across a number of institutions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #002e5d; font-size: 15px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Vector helps universities respond to the rapid rise in demand for AI talent by working with specific AI programs and employers to connect high potential talent through relevant degree programs to career opportunities that will transform Ontario&#8217;s economy. Vector also provides first-in-line access to AI talent recruitment and retention support through various events and a dedicated AI job board.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #002e5d; font-size: 15px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Vector contributes to thought leadership and AI expertise on important policy considerations and critical issues at the intersection of AI and society to support responsible AI adoption that benefits all Ontarians. This thought leadership includes creating non-competitive environments where businesses develop frameworks for addressing industry-wide challenges such as data governance and trustworthy AI.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The Role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Reporting to the Vector Institute&#8217;s Board, the Chief Executive Officer (CEO) will be responsible for setting the vision and multi-year strategy for the Vector Institute, overseeing all aspects of the organization&#8217;s operations. The CEO will ensure the Vector Institute delivers on its four key mandates, namely (i) top 10 world-leading centre for machine learning and deep learning research, (ii) expand partnerships with Canadian industry through programs for talent, training, and applied AI projects, (iii) enable effective &amp;amp; appropriate research access to health data, and iv) lead discussions on Canada\'s and Ontario\'s role in AI, including economic and societal impacts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The CEO will also develop and evolve a policy framework around AI initiatives and catalyze collaboration with Canadian ecosystem partners to enable startups, scaleups, and SMEs to leverage AI and compete more effectively in the global economy. The goal of this collaboration is to ensure Ontario&#8217;s early-mover advantage by accelerating applied AI in Ontario businesses to fuel economic growth and global competitive advantage. As well, this is a chance for the new CEO to shape the AI ecosystem by funding a broader field of fellows and civil society organizations &#8211; that will have a lasting impact for many decades to come. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Other key priorities and focus areas for this role include: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Crystalize what the evolution of AI means for Canada: for universities and for businesses, including the identification of investment opportunities to fill technology and service gaps. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Support the growth, sustainability, and commercialization of Canadian AI organizations (both established companies and startups) by partnering with Canadian industry and public institutions to ensure that they have the people, skills and resources to be best-in-class.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Increase AI job growth, attract international investment, and grow AI talent in Ontario.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Help AI organizations to navigate the complexities of emerging AI trends and shape the development of consultations on AI regulation in Canada.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Engage governments who have stated commitments to AI, ensuring their investments are deployed in the most impactful way possible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Help build a world-leading researcher and sponsor ecosystem around AI.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Attract and build a talent pipeline to ensure the Vector Institute has the right leadership, capabilities, and resources to successfully fulfil its ambitious mission. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif; font-weight: bold;"&gt;Candidate Profile&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The CEO will be a dynamic, visionary, innovative leader with AI literacy (e.g., around policy matters and applications for AI) and a passionate belief in the transformative power of AI, exceptional organizational leadership skills, and proven experience growing/scaling technology enabled organizations. The successful candidate will balance commercial leadership with a focus on both mission and purpose. They will be a highly credible, influential, and respected leader within the Canadian marketplace capable of taking the Vector Institute to the next level. This executive will have the ability to lead a mission-driven organization and work effectively across a wide range of stakeholders (e.g., industry sponsors, businesses of all sizes including startups, researchers/universities, etc.). They will be well-networked tapped into diverse ecosystems, and adept at making connections and forging partnerships across a wide range of stakeholder groups. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The successful candidate will have a proven track record of building, developing, and retaining high impact teams. As well, they will have exceptional interpersonal, communications, and presentation skills required to lead a dynamic team, interact effectively and drive consensus with the Board, and build key strategic relationships within private industry and the public sector. Exposure to the broader public and not-for-profit sectors (e.g., universities, health, governments) is advantageous but not essential. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;In terms of the performance and personal competencies required for the position, we would highlight the following:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Setting Strategy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The ability to create and articulate an inspiring vision for the organization.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The inclination to seek and analyze data from a variety of sources to support decisions and to align others with the organization\'s overall strategy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;An entrepreneurial and creative approach to developing new and innovative ideas that will stretch the organization and push the boundaries within the industry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The ability to effectively balance a desire/need for broad change with an understanding of how much change the organization is capable of handling and to create realistic goals with implementation plans that are both achievable and successful.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Executing for Results&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The ability to set clear and challenging goals while committing the organization to improved performance; tenacious and accountable in driving results.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Comfortable with ambiguity and uncertainty; the ability to adapt nimbly and lead others through complex situations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;A risk-taker who seeks data and input from others to foresee possible threats or unintended circumstances from decisions; someone who takes smart risks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;A leader who is viewed by others as having a high degree of integrity and forethought in their approach to making decisions; the ability to act in a transparent and consistent manner while always considering what is best for the organization.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Leading Teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The ability to attract and recruit top talent, motivate a team, delegate effectively, celebrate diversity, and manage performance; widely viewed as a strong developer of others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;The ability to persevere in the face of challenges and exhibit a steadfast resolve and relentless commitment to higher standards, which commands respect from followers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;A leader who is self-reflective and aware of their own limitations; leads by example and drives the organization\'s performance with an attitude of continuous improvement by being open to feedback and self-improvement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Relationships and Influence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Naturally connects and builds strong relationships with others, demonstrating strong emotional intelligence and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;an ability to communicate clearly and persuasively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;An ability to inspire trust and followership in others through compelling influence, powerful charisma, passion in their beliefs, and active drive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Encourages others to share the spotlight and visibly celebrates and supports the success of the team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Creates a sense of purpose/meaning for the team that generates followership&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt; beyond her/his own personality and engages others to the greater purpose for the organization as a whole.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Driving Sustainability&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Integrates economic, societal, and environmental factors into a purpose-driven strategy, turning sustainability into a competitive advantage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Understands and incorporates viewpoints from all key stakeholders to drive decision making and share the benefits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Delivers breakthrough innovations and business models that create value for all stakeholders, continually challenging traditional approaches.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px; font-family: Arial, sans-serif;"&gt;Sets audacious business and sustainability goals, driving concerted action and investments, and stays the course in the face of setbacks or push-back from short-term oriented stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vector has chosen to partner with Russell Reynolds Associates to conduct this search. As such, please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Russell Reynolds Associates, using &lt;a href="mailto:VectorInstitute-CEOrole@russellreynolds.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;VectorInstitute-CEOrole@russellreynolds.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:VectorInstitute-CEOrole@russellreynolds.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;VectorInstitute-CEOrole@russellreynolds.com&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=207&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Postdoctoral Fellows Research &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;POSITION OVERVIEW&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Are you an&amp;nbsp;early career researcher&amp;nbsp;with the potential to become a world-class machine learning scientist? The Vector Institute invites applications for Postdoctoral Fellows who are working on cutting-edge fundamental research in machine learning and deep learning algorithms and their applications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Our areas of research include:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Computer Vision&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Generative Models&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Healthcare &#8211; computational biology, genomics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Natural Language Processing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Optimization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Reinforcement Learning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Statistical Learning Theory&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Sequential Decision Making&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Security, Privacy &amp;amp; Fairness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Quantum Computing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The standard term for a Postdoctoral Fellow position is 1&#8211;2 years, with a possible extension to 3 years. Also available is the opportunity for eligible individuals to complete a&amp;nbsp;placement at Vector before going on to take a faculty role elsewhere.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Postdoctoral Fellows at the Vector Institute are&amp;nbsp;early career researchers&amp;nbsp;with the potential to become world-class researchers. Like postdoctoral researchers in a university lab, Postdoctoral Fellows at the Vector Institute are tasked with and supported in carrying out state-of-the-art research, publishing at the highest international level, and contributing to the academic life and reputation of the Institute. The Vector Institute offers a dynamic environment, and research freedom and opportunity to collaborate within and across research areas. They are part of a thriving research community of over 500 Vector Faculty Members, Faculty Affiliates, Postgraduate Affiliates, Postdoctoral Fellows, and graduate students.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Postdoctoral Fellows at the Vector Institute have access to the resources of a well-funded institute dedicated solely to machine learning and deep learning, and are encouraged to work with any of our over&amp;nbsp;30 world-class faculty in machine learning and deep learning, though they will work primarily with 1&#8211;2 faculty members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;They&amp;nbsp;will be expected to propose work on research topics of their interest related to machine learning and deep learning and carry out that research with a great deal of independence. Should they be so inclined, Postdoctoral Fellows may teach and mentor at the Institute; engage in entrepreneurial activities; and/or work with existing companies to enhance their research. They have the ability to collaborate with the graduate students of the machine learning group at the University of Toronto, as well as the graduate students of other affiliated faculty, who spend the bulk of their time at the Institute.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;ABOUT&amp;nbsp;VECTOR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Vector Institute is an independent non-profit corporation, with Faculty Members and Affiliates from the University of Toronto, University of Waterloo, and other Canadian universities. It is supported with generous funding from the provincial and federal governments, as well as Canadian industry sponsors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Vector Institute is located in the MaRS Discovery District building, spanning nearly the entire 7th floor and overlooking downtown Toronto and the beautiful Queen&#8217;s Park. On any given day, the Vector Institute houses over a hundred students, dozens of Faculty Members, supported with state-of-the-art compute power, and dedicated professional staff. The daily life and concentration of expertise in the Institute fosters collaboration and the exchange of ideas among its members through talks, seminar series, visitors, and tutorials.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Vector Institute&#8217;s vision is to drive excellence in the creation of artificial intelligence, to use it to foster economic growth, and to improve the lives of Canadians. To that end, the Vector Institute has close ties to both academia and industry. This puts our Postdoctoral Fellows in a unique position to contribute broadly. A successful contribution can range from developing core algorithmic techniques and theoretical analyses of machine learning algorithms, to working closely with existing companies and health organization, to engaging in entrepreneurial activities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;In addition to their research, Postdoctoral Fellows have the opportunity to work with industry to develop machine-learning-based solutions for their problems or engage in related entrepreneurial activities. We have dedicated staff facilitating all aspects of engaging with Vector sponsors and affiliated institutions, as well as close ties to incubators for entrepreneurial activities. The Vector Institute has extensive access to computing resources and datasets. We have a team of AI Engineers who help improve research productivity through software platform development, ensuring research reproducibility, publishing open source code and data, and in readying code for commercial use.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;WHO SHOULD APPLY?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;We are looking for people with interests across a broad spectrum from core machine learning or deep learning research to more applied and entrepreneurial activities. We are also looking for people who have excelled in other areas and are interested in moving into deep learning or machine learning more broadly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;PhD or equivalent in Computer Science, Statistics, Electrical Engineering, or a closely related field. You must have completed all requirements of your doctoral degree no more than three years before the application deadline;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;An excellent publication record in machine learning;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Expertise in a core area of machine learning, such as deep, unsupervised, and reinforcement learning, optimization, and theory; and/or applied machine learning, such as natural language, health, vision, robotics, medicine, biology, transportation, media, and finance;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;For those looking to pivot to machine learning from a field with technical overlap, we are looking for an excellent publication record in your field as well as expertise in an area with some potential relevance to machine learning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;APPLICATION REQUIREMENTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Please note that all documents have to be converted and merged into &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;a single PDF document&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt; and uploaded &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;as one PDF file&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;A cover letter, including identifying a Vector Faculty Member as potential supervisor. We encourage applicants to contact Faculty Members before submitting their application.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;A &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;curriculum vit&#230;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Links to at least three recent publications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;A research statement outlining a proposed program of research.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;Reference Letters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Three reference letters. One referee should be your PhD supervisor. If referees prefer to submit reference letters directly, they can be sent to&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;research@vectorinstitute.ai.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;DEADLINES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;October Cohort&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;To be considered for the October cohort application and reference letters must be received in full by October 31st. Any applications received after this date will be added to the next cohort.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;February Cohort&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;If you wish to be considered for the February cohort application and reference letters must be received in full by February 28th. Any applications received after this date will be added to the next cohort.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;June Cohort&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;To be considered for the June cohort application and reference letters must be received in full by June 30th. Any applications received after this date will be added to the next cohort.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Hiring Committee reviews applications on a rolling basis three times a year: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;November, March, and July&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Please submit applications,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;using the link provided, ensuring all required materials are included in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; text-decoration: underline;"&gt;one PDF document&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;INTERVIEWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Please note that all interviews are currently being held remotely due to the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;We thank all applicants for their interest in this exciting opportunity and will be in touch with those whose qualifications most closely match with our needs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #1d1d1d; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Achieving a more equitable, diverse and inclusive research institute is essential to creating excellent, innovative, and impactful research. The Vector Institute is committed to employment equity and diversity in the workplace and welcomes applications from women, racialized persons/visible minorities, Indigenous peoples, persons with disabilities, and 2SLGBTQIA+ persons. Should you wish to self-identify, please indicate this in your cover letter. All qualified candidates are encouraged to apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Further, we are committed to fostering an environment of inclusivity and accessibility. If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=136&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Programs Officer Research &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Vector Research Operations &amp;amp; Academic Partnerships team is seeking a dynamic and action-oriented individual in the role of Programs Officer to execute programming for Faculty Affiliates, graduate students, and alumni in AI.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Reporting to the Manager, Research Programs, and working closely with the Program Manager, Student Engagement, the incumbent will coordinate research and career development opportunities for a growing pool of students and affiliated members specializing in AI.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;Key Responsibilities:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;Build strong connections with students in Vector-recognized master&#8217;s programs and AI researchers about the programming and resources offered at Vector through initiatives such as orientation presentations, attendance at student facing events such as conferences, etc.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;Coordinate satellite/outreach events across Ontario to connect with Faculty Affiliates, graduate students, Postdoctoral Fellows, and alumni in different communities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;Provide support for career and recruitment programming for AI students&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;Work with undergraduate AI clubs across the province to support student initiatives, such as conference sponsorship, securing speakers for club events etc.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;In partnership with the Events Team, develop and build on events to bring together and showcase the strength of the research community; such as an annual research symposium, graduate visit day, and Deep Learning and Reinforcement Learning Summer School.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Support the implementation and ongoing improvement of multiple programs that contribute to the advancement of the Vector Institute\'s Al research agenda, such as the Faculty Affiliate Program and Faculty Affiliate Researcher Program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;Help establish an alumni program to connect a growing cadre of alumni to Vector programs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Other related duties as assigned.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Why you should apply:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are passionate about growing Canada&#8217;s global leadership in AI research;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have a range of experiences in student programming and community building and want to apply this to supporting a growing AI ecosystem;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are highly organized and motivated to work with diverse perspectives and ideas to foster a creative and collaborative research environment for world-class AI researchers;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You believe good ideas are important, but execution is key, and you hold yourself accountable for delivering results;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are curious and eager to challenge your comfort zone on an ongoing basis;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are entrepreneurial and thrive in a solutions-oriented environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Success Measures:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Strong, growing, and engaged student and alumni network;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Top of mind awareness of Vector&#8217;s student and researcher programming;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Excellent relationships with university student clubs and other organizations;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Well-executed programming with strong stakeholder management and service delivery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Productive relationship management with the researcher community.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The ideal candidate is hard working with great attention to detail and customer service. A strong project management skill set is vital to success in this position. In addition:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are outgoing and derive a high degree of satisfaction connecting with students and other stakeholders and strengthening a sense of community.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are a captivating and engaging presenter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have experience working with students in a post-secondary environment or similar environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have strong time management skills with a demonstrated ability to work with a diverse group of individuals in a team environment (e.g., graduate students, Faculty members, senior external researchers, leadership teams, operations staff, and graduate students), maintaining confidentiality and providing all with a trusted, respectful point of contact.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are creative and enjoy collaborating within a small entrepreneurial environment that is results-driven.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You possess a positive attitude, integrity, a sense of humour, are tactful, and bring positive energy and outlook to a not-for-profit corporate culture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have excellent verbal and written English communication skills.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have strong Excel skills and are comfortable picking up and learning new technologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Familiarity with GSuite or the Microsoft Suite of applications, Eventbrite, WordPress, and Zapier would be an asset.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Sameera Ali, Talent Acquisition Specialist, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 16, 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=202&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Research Operations Officer Research &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Vector Research Operations &amp;amp; Academic Partnerships team is seeking a dynamic and action-oriented individual in the role of Research Officer, to execute and deliver on key student funding and other core research operations initiatives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;Manage the administration of a Research Grant Program for a growing research community.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Work with Faculty members and institutional partners to manage the administration of Purchase Orders for New Graduate Student Funding, and any other contractual arrangements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Assist with the development of project plans, workflo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;ws, and process optimization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Support corporate reporting requirements such as the annual report, risk reporting, institutional reporting, travel memos, and expense claims.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Build and maintain a comprehensive section on the Vector Intranet and Vector wiki for Faculty Members, Postdoctoral Fellows, and graduate students to be able to access institutional information.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Manage computing requests for the scientific computing deadline queue.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Track and pull statistics on conference acceptances.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Other related duties as assigned.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Why you should apply:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are passionate about growing Canada&#8217;s global leadership in AI research;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are highly organized and motivated to work with diverse perspectives and ideas to foster a creative and collaborative research environment for world-class AI researchers;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You believe good ideas are important, but execution is key, and you hold yourself accountable for delivering results;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are curious and eager to challenge your comfort zone on an ongoing basis;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are entrepreneurial and thrive in a solutions-oriented environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Success Measures:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Prompt and thoughtful actions support research operations and business requirements at Vector;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Smooth running processes and tracking for funding arrangements and program delivery&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Strong relationships developed with institutional contacts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;PROFILE OF THE IDEAL CANDIDATE:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The ideal candidate is hard working with great attention to detail and customer service. A strong project management skill set is vital to success in this position. In addition:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are outgoing and derive a high degree of satisfaction connecting with students and other stakeholders and strengthening a sense of community.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have experience in student funding or other transferable experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have a high attention to detail.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have strong time management skills with a demonstrated ability to work with a diverse group of individuals in a team environment (e.g., graduate students, Faculty members, leadership teams, operations staff, graduate students, institutional partners), maintaining confidentiality and providing all with a trusted, respectful point of contact.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are creative and enjoy collaborating within a small entrepreneurial environment that is results-driven.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You possess a positive attitude, integrity, a sense of humour, are tactful, and bring positive energy and outlook to a not-for-profit corporate culture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have excellent verbal and written English communication skills.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have strong Excel skills and are comfortable picking up and learning new technologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Familiarity with GSuite or the Microsoft Suite of applications, Adobe Acrobat DC, Github, Concur and SAP.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #202124; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Experience with reporting in SalesForce is an asset.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #202124; font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"&gt;HOW TO APPLY&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Sameera Ali, Talent Acquisition Specialist, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 8, 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=201&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item><item><title>Research Services Officer Research &#183; Toronto, Ontario</title><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div class="col-xs-12 BambooRichText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 15px;"&gt;Research Services Officer&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The Vector Research Operations &amp;amp; Academic Partnerships team is seeking a dynamic and action-oriented individual in the role of Research Services Officer to support the implementation of the Vector Institute&#8217;s Canada CIFAR AI (CCAI) Chair program, which is part of the Government of Canada&#8217;s &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Pan-Canadian AI Strategy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt; (PCAIS) administered by CIFAR.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Reporting to the Manager, Research Services, the incumbent will support the recruitment, onboarding, and support of Vector Faculty Members and Vector Postdoctoral Fellows. The role will also monitor key reporting requirements for PCAIS 2 and coordinator reporting requirements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;In addition, the Research Services Officer will support initiatives that strengthen the researcher community at Vector, such as a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Visiting Researchers Program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Key Responsibilities&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Support talent recruitment and acquisition activities for faculty and postdoctoral fellows by coordinating Vector&#8217;s Recruitment and Hiring Committees.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;In concert with external university partners and internal stakeholders, ensure a strong positive experience during the faculty and postdoctoral fellow recruitment and onboarding.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Schedule and document of the annual faculty review process and steward the renewal process for CCAI Chairs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Support the Research Director and Research Operations and Academic Partnerships team to foster a strong culture of collaboration and dialogue among faculty and researchers, as well as initiatives to enable professional development among faculty.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Coordinate annual reporting requirements for formal Affiliation Agreements with partner institutions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Support a Visiting Researchers Program including review process, recruitment, and onboarding of Visiting Researchers to Vector.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;With Manager, Research Services, ensure the Vector Institute&#8217;s formal agreement with CIFAR is executed, and accountability requirements and reporting metrics are delivered in an accurate and timely manner.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Other related duties as assigned.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Why you should apply:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are passionate about growing Canada&#8217;s global leadership in AI research;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have a range of experiences in either a research institute or university setting as well as experience in program implementation and project management;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are highly organized and motivated to work with diverse perspectives and ideas to foster a creative and collaborative research environment for world-class AI researchers;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You believe good ideas are important, but execution is key, and you hold yourself accountable for delivering results;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are curious and eager to challenge your comfort zone on an ongoing basis;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You are entrepreneurial and thrive in a solutions-oriented environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Success Measures:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Prompt and thoughtful actions support research operations and business requirements at Vector;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Smooth running processes and tracking for PCAIS agreements;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Well-executed programming with strong stakeholder management and service delivery and,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Productive relationship management with Vector Faculty Members and its researcher community.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Profile of the Ideal Candidate:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;The ideal candidate is hard working with great attention to detail and customer service. A strong project management skill set is vital to success in this position. In addition:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Ability to effectively collaborate with a diverse range of individuals and perspectives across a broad range of sectors and stakeholders;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Exceptional communication and organizational skills as you work with multiple stakeholders and concurrent priorities;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;High attention to detail as it relates to contractual and complex reporting requirements;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;2+ years of strong, practical real-world experience in roles that have included project delivery, program implementation, policy analysis, and stakeholder coordination;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;Experience that provides strong knowledge of an academic research environment is a strong asset;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;You have a data-driven mindset and the ability to translate data into actionable insights with a keen eye for detail and an ability to quickly identify and troubleshoot problems that arise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"&gt;How to Apply&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please address applications (cover letter and resume) to Sameera Ali, Talent Acquisition Specialist, using the link provided. The deadline for submission is &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;August 16, 2022.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the Vector Institute we are committed to driving excellence and leadership in Canada&#8217;s knowledge, creation, and use of AI to foster economic growth and improve the lives of Canadians. We strive for greater inclusion in the programs and culture that we build by welcoming and encouraging applications from all qualified candidates. This includes but is not limited to applicants who are Indigenous, 2SLGBTQIA+, racialized persons/visible minorities, women, and people with disabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you require an accommodation at any point throughout the recruitment and selection process, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:hr@vectorinstitute.ai" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hr@vectorinstitute.ai&lt;/a&gt; and we will happily work with you to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><url>https://vectorinstitute.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=203&amp;source=bamboohr&amp;source=Vector_talent_hub</url><logo>https://talenthub.vectorinstitute.ai/uploads/employer/logo/319524/Just_Vector_Logo.png</logo><company>Vector Institute</company></item></items>